Alright, okay, I gotta take a moment to collect myself here.
Next target.
What do we have?
Okay, looking for a description of Terminator morphology, I think?
Let me get oriented.
Whoa!
Angela, you guys!
You're not gonna believe this!
What?
I really think I just saw a flash here!
No, you didn't!
No, it was a bright white flash, really tiny, but it was there.
Did you see it, Trevor?
Yeah, come on over here.
Well, I guess you missed it now, huh?
I wonder if any of the saw cameras caught that.
It was just like a bright white light over there in the unilluminated portion of the moon, really fleeting, but that was inspiring.
Where was it?
Well, so here I am in the port forward window, and I think it was kind of like off in the upper right quadrant of my view here.
Wow, that was incredible.
I hope you can pull this out of other vehicle data.
I mean, wow.
We got to get a seismometer on the moon ASAP.
I'll be honest, I was kind of skeptical we'd see one of these, but we sure got lucky.
What an experience.
I think I remember this was really high priority for the lunar science team, so I'm really glad we got this data point for them.
All right, mark the time that you've seen it.
Yeah.