Alright, I'm getting set up in the forward port window and Kelsey's got the camera in the starboard window.
Next up on our target list looks to be the Apollo Basin.
Got a good close view of that in our current orientation, mostly by eyes, but I did take a quick look at it through the camera at the highest zoom.
Our orientation is slightly oblique, but got a pretty good view of it now.
Just want to say a few things about the size.
It's really filling the field of view of the camera at full zoom when I took that quick peek, and hopefully Kelsey's capturing that now.
It's hard to make out the boundaries in this illumination I definitely can make out the boundary where the contact is to that larger crater from Apollo To its left side.
Let me look real quick and see what crater that is Hang on one second.
Oh, it's Oppenheimer.
So yeah, just to
what I'll say the left of Apollo is Oppenheimer in our current orientation and so it can definitely make out some very distinctive structure there between the two.
What I did want to point out here is the pronounced rust color that I'm picking up on the mare that's nearest to Oppenheimer.
So the mare I'm talking about is, there's like a mare in the center of Apollo Basin, and then there's a smaller little patch closer to that Oppenheimer crater.
And I'm picking up a really distinctive rust color, especially in this illumination condition.
The mare in the center of
of Apollo Basin doesn't look to have that rust color.
It looks darker to me, a little bit on the, you know, blacker side.
And then the mare to the south, so if Oppenheimer is at nine o'clock, so at six o'clock of Apollo Basin, the mare to the south may also have that slight rust color that I'm picking up.
But definitely the
The mare at the nine o'clock closest to Oppenheimer's got this really interesting rust color that I haven't seen that, certainly not in our other observations.
Overall, just checking my cue card here.
Oh, the shadows, yeah, just not too much shadows.
As I said, this illumination condition's not picking out a lot of shadows, but I do really see some distinctive structure between Apollo
Oppenheimer.
That's kind of what's sticking out to me most as far as the structure and also that range just to the left side or the nine o'clock of the center of Apollo Basin.
There's a mountain range, I'll call it, that runs kind of north-south or from between 12 o'clock and 6 o'clock just to the left of that central mare.
That's also really sticking out to me and hopefully Kelsey's capturing that in some of the photos.
Yeah, that's all I want to say on Apollo.
I'm going to go check on the target list for the next one.
Thanks.