Okay, next up on the LTP, Orientale.
Alright, looks like they're specifically asking us to focus on the angular range, but I need to look at the LGR to refresh my memory.
Okay, yeah, beautiful impact basin right here.
Let me try to make sure I'm looking at the right thing here, though.
Okay, yeah, pretty distinctive feature, and I know it's one of our geography anchor points.
Jacob, don't worry, I did my geography homework.
All right, Angela's next to me.
I know she's working on getting it in her camera view, but for now I'll say, whew, this is a beauty.
Angela, you see this?
Uh, yeah, just give me, give me a second.
I'm just trying to get to the right, uh,
Oh, no.
All right.
Yeah.
Oh, that's that.
Oh, wow.
I know.
Beautiful multi-ring base in here.
It's off to the left of Oceanus Procellarum, maybe at a distance of like one oriental diameter.
It's roughly circular.
Two primary sets of rings.
which rim kind of a dark mari patch i think in the middle the mare patch is roughly circular maybe slightly elongate uh in the north south axis the dark patch is quite dark especially at its southern end but the northern end has a much brighter albedo
Yeah, I got some good, got some good pictures over here.
Alright, did you, cause like, I can't quite make out the detail with my naked eye.
Can you look at the northern end of the Mare patch?
I'd be interested to hear your take, but it looks like maybe a much brighter, and I think maybe they said that that means younger crater came in here and it's sending its ejecta down into the Mare patch?
Yeah, let me just try and get this focus.
It's kind of hard to, to kind of stay in.
in with what I'm trying to target when I'm moving around a little bit.
So just give me a second while I'm rolling on here.
All right.
Just want to make sure I'm not crazy.
Here, let me help you with that.
Hold on.
Yeah, here.
Do you want to use the camera to just get it better?
No, no, no.
You got it.
I'll just anger you here for a second.
OK.
All right, let's see.
I see a few other younger craters on top of the mare patch.
My personal favorite, wow, now that I'm looking at this, it's a crater just to the east of like the main big mare patch that maybe itself, the crater looks like it has its own tiny little patch of dark material within it.
Interesting.
I might need to hear the science team's interpretation of that one.
Angela, can you get a picture of my favorite crater over here?
Yeah, point it up, right there.
It's this one, right off to the right side of that mare patch.
Look at it, it's got a little baby mare patch in it.
Oh, I see it!
It's so cute!
Look at the picture!
Oh, that's awesome.
Alright, I think we got it, science.
Okay, so, sorry, I know I'm getting really distracted by these smaller craters.
You know how I love craters.
Back to Orientale proper here.
Looks like its mare patch has rounded edges in most places, whereas the two rings have sort of like a scalloped look.
The inner of the two rings looks like it's got some topography to it.
It's not fully continuous all the way around.
Not sure if it's just an illumination effect, but the that southern end of the ring looks like it has more of like a topography pop to it, especially down at like the five to six o'clock position.
I say that because there's like a higher albedo section of that inner ring that just pops.
over up on the northeast side of the inner ring maybe between like i don't know midnight and three o'clock there's a lot going on wow geez throughout that whole section there's a patch of the dark low albedo mare-like material it starts just inside the inner ring it's not too big all right wow and look distracted i know i'm supposed to be thinking about the annular ring do you remember what they mean by annular ring
Uh, yeah, it's in your lunar target.
It's in your lunar dot!
All right, fine, yeah, check the tape.
All right, I can't quite tell here, but maybe they mean this dark circle down here to the south.
Oh yeah, that's ringing a bell from training.
Now that I'm looking at this... Angela, what is this?
It's a circular feature, but it's definitely not a crater.
or I don't really see any topography it looks kind of like just like a dark ring of material like lower albedo that looks kind of like I don't know superficial on top of everything else I even see a place at like three o'clock on the ring where it's sitting on top of the inner oriental ring I I remember my superposition science team don't worry it's younger than that ring the ring is more concentrated and darker for like the whole top half whereas like the southern half is kind of diffuse and I think slightly higher in albedo is what I'm seeing but Angela I'd like to hear if you you see the same
Yeah, I think it's a little bit higher in albedo.
That's what I'd agree.
But don't worry, I'm going to get pictures.
Because really, I don't know.
I trust my eyes right now.
I've been staring at this bright moon for a little bit too long.
It can never be too long.
All right.
Well, OK.
I've been talking for a while.
I have no idea how long.
I hope this didn't get us off timeline.
All right, last big picture comment.
I know you want us to talk about facial relationships.
I do see a really bright, really small crater off to the east side of Orientale.
It's got some beautiful bright rays coming out that do cross Orientale, and that's a beauty.
I wish I could remember what it's called.
And that's Orientale, folks.
What a ride.
Woo!