This is Marie for ImageA.
I'm looking at the Mare Crisium from the email and I'm looking at it with my eyes on a computer screen right in front of me.
The target is located in the northern hemisphere to the west of the visible moon.
It is to the east of Mare Trunculitatis and to the
west of Smithy and something else.
This is a pretty large mare filled crater that is smaller than the Mare Tranquilitatis to the west but pretty similar in size to the Mare Smithy down below.
And it is more circular in shape, almost looks like a snail or an eyeball where it has a circular piece with a little bit more coming off to the west.
The edges are not sharp.
They're more, they look scalloped, but that's just different, sort of rounded infills.
It is a, for color, it is a,
grayer tone than the surface around it.
It's got a lower albedo.
It is one of the darkest things that we see.
It is very similar to a lot of the other dark areas that are visible on the moon right now.
The color is not smooth.
It has lines and streaks of a lighter color across them, mostly originating from a
bright raid crater to the west of the mare.
The texture looks smooth in this area of the moon.
You can't see a lot of relief.
You can tell there are some smaller craters that are impacted into it, but a lot of the relief is on the visible eastern limb of the moon.
Let's see.
well defined compared to what's around it.
The slopes, the topography isn't very, it's very hard to pick out here.
You can tell that there are some imprinted impacts.
Let's see.
Some of the streaks are for radiologic relationships.
Some of the streaks that are going across the mare seem to be radiating from other really bright craters, both to the sort of nine o'clock position to the west and more of like the 435 position down to the southeast.
And also there's a radiating bright crater
at the about 131 to 12 position up there.
Let's see.
For thoughts, this looks like a very dark area, very smooth, not a lot of details that can be picked out, but the largest changes that we're seeing here is albedo differences.
We'll call that one done.