All right, for image C, that is the terminator and the limb of the moon that I am looking at as a target from the email you sent me.
And I am identifying it with my eyeballs on a computer screen just in front of me.
I can see the sliver, looks like the crescent of the moon.
on the eastern limb that is illuminated with the rest of the lunar surface being dark.
You can see that there are some you can see some evidence of craters potentially some linear features in there as well along there it's sort of it's
very slim margin of the moon.
Let's see, you can see part of it is potentially a mare region.
The outer edge of the moon has a very crisp edge and the terminator edge is a little bit fuzzier.
Along the, we see for color the whiter outside and it becomes grayer as we get closer to the terminator.
Inside one of the craters that is seen from about a quarter of the way down, you can see a very dark interior and then you see a linear raised topographic feature coming out.
And then you can see craters mostly on the lower half of the crescent that are more evident there.
Yeah, the top has more of a grayer tone than the bottom half.
It has a higher contrast of features.
The texture towards the southern part of the crescent is rougher.
It looks smoother towards the upper part.
see topography.
You can actually see raised crater rims.
You can see looks like some peak structures down towards the bottom part potentially that raise a linear feature towards the top.
We can see some topography as I have talked about.
We see that there is light coming
we talked about the light coming onto the surface of the moon from the east and like towards the equatorial region is where that light is the brightest.
geologic relationships in the upper portion of the crescent on what appears could be a grayer region which is more of a mare region.
You can see a raised rim of a crater with that linear feature on top of the potentially on top of the mare.
And you can see overlapping of craters in the southern part.
This is another very pretty one.
Every- my impressions every time I look at these, they're beautiful.
And... That's it.
Hopefully this isn't what the moon's gonna look like when they're seeing it because that means we are about to go around and just stare at a dark moon.
And that'd be pretty sad.
Okay.
Done.