Okay, next up is Leibniz Target.
Kelsey's got the camera.
I'm now in the port starboard window making observations, trying to get oriented.
The target name is Leibniz Crater.
Trying to get oriented.
It's a little bit skewed to us now, so doing some magic here with the tablet to get oriented.
oblique to us and got a pretty good view at it.
And I think the target is to try to get a good zoom on this one, Kelsey.
It's a really circular crater.
If I'm looking at the right one with Leibniz, it's got a rubbly texture that surrounds the interior of the crater.
It's got really two unique craters inside of it.
One is, I can see the depression given this illumination, the other one looks like it's infilled a little bit, looks like two eyes if I turn my head the right way, and then the the face of the crater or the nose of the crater would, there is a some distinctive color change
I think this may be something that I was cuing my eyes into earlier with these lunar swirls and a little bit of color change.
It's definitely brighter in that area.
Again, struggling with the orientation, but I believe
I believe Oppenheimer and Apollo Basin were just to the north of this now or just upwards of this.
I don't know if I've got my orientation right, but I could be a little screwed up on this one.
Hopefully the camera will capture its orientation with the surrounding craters.
Shadows are coming from the bottom up now and making the six o'clock of our view right now very distinctive, that rubbly texture I described at the more southern or the six o'clock position of the crater.
and the 12 o'clock position of the crater from our orientation definitely has a disturbed rim as a medium-sized crater has definitely disturbed that rim and made some unique features in there.
Slopes look pretty crazy in that rubbly area and the textures are just pretty flat across the middle of that crater, just
wanted to definitely highlight and hopefully the camera captures that unique colorization that we're seeing in some of that possible lunar swirls.
Um, it's a tonal difference, definitely makes it stand out.
Um, and the, the swirl part is a little bit lighter toned.
Uh, I would say medium gray leading up to that a little bit brighter white to tan, um, lunar swirl area in the center of the crater as described.
Okay.
Onto the next target.