All right, next up is Mare Ingenii.
I'm going to the forward window with the camera in hand.
It's just me up here trying to make a lot of observations, zooming in with my camera here.
So I'm just going to do some talk out loud for you.
All right, so Ingenii, let me first orient myself.
I've got no oblique view from the lunar
targeting plan.
Let's see, north there, so go south.
Really just looking along the terminator.
That's what I expect my main indicator will be.
This is a pretty cool looking
cool looking mare.
Okay, so I see, okay, I've found SBA.
I'm looking just along the terminator.
It's like from this image that my plan.
Looking for mare info, got some irregular shapes spilling out.
Yeah, okay, I'm not really seeing it yet.
I'm just continue looking down.
Okay, I'm seeing a crater that has these kind of five
like, craters aligned within it.
You know, in this kind of elongated snowman-looking crater.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, now I'm seeing it.
It kind of looks, this Injunai kind of looks like a, almost like an octopus shape, with the kind of legs of the octopus facing away from the Terminator.
All right, okay, I'm seeing it now.
I think I was trying to look a little too early because it was still in shadow.
So, yeah, I see it now.
And it's a really clear circular shape where the boundary facing away from the Terminator is at the broken part of this kind of circle.
So it's not a complete circle because when I zoom in with my camera, there's almost this like elongated island in the broken boundary.
And that island is kind of like maybe less than a quarter.
of this overall shape.
And again, that kind of broken part of that circle is facing away from the Terminator.
That's really cool.
But yeah, overall Engine Eye also has like a raised, like bigger ridge that's like around and like encircling the crater.
It's at least an interrelating part of it.
Kind of looks like a C-shape from where I'm at now, where the opening of the C is kind of disappearing into the darkness of the Terminator.
So maybe I'll just keep an eye on that for the next time I come around here.
But yeah, the interior doesn't look solid.
It actually kind of has some albedo variations where there is lighter and darker, but I mean, I'm not really seeing a pattern in there.
So it doesn't really look smooth either.
That basin kind of looks undulating or hummocky, maybe even seeing a wrinkle in there.
Yeah, and I'm also seeing like maybe, if I zoom in, I think I do see like little specks and little craters in here.
But yeah, that wrinkle is parallel and like kind of in the same strike as that island of that boundary that I described, that kind of broken outer boundary of Ingenii.
So that's cool.
I can't see too much more, so I'll end it there and then I'll come back to this in a little bit.
### Transcript 002
Okay, next up on the LTP, Orientale.
Alright, looks like they're specifically asking us to focus on the angular range, but I need to look at the LGR to refresh my memory.
Okay, yeah, beautiful impact basin right here.
Let me try to make sure I'm looking at the right thing here, though.
Okay, yeah, pretty distinctive feature, and I know it's one of our geography anchor points.
Jacob, don't worry, I did my geography homework.
All right, Angela's next to me.
I know she's working on getting it in her camera view, but for now I'll say, whew, this is a beauty.
Angela, you see this?
Uh, yeah, just give me, give me a second.
I'm just trying to get to the right, uh,
Oh, no.
All right.
Yeah.
Oh, that's that.
Oh, wow.
I know.
Beautiful multi-ring base in here.
It's off to the left of Oceanus Procellarum, maybe at a distance of like one Orientale diameter.
It's roughly circular.
Two primary sets of rings.
which rim kind of a dark mare patch i think in the middle the mare patch is roughly circular maybe slightly elongate uh in the north south axis the dark patch is quite dark especially at its southern end but the northern end has a much brighter albedo
Yeah, I got some good, got some good pictures over here.
Alright, did you, cause like, I can't quite make out the detail with my naked eye.
Can you look at the northern end of the Mare patch?
I'd be interested to hear your take, but it looks like maybe a much brighter, and I think maybe they said that that means younger crater came in here and it's sending its ejecta down into the Mare patch?
Yeah, let me just try and get this focus.
It's kind of hard to, to kind of stay in.
in with what I'm trying to target when I'm moving around a little bit.
So just give me a second while I'm rolling on here.
All right.
Just want to make sure I'm not crazy.
Here, let me help you with that.
Hold on.
Yeah, here.
Do you want to use the camera to just get it better?
No, no, no.
You got it.
I'll just anger you here for a second.
OK.
All right, let's see.
I see a few other younger craters on top of the mare patch.
My personal favorite, wow, now that I'm looking at this, it's a crater just to the east of like the main big mare patch that maybe itself, the crater looks like it has its own tiny little patch of dark material within it.
Interesting.
I might need to hear the science team's interpretation of that one.
Angela, can you get a picture of my favorite crater over here?
Yeah, point it up, right there.
It's this one, right off to the right side of that mare patch.
Look at it, it's got a little baby mare patch in it.
Oh, I see it!
It's so cute!
Look at the picture!
Oh, that's awesome.
Alright, I think we got it, science.
Okay, so, sorry, I know I'm getting really distracted by these smaller craters.
You know how I love craters.
Back to Orientale proper here.
Looks like its mare patch has rounded edges in most places, whereas the two rings have sort of like a scalloped look.
The inner of the two rings looks like it's got some topography to it.
It's not fully continuous all the way around.
Not sure if it's just an illumination effect, but the that southern end of the ring looks like it has more of like a topography pop to it, especially down at like the five to six o'clock position.
I say that because there's like a higher albedo section of that inner ring that just pops.
over up on the northeast side of the inner ring maybe between like i don't know midnight and three o'clock there's a lot going on wow geez throughout that whole section there's a patch of the dark low albedo mare-like material it starts just inside the inner ring it's not too big all right wow and look distracted i know i'm supposed to be thinking about the annular ring do you remember what they mean by annular ring
Uh, yeah, it's in your lunar target.
It's in your lunar dot!
All right, fine, yeah, check the tape.
All right, I can't quite tell here, but maybe they mean this dark circle down here to the south.
Oh yeah, that's ringing a bell from training.
Now that I'm looking at this... Angela, what is this?
It's a circular feature, but it's definitely not a crater.
or I don't really see any topography it looks kind of like just like a dark ring of material like lower albedo that looks kind of like I don't know superficial on top of everything else I even see a place at like three o'clock on the ring where it's sitting on top of the inner Orientale ring I I remember my superposition science team don't worry it's younger than that ring the ring is more concentrated and darker for like the whole top half whereas like the southern half is kind of diffuse and I think slightly higher in albedo is what I'm seeing but Angela I'd like to hear if you you see the same
Yeah, I think it's a little bit higher in albedo.
That's what I'd agree.
But don't worry, I'm going to get pictures.
Because really, I don't know.
I trust my eyes right now.
I've been staring at this bright moon for a little bit too long.
It can never be too long.
All right.
Well, OK.
I've been talking for a while.
I have no idea how long.
I hope this didn't get us off timeline.
All right, last big picture comment.
I know you want us to talk about facial relationships.
I do see a really bright, really small crater off to the east side of Orientale.
It's got some beautiful bright rays coming out that do cross Orientale, and that's a beauty.
I wish I could remember what it's called.
And that's Orientale, folks.
What a ride.
Woo!
### Transcript 003
All right, next up for me is a Terminator target.
I'm still in the port forward window.
I'm going to take a mosaic here.
Some other crew members got called off on another task, so I'm going to try to go both take the pictures and description at the same time here, see how that goes.
Capturing a mosaic now along the terminator for this target.
So again, I'm using both my eyes and camera looking up and down just over the viewfinder as I'm making these observations and taking the photos.
This is a oblique view trying to capture the top, which I think our orientation right now is with the moon kind of upright or north from our current attitude.
And one of the things that's really sticking out to me that I'll describe and hopefully capture it in this mosaic is the larger impact basin.
I'm not sure of the name of that one yet, but
It's a larger impact basin with a medium-sized crater kind of at it's seven or eight o'clock.
It's near the northern pool at least and it's the terminators right on it right now which is really making it pop.
So hopefully capturing good photos of that.
No noticeable hues or colors.
It's mostly really dark on the west side or the left of my left right now of the terminator not seeing anything beyond that crater that I described at a larger impact basin.
and then it's just shades of gray as we go eastward.
What's really popping is the smaller craters as well.
What I'm seeing is the shadows almost fill the bottom of the medium-sized craters, but the small craters
are really popping more than what we've seen a little bit earlier.
And it really makes for a unique texture across the illuminated portion.
Hopefully got that mosaic for you and gonna bounce on the next target.
I think I'm a little bit behind my timeline and call this mosaic good.
### Transcript 004
Okay, next up is Leibnitz Target.
Kelsey's got the camera.
I'm now in the port starboard window making observations, trying to get oriented.
The target name is Leibnitz Crater.
Trying to get oriented.
It's a little bit skewed to us now, so doing some magic here with the tablet to get oriented.
oblique to us and got a pretty good view at it.
And I think the target is to try to get a good zoom on this one, Kelsey.
It's a really circular crater.
If I'm looking at the right one with Leibnitz, it's got a rubbly texture that surrounds the interior of the crater.
It's got really two unique craters inside of it.
One is, I can see the depression given this illumination, the other one looks like it's infilled a little bit, looks like two eyes if I turn my head the right way, and then the the face of the crater or the nose of the crater would, there is a some distinctive color change
I think this may be something that I was cuing my eyes into earlier with these lunar swirls and a little bit of color change.
It's definitely brighter in that area.
Again, struggling with the orientation, but I believe
I believe Oppenheimer and Apollo Basin were just to the north of this now or just upwards of this.
I don't know if I've got my orientation right, but I could be a little screwed up on this one.
Hopefully the camera will capture its orientation with the surrounding craters.
Shadows are coming from the bottom up now and making the six o'clock of our view right now very distinctive, that rubbly texture I described at the more southern or the six o'clock position of the crater.
and the 12 o'clock position of the crater from our orientation definitely has a disturbed rim as a medium-sized crater has definitely disturbed that rim and made some unique features in there.
Slopes look pretty crazy in that rubbly area and the textures are just pretty flat across the middle of that crater, just
wanted to definitely highlight and hopefully the camera captures that unique colorization that we're seeing in some of that possible lunar swirls.
Um, it's a tonal difference, definitely makes it stand out.
Um, and the, the swirl part is a little bit lighter toned.
Uh, I would say medium gray leading up to that a little bit brighter white to tan, um, lunar swirl area in the center of the crater as described.
Okay.
Onto the next target.
### Transcript 005
Alright, I'm getting set up in the forward port window and Kelsey's got the camera in the starboard window.
Next up on our target list looks to be the Apollo Basin.
Got a good close view of that in our current orientation, mostly by eyes, but I did take a quick look at it through the camera at the highest zoom.
Our orientation is slightly oblique, but got a pretty good view of it now.
Just want to say a few things about the size.
It's really filling the field of view of the camera at full zoom when I took that quick peek, and hopefully Kelsey's capturing that now.
It's hard to make out the boundaries in this illumination I definitely can make out the boundary where the contact is to that larger crater from Apollo To its left side.
Let me look real quick and see what crater that is Hang on one second.
Oh, it's Oppenheimer.
So yeah, just to
what I'll say the left of Apollo is Oppenheimer in our current orientation and so it can definitely make out some very distinctive structure there between the two.
What I did want to point out here is the pronounced rust color that I'm picking up on the mare that's nearest to Oppenheimer.
So the mare I'm talking about is, there's like a mare in the center of Apollo Basin, and then there's a smaller little patch closer to that Oppenheimer crater.
And I'm picking up a really distinctive rust color, especially in this illumination condition.
The mare in the center of
of Apollo Basin doesn't look to have that rust color.
It looks darker to me, a little bit on the, you know, blacker side.
And then the mare to the south, so if Oppenheimer is at nine o'clock, so at six o'clock of Apollo Basin, the mare to the south may also have that slight rust color that I'm picking up.
But definitely the
The mare at the nine o'clock closest to Oppenheimer's got this really interesting rust color that I haven't seen that, certainly not in our other observations.
Overall, just checking my cue card here.
Oh, the shadows, yeah, just not too much shadows.
As I said, this illumination condition's not picking out a lot of shadows, but I do really see some distinctive structure between Apollo
Oppenheimer.
That's kind of what's sticking out to me most as far as the structure and also that range just to the left side or the nine o'clock of the center of Apollo Basin.
There's a mountain range, I'll call it, that runs kind of north-south or from between 12 o'clock and 6 o'clock just to the left of that central mare.
That's also really sticking out to me and hopefully Kelsey's capturing that in some of the photos.
Yeah, that's all I want to say on Apollo.
I'm going to go check on the target list for the next one.
Thanks.
### Transcript 006
Okay, what do we got here?
What's next?
What's next Buys-Ballot?
Oh I'm not sure.
I remember this too.
Well, you're gonna need to give me some direction Yeah, I'm gonna need to give myself some direction.
All right, let's pull up the lunar geography review.
I know we're on the far side Clicking in there
Oh gosh, it's not even on this medium label.
It's right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
That's a small sucker.
Okay.
It should be like halfway between Jackson and Moscoviense.
So let's see here.
Let me go back to the targeting plan.
Let me see what we got.
Okay.
This is tough.
What am I even looking at here?
Where?
I got my camera ready.
Should Moscoviense be off to the west, Angela?
I don't know.
I can't see Moscoviense anymore.
Oh, is there a possibility?
Is this upside down?
All right, let me flip this upside down here.
What do we got?
Okay.
So the image in the targeting plan was upside down, but now I think I got it.
So I think I see Jackson Crater, that really popped.
So it looks like Buys-Ballot, yep, they're telling me it should be pretty, pretty close to... How pretty is pretty?
That's a good question.
Like the size of Jackson?
Yeah, yeah.
It's maybe like, it's about the size of Jackson and it's maybe about like...
i don't even know eight to ten jackson diameters which direction to the i think if i'm looking at this right it's to the west to the west so yeah okay yeah all right so i think i got it here that took a while sorry about that shape stuff because i'm looking at a lot of graders that might be around that size
Yeah, the shape, wow, look at this.
This is, this almost looks like, I don't know, like an arrowhead or something.
Like it's, it's... Oh, I got it.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll take some pictures now.
Yeah, it's like an arrowhead feature and there's actually like a higher topographic ridge that runs through the middle of Buys-Ballot.
So let me see here.
yeah and it's it's kind of sitting on or under i can't quite tell from here no it's got to be sitting on a crater that's just sort of at the fat arrowhead end yeah and it's that that one it's sitting on looks like it's got more muted topography i'm thinking and the tip of the arrow is kind of pointing at like uh oh i guess it's telling me on the ltp it's the Lacus Luxuriae Region
Oh, I see.
It looks like kind of like a spillout.
Yeah.
It's a dark kind of like grayish blue looking.
Okay.
I'll take some pictures of that.
Slightly the area outside of Buys-Ballot is kind of like darker and albedo and then Boy's Ballad does look kind of crisp next to the surrounding features I'm thinking.
Does it look like it's spilling out because it kind of looks like it's coming from maybe that arrow point to me?
Maybe.
It's kind of hard to tell and I guess
Yeah, I mean, maybe one edge of Buys-Ballot looks more muted in topography than the other edge.
Do you see what I'm saying here?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it might be the shadows, but yeah, I see what you mean by that.
Alright, I'll be honest.
I'm not too sure what's going on here.
I know that there can be some weird-looking craters, but this one is an oddball.
I think all we can really do here, Angela, is get some pictures of it and hope that the science team back on Earth can figure this out for us.
Yep, I'll make sure that my focus of my camera is all over that area so you can maybe do some cool stuff with the photos, but I got the pictures.
Alright, moving on.
### Transcript 007
all righty i heard that we're gonna start to see the moon so buckle up i got my cam ready oh wow oh i'm starting to see this liver this liver of the it looks like a wow what do you got yeah it's earth peeking from behind the moon and it is
Beautiful!
Hey!
Trevor!
Kelsey!
Whatever you're doing, get over here!
This is what we've been waiting for!
And look out the window!
It's, it's everything right... there.
Wow.
A beauty!
That's, that's something special.
That's, that's pretty breathtaking.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna take a moment.
Yeah, wow.
Take a look at that.
Alright, I'm doing it.
I'm blocking it out with my thumb.
It's an honor, guys.
There's really no one I'd rather be here right now in this moment than with you guys.
Back at ya.
Trevor, stop what you're doing over there.
Stop being productive.
Come on over and take a look at this.
All right, all right.
Okay, I'll start to describe.
Yeah, I'm seeing the, oh, it's just, it's hard to do the science, but I'm looking at something so special.
Yeah, I'm seeing the blues.
Dark and light blues.
The white's really standing out.
Hi, Antarctica!
Earth's South Pole looks pretty great from over here.
Oh, I can see you guys, Houston.
See those swirls of clouds.
South America.
Oh, don't worry, Earth.
I'm getting pictures of all your good angles.
You're looking great from here, Houston.
Oh, all right.
And now I take a full Earth.
So mark this time.
That's when the...
I can see it all.
There's no more shadow of the moon on the Earth.
So that's pretty crazy.
Space has never looked so black from over here.
So yes, Earth is coming right above or north of the equator or the equatorial line.
So like if north is 12 o'clock, we're looking at like 930.
Man, the Earth looks so smooth.
It looks peaceful from here, doesn't it?
It really does.
And the far side of the moon looks pretty rough compared to just how smooth and beautiful the Earth is.
I'm feeling like the luckiest person, not on Earth, luckiest person around the moon right now.
Yeah, I can see it all, Houston.
I'm starting to feel a little homesick.
But yeah, I'm looking through my camera lens.
See a little bit more detail for you guys.
I can see the greens and the browns.
See Amazon rainforests.
Maybe those are the Andes.
Absolutely gorgeous.
Angela's got some good pictures here.
Hey, mark this up.
This is definitely the first one that we're going to have to send down back to Earth.
People are going to want to see these pictures as soon as we can.
So prep yourself, Houston.
You've got some beautiful shots coming down.
I can't wait to tell you all about it.
Oh my god.
I could cry.
### Transcript 008
All right, Houston, I'm coming back to Ingenii.
So I did a pass on Ingenii in a more oblique view, and now I'm coming back at a more nadir view, now that some time has passed.
And it's super easy to find now, because I know exactly what I'm looking for.
So let's give you some descriptions here.
So first thing that pops up, this outer rim that I talked about, that looks like a bigger raised topographic high, that's
that was that sea but I didn't know if that sea connected and it does look like it's completely, I'd say roughly encircling Ingenii and then a crater that's around the same size as Ingenii and then a few other smaller craters in that.
So it's definitely within that boundary.
um let's see looking a little bit closer with my camera um yeah these light and dark toned albedo um kind of basin color variations it's definitely uh definitely seeing what you were describing as the lunar swirls here um i will say there's no real pattern that's coming out to me um but i am seeing some great uh variations at this angle that weren't weren't as clear in the oblique view so
I'll make sure to get you guys some pictures and you can you can tell me what you what you see And yeah these there's some craters that are popping out as well.
I wasn't a little sure before but now I'm there's like one crater That's like smack dab in the center of Ingenii and I could see that really really clearly Oh, there's another one.
That's like pretty distinct to that's
I called Ingenii like the octopus.
It's like in the northern leg of that octopus, where that elongated island is separating out the kind of northern legs and the southern legs, if you're picking up what I'm saying.
And there's a, in between, you know, kind of following along that rough boundary circular of Ingenii, I'm seeing another pretty bright crater.
And honestly, actually, it looks like there's some
light toned albedo kind of color that's associated with that as well.
And it's really associated with the, I guess it's the eastern kind of fan of that crater.
So there's a little bit of association with that crater there.
So I'll make sure to get some good pics of that.
Yeah, I noted a kind of wrinkle that I saw and I'm seeing that too.
There's actually another one.
that i'm seeing as well that's kind of close to the terminator but like more on the southern end of of engine eye but around the same strike um as that more prominent one um that's on the western side so that's pretty uh that's a little bit more noticeable now um there's also seems to maybe be like some uh
Some like lineations maybe, some alignments of maybe craters or like maybe it's a little bit hard to say, but maybe they're like these lighter tone kind of lines and those lines are going maybe like, hold on, let me think about what direction these are going.
Kind of west striking kind of roughly.
Man, kind of hard to say here, but it's almost, it's roughly perpendicular or like 45 degrees in perpendicular from that wrinkle ridge that I was, that wrinkle I was talking about.
And that looks like it's crossing like the entirety of Ingenii.
So, and I, other than that though, there's not like a ton of pattern that I'm seeing in the mare, but super cool views.
And don't worry, science, I'm going to get you all kinds of pictures.
### Transcript 009
Alright, okay, I gotta take a moment to collect myself here.
Next target.
What do we have?
Okay, looking for a description of Terminator morphology, I think?
Let me get oriented.
Whoa!
Angela, you guys!
You're not gonna believe this!
What?
I really think I just saw a flash here!
No, you didn't!
No, it was a bright white flash, really tiny, but it was there.
Did you see it, Trevor?
Yeah, come on over here.
Well, I guess you missed it now, huh?
I wonder if any of the saw cameras caught that.
It was just like a bright white light over there in the unilluminated portion of the moon, really fleeting, but that was inspiring.
Where was it?
Well, so here I am in the port forward window, and I think it was kind of like off in the upper right quadrant of my view here.
Wow, that was incredible.
I hope you can pull this out of other vehicle data.
I mean, wow.
We got to get a seismometer on the moon ASAP.
I'll be honest, I was kind of skeptical we'd see one of these, but we sure got lucky.
What an experience.
I think I remember this was really high priority for the lunar science team, so I'm really glad we got this data point for them.
All right, mark the time that you've seen it.
Yeah.
### Transcript 010
Hello!