All right, this is Andre, and I'm doing my target six.
This is the Orientale annular ring.
As I'm looking at Orientale, I'm at the, oh, thank you.
Cool.
All right, so for Orientale, I have it identified.
It's got the outer ring and the inner ring.
There is a dark mare in the middle.
It's a dark gray overall.
There's some shades of lighter gray as well.
And then on the 7 and 8 o'clock position of Orientale, I see the annular ring.
I kind of describe it as a kiss mark or a lipstick mark.
is there's a darker mare on the inboard side of the annular ring at that 7-8 o'clock position and a lighter mare on the outboard side of the annular ring on the edge there.
Those are where the lips would be and I'm noticing that the annular ring is on the
edge of the Orientale Basin where it doesn't look like the outer ring is very prominent or high.
It looks kind of flat maybe because it's lower in elevation and on the opposite side at the two or three o'clock you can see Orientale's more prominent features, rugged terrain, but more on the southeast side it looks flat
And as I notice on the most outward piece of this ring for the bottom lip, I'll call it, on the kiss, it actually starts to, as you move outward, narrow into a triangle.
And then it looks like there's a small point that's somewhat separate of this bottom lip, almost like a bottom lip ring, I would say.
So that's an interesting feature.
where I never noticed that until looking at it in detail here, the extra dark patch that's outboard of the kiss itself.
And then in between the kiss and the dark mare of orientale, there's just a very light, very small crater or patch of albedo.
So I'm not sure if that's a crater that would be above the upper lip on the left side.
And then to the left of that, there's a little
white plain field as well.
And I think that's mostly it for this annular ring, but very interesting feature.
### Transcript 002
All right, coming up on the Dewar Crater region here.
I think I'll be, well, someone will be getting the opportunity to look at it again later.
But for right now, I see it's fairly close to the terminator edge.
I know I'm looking for a sort of albedo anomaly here and looking for some sort of like darker material that kind of comes out from the bottom of Dewar.
I think I see it.
It's more diffuse.
I don't really see, it's not like constrained or confined to a crater, but rather it appears to be darker material.
I don't see a ton of like vibrant colors, but it's definitely darker material that's kind of coming out like to the, almost like the southeast of Dewar Crater.
Let's see, size, it's probably like,
maybe one Dewar Crater diameter, long away from, again, the southeast edge of Dewar Crater.
And again, it's diffuse, even the sort of like the boundaries of the Albedo Anomaly itself are fairly diffuse.
It also kind of comes up like sort of to the east and the north a bit, again, diffused.
It almost looks like, I don't know, like someone
sprayed flour on the lunar surface or something and it sort of came out in an irregular pattern from the middle of Dewar crater.
Let's see what else I can tell you here.
Texture-wise, it doesn't appear to have an underlying consistent texture that's associated with the albedo anomaly.
I can't quite tell if there's any sort of surface texture associated with it, which makes me think there likely isn't.
It really just does appear to be a darker patch of lunar surface.
I hope that's helpful.
Looking forward to round two.
### Transcript 003
All right, moving on to Mare Inginii in Swirls, target number five.
I've got a good view of it out the window, getting a little bit of glare coming across a portion of the moon, but it got Mare Inginii pretty clear.
One of the things that immediately stands out to me is the in-bang relationships of some of the infill.
I expected it to be a little bit rougher, but man, it really looks smooth.
The boundary relationship between the embayment and the hills, especially to the three o'clock of that feature with the 12 o'clock being the moon as it's currently oriented in the window, are really stark.
So across the three o'clock, that boundary between the embayment of the two little ears that are kind of looking
towards that three o'clock direction and the hills, if I call it that, just adjacent to them is really stark and really prominent from this orientation.
I'm looking pretty close at any color relations or colors that stick out to me.
I'm not seeing anything immediate, but the albedo of those swirls is definitely standing out to me.
I can see light tone grays, but also a medium gray that are pretty stark against the background of that infilling material.
So I was seeing at least three tones of gray
no distinct colors outside that gray spectrum from my eye right now.
The illumination is perfect right now, especially to pick up those hills that I was talking about at the three o'clock position, and not seeing many textures again.
They're just really stark across the flat part of that infilling of Mare Inginii and the textures at the
nine o'clock are starting to be a little diffuse, but that could be an illumination condition.
I talked about those contacts again, it just really stick out to me at that three o'clock between the inbaying and the hills.
And yeah, really just an amazing feature, good illumination for this one.
And those swirls are pretty prominent as I talked about in that mid to light tone gray.
### Transcript 004
All right, I am going to do a recording of mare ingenii.
So I am looking at the crater.
It is partway down to the South Pole.
It's really easy to see the swirling that we have in mare ingenii here that looks like white streaks, curly, swirly streaks going across.
It seems like those swirls are most prevalent in the bottom half of that mare field.
As you go up a little higher, actually the whole, it almost looks like an eyeball.
And so if you see that darker part of the mare pond, it is darker in color.
It doesn't really have as many of those swirls.
But when you look around the outside, it's almost like where the iris of the eye would be.
You can see those swirls very similarly to the veins that you would see in your eye.
The texture along the right side of the crater, it's sort of a rubbly texture.
You can tell that there's just a lot of broken down material near where the crater rim would have been.
And the interesting thing is also just looking at this, I see a lot of that orange brown rusty color that matches some of the other mare infills that we see in South Pole Lake and Basin.
It's really cool to see these swirls in exactly where they're supposed to be and they really do look similar to what we are seeing in Muscoviense as well.
### Transcript 005
Hello, perfect.
This is Marie making a recording of Crookes Crater.
And so I am looking at the crater with my eyes just out the window.
I can see that it is partway between Jackson Crater and Apollo Basin.
The Crookes Crater, you can see that it has an injected blanket and a couple of rays that come out.
Um, and so that ejecta blanket is very white compared to the surrounding as it's very bright.
Um, and almost looks, um, see, it is a, it is very similar in size.
It almost looks like the majority of the race system could fit inside, um, Apollo basin.
Um, and so that ejecta blanket is about that size.
It's very bright.
It's very white.
I can't really see any shadows here based on our geometry because I'm essentially looking straight down on it.
I can't really see much structure to it, but you do see that white circle interior of the crater.
It does stand out as brighter from the ejecta blanket.
Um, it does look like it is the, um, it almost looks like a ejecta, an ejecta ray from Jackson actually goes over it.
Um, and it looks very much like a, um, it just passes right through.
So I think that it is underneath one of those rays that is coming down from Jackson crater.
Um,
It's really neat to see all these bright spots with all these rays right now in this lighting and really excited to move on to our next target.
### Transcript 006
This is Marie making observations with the camera.
I'm trying to find Bose Ballot.
Bose Ballot.
Nope.
Bose and Bhabha.
Crater right now.
Craters.
I know that they're below Apollo Basin, but it's actually, at this lighting, it's really hard to pull them out because of the morphology is making it
more difficult to find exactly where the craters are.
And so what I'm doing instead is I'm just going to take a bunch of pictures of this bottom rim below Apollo Basin at the highest resolution that I can and try hopefully that you'll be able to see.
So I'm sure that I will have captured it.
might not be in the middle of the frame.
Yeah, without that defining morphology, it's actually pretty difficult to see, but I can still see a lot of that rusty brown color down here, and so the rims of the craters aren't as well pronounced, and so it's definitely a more difficult one to find, but hopefully the pictures help.
### Transcript 007
All right, looking forward to this.
I've got I think one more target here before Earthset and I can see Earth coming up on the on the side of the moon here.
But before we get there.
Really want to take the opportunity to describe this beautiful whole moon view I'm getting Wow, okay, where to even start?
We've got quite a variation of Albedo as the earth is approaching the sort of the limb of the moon and
Wow, it looks, you know, much brighter white.
You see, you know, crater array systems from several craters extending across the surface, and they really pop in this illumination profile.
You know, to the south, I got a great view here of the South Pole-Aitken Basin, starting to see that, you know, darker, grayer material in that beautiful SPA really pop out, and inside of it is
a series of other craters, some of which have dark smooth interiors and some of which have even darker patches that look like some of the mare patches.
There's one crater there that actually has patches of mare, several discrete patches of mare, whereas a few of the other craters within SPA have maybe more traditional, looks like mare infill there.
I'll tell you, it really is a beautiful view here.
I'm starting to see, I think, Muscovians, which I know is a really exciting science target.
Jackson Crater pops in the middle where you see a sharp crater rim for Jackson.
And the rays almost look like a star.
I see kind of like five rays coming out.
The ray to the north.
Is fainter- the other four rays- really are coming out- kind of like in an even spread and even spacing radially out from the center of.
Of Jackson crater there-
Wow yeah I mean of course toward the Terminator we're starting to see some more distinct shadowing there and again like that morphology really pops on the west side whereas on the east side I'm able to pick up that really bright albedo color.
And it's just really a spectacular view of these different albedo provinces that I see moving from east to west.
I'm starting to see Earth get a lot closer to the limb of the moon here, so I know I've got to transition to Earthset.
Wowee, this is a great view and really fortunate to be able to see it here.
Last thing I'll say is I think I missed the textures.
On the east side, the texture really is starting to get pretty, you know, of course washed out due to the illumination conditions there, so it looks pretty smooth to my eye, but wow does that texture start to pop as you're looking at the Terminator.
It's a beautiful view here, and as we're getting ready to see Earthset, I just want to say, you know, thanks and see you on the other side.
### Transcript 008
All right, this is our target number nine.
We're describing the moon in general.
And as I'll do this, I'm going to start big and then go from north to south and left to right.
So overall, on this side of the moon, I see a combination of grays and whites with a few mares in the south
east and a few towards the south-southwest.
That south-east is Orientale and south-southwest is Apollo Basin.
We still have a few mares to the north-east over there on the edge of the moon.
Now as I go from north to south and left to right, I'm seeing in the
top left quadrant there, medium gray type of fields with spots of white, very distinct blotches.
They could be craters, they could be upturned regolith.
And as I'm going from left to right in the north side, I'm seeing some cratering that is horizontal.
And there's a few white spots towards the north-north side, two of them that look like a pair in a vertical linear fashion.
And then as I go to the right, I'm seeing more white spots that are circular in nature, almost look like a pepperoni pizza with white pepperonis on a gray piece of cheese.
And now I'm finally getting to the dark mares on the edge on the east side or right side of my view.
And those are kind of like algae looking dark mares.
very thin along the eastern side and the northeast quadrant.
Coming back to the left, I'm glossing over, it looks like Oum crater with all of its rays, and then going to the middle point of the north side, there is more dark gray regolith versus white patches.
Then going over to Oum, I'm seeing
the star pattern rays, and then the features of the craters start to become more prominent as I'm looking right where Jackson is and then to the west side.
It looks very more distinct from an albedo perspective and feature perspective.
Now along the equatorial line, I see those craters on the left side, and they are more distinct but smaller in the equator.
And then as I go towards the middle, there's a large crater directly in front of us, normal to our view, that has an interesting star pattern, four points.
It's making an X that's in a diagonal form.
And then over to the right of that, there's a big white blotch in between Oum and Orientale.
That's a very interesting feature.
And then going to the southern hemisphere,
Orientale has a bunch of bright splotches to its 10 o'clock position and sweeping in the northwest quadrant of Orientale and then going back to the center in the mid latitudes of the south hemisphere.
There's not many features that I could tell probably because of my viewing angle as far as terrain but lots of albedo patches that are from the northwest down to the southeast and that kind of hovers right on the northeast side of
Apollo Basin.
And then as I get to Apollo Basin, there's a lot more dark gray albedo to the southwest.
And then there's more cratering that is seen because of the viewing angle to the southwest hemisphere that kind of blends into the Terminator.
### Transcript 009
Alright, moving on to target number 15.
We're going to Jackson.
So I'm looking at Jackson now.
I've certainly been able to locate it given some of the surrounding landmarks to focus in on it.
If I do look down at my LTP, I tend to
lose exactly where it's at, so it takes some relocating every time I look back out.
So I'm gonna concentrate on just describing Jackson and then I'll take a look and make sure I didn't miss anything in the actions or the cue card.
So just looking at Jackson for its shape and size, super circular,
crater.
I do pick up in this illumination condition some of the central peak that looks at the bottom of Jackson and get a lot of the terracing, particularly to the nine o'clock position in our current orientation of the window with 12 o'clock being up the lunar north.
Now also mention that
I see some distinct rays from Jackson.
I think that was one of the actions out of the LTP.
I see distinct rays at the four o'clock and the 10 o'clock that extend about five to six Jackson diameters away from Jackson itself.
And those kind of peter out or I lose that distinct ray colorization when it impacts or when it gets into some other impacts that are further extent, but also have some, some rays associated with them.
But Jackson for sure is, has some distinct rays as my eyes have become adapted to the lighting environment.
There also maybe is a subtle ray that goes down to the seven o'clock.
It's less prominent, but definitely see some of those light tone rays coming from Jackson.
Now they're light tone, but they're not in this illumination condition any lighter than the bottom of Jackson.
So if I was to describe the three color tones that I just outlined there, the lightest is the
the bottom of Jackson and then the light rays are the next color tone and then there's kind of the gray background that is the surrounding terrain.
And so I just wanted to enumerate that tonal difference in three distinct broad categories.
Um, let me take a look at the LTP again here real quick.
So that covers the color, some of those albedos, um, and that tonal difference that I was talking about and texture.
Yeah, the biggest texture thing that sticks out with Jackson to me, um, is the terracing and that central peak.
Um, don't see any specific texture in those rays I described, but the terracing is pretty, um,
dramatic, even though it's a small crater, it stands out because of that terracing.
And I think that covers it for the LTP.
Let me take one last look.
Yeah, the relationship with the rays across the surface are, as I described, pretty prominent within two or three crater diameters of Jackson and then start to fall off as you get to those five or six crater diameters away.
That's it with Jackson.
Moving on to the next one.
### Transcript 010
Okay, this is Christina Cook.
I'm doing an observation for site 19 Jackson Crater.
Visually tracing the rays from the center of the crater, I'm gonna describe how they change as they move away.
I think a really neat thing about Jackson Crater is they are very predominant rays, and they all kind of peter out at about the same radius from the center of Jackson Crater, which makes it almost look like a starfish.
that distance from the center of the crater is probably about six crater diameters away, five to six crater diameters away.
One ray that extends a little farther than that is the one that goes down to what I think is Korolyov
crater or basin and a high albedo little spot that's above it, that ray is a little longer than the others.
It almost also appears as if two rays that go out the top of Jackson Crater a little bit towards the northeast almost crisscross.
Difficult to say whether that's albedo or if that's terrain that makes it look like it, but
there is kind of an area on the northeast and triangular shaped area of Jackson that kind of is almost like a continuous ray blob, if you will.
Like I said, they all kind of peter out after that or turn very, very light and are more difficult to trace after that.
And I think that's all I'm going to talk about for Jackson.
### Transcript 011
Christina here, working through my targeting.
Next up is number 16, Oppenheimer.
I am looking through the camera at the moment, and so I can get pretty close, zoomed in.
Oppenheimer and Apollo Basin right next to each other.
I'll say the first thing that stands out to me
are the color tones.
Oppenheimer has kind of this reddish hue to it, with its mare being more like almost like a dark purple.
And the mares that are really standing out to me are the kind of three
to the left side of the crater.
And then as you go more towards Apollo Basin, the color tone changes pretty significantly because you have this big ray, this light-toned ray that's coming from Crooks that is just almost cutting
Oppenheimer in half.
It's going kind of close to straight up and down through the crater and proceeds double the length, at least, past the crater as well.
And in that ray, there's actually two tones of this kind of lighter hue that's also about equal
on so i'll say that if you kind of split that ray in half vertically on the left side of it has this more of a maybe we'll call it like a tan like a a tanner browner light toned color and then on the right side of it closer to apollo basin it's definitely more of a
a lighter tan, I'll say, but there's a little bit of tonal difference with the lighter color closer towards Apollo Basin.
And then as you move more towards Apollo Basin, you have a reddish tone, but it's a little bit lighter than what I'm seeing in Oppenheimer.
And then the Mare also, instead of like the dark purples, if you call it like a little bit of darker purple in the Mare,
In Oppenheimer, in Apollo, it's more of like a bluer in the mare.
And then go into texture.
Let's see, Oppenheimer is a little bit, maybe I'd call it rougher than Apollo overall.
And I'm definitely seeing these kind of finer structures that are at the base, at the kind of basin of Oppenheimer.
And I can even see them in my LTP, but yeah, they're not present in Apollo either.
So I just see these kind of linear fractures and structures in Oppenheimer at the, at its basin.
Overall though, these kind of the margins of the mare, I would say, are more diffuse in Oppenheimer than Apollo.
Like there are some margins, like I said, those three kind of primary mare are what stands out.
And what I mean by that,
are there's the very circular, so if you're talking about Oppenheimer on the kind of left side of it, there's a really circular mare which has like two
it kind of horizontal notches to it.
And then below that, a little to the left, you have a little bit of a smaller splotch.
And then a little bit below that, a little bit more to the right, there's kind of a dark, diffuse mare patch.
Whereas Apollo, it's very clear that there are, instead of, like I said, the margins are more diffuse in Oppenheimer than they are in Apollo.
The Apollo mare is very clear,
lineation and differentiation between the light and the dark of the mare and the light-toned surrounding area.
### Transcript 012
Christina here.
Moving on to my next target, which is Apollo Basin, target number 17.
I did a lot of descriptions on Apollo Basin when I compared it to Oppenheimer for target 16, but I'm going to continue on focusing on Apollo Basin.
So the first thing I'll note is the color tones.
And there doesn't seem to be a significant color tone difference in
The kind of inner ring of the basin and the exterior ring of the basin They seem to be around the same color tone, which is in the mare this dark blue Very dark kind of black blue color and then everything else which has a slight kind of reddish gray
tone to it.
With the exception of maybe like three pretty bright craters that stand out, the one that stands out the most is kind of the northeast of the mare that's inside of the inner basin.
and it stands out because it has rays that are maybe like four rays that are clearly cutting across that mare, that irregular shaped mare, and it seems like those rays are
you know, they're very clear because they have a contrast in the dark mares because they're such light tone.
And then they continue on, but the end of it is a little bit diffuse.
I know I can't see those rays on the other side of that inner ring.
So they seem to be constrained in some way to the inner ring.
And their direction is kind of north,
northwest, cutting diagonally down and across.
And then the other two brighter craters that stand out are outside of that inner basin and slightly to the east of the dark mare patch that's
on the left side of the basin.
If you're looking at it like a face, it's the left eye of that mare patch.
It's a little bit to the right of it.
And then if you're looking at the smile, right above, north of the smile, that's the other kind of bright crater.
So there's that kind of three bright craters that stand out.
And I've kind of tried to describe them in association with the mare, but hopefully that comes through in the pictures.
In general, in terms of the texture, Apollo Basin seems a lot smoother, especially in the kind of mare regions.
Definitely seems like they're a little bit more of a flow or a mantled type of smooth look versus Oppenheimer, which has a little bit more ruggedness to it.
And like I mentioned, there's more contrast and sharpness in the boundaries of those dark patches in Apollo Basin than Oppenheimer.
And the last thing I'll say is it does seem like Oppenheimer is
kind of physically on top of Apollo Basin, like it's cutting into it, it's cutting off a little bit of the margin, and then there's these rays that are cutting straight through from a crater above.
### Transcript 013
All right, moving on to target 20, the Poincaré Crater region.
I've been staring at this one for a little bit now before I started this recording, and I'm looking for that stratigraphic relationship that's called out for this basin.
I totally understand that it's within SPA, or at least in a Western region of SPA, but I'm trying to look for this resurface volcanism
And it's just not standing out to me.
Maybe it's the illumination condition on this one.
Maybe it's because of that being near the Terminator, but I'm not picking up on the things, the actions that are outlined in the LTP.
Color's pretty diffuse across this one, not picking up any kind of color differentiation that, at least from my eyes and at this, you know, without a,
optical device to get any closer in on it.
Wrinkle ridges, not seeing any.
The basin rings, I can't see that it's a basin, but I kind of have to squint to see that in that area.
And the mari relationships, just because it's all tonal, about the same down there in this illumination conditions.
Not, not
not anything's really standing out to me.
So sorry, this one might be a dud for you guys, but really not seeing anything standing out in that area that gets me at the stratigraphic relationship or the volcanic activity in this area.
Sorry about that one, but moving on to the next one.
### Transcript 014
Jeremy here doing my next observation, which is Target 24, South Pole Aitken Basin.
Reid has the camera right now, so I'm just using my eyes, looking at this pretty big region, which is most of the south, you know, south side of the moon, except what's kind of cut off by the Terminator on my west.
The first thing I'll note is the color.
The thing that stands out the most with the color is the light-toned ray that's coming straight kind of through the margin of Apollo Basin and Oppenheimer.
It continues all the way down.
I can't necessarily say I see the end of it.
This keeps continuing down through the moon.
Maybe it kind of goes, it follows a linear trajectory and then maybe has one fork in it that's forking towards the west.
But that light tone is pretty clear.
The dark mare patches are also, in contrast, stand out.
Apollo Basin, dark blue mare, and then that's a similar kind of tone in mare to maybe a little bit of Leibniz crater.
And then looking more towards the Terminator, maybe a little bit also in some of the swirls of Injani have a little bit of that dark blue as well.
and then things are a little bit more lost from color towards the terminator.
And then color-wise, again, the redder tones in Apollo Basin are standing out.
And then also there's some like reddish tones in Mare Anjanai too.
It's got that right above the margin on the north side.
It almost seems like a little bit of like a red
I don't want to say glow, but a little bit of a diffuse red color that emanates out from the north of Injani, which is really pretty spectacular.
And it's a little bit in the swirls as well, that red tone.
Reddish, orangish, muted colors.
Not very bright, but muted.
In terms of structures, I can roughly see the
You're going to call the boundary of South Pohegan Basin at the at the northern side.
And then some of these right at the terminator that roughness pops out.
I'm not entirely sure what crater.
Sorry, what ridges is standing out to me right at that terminator, but it's to the east of engine.
I definitely looks like it's more, uh, an elongated ridge and that's, that's pretty clear.
Um, it's really cool.
All that lighting makes that topography stand out.
### Transcript 015
Alright, my second time looking at Mare Inginii and swirls.
Hopefully my crew members over there are taking some good pictures of this photometric effect.
I'm seeing a little bit, again, this is target 28, Mari Injani's a little bit smaller than our Apollo base, and that's how I index off of Apollo base, and then just kind of move to the left in the current orientation.
That's how I pick that up.
The boundary of Mari Injani's may be a little bit more distinct in this illumination condition, so I'm glad I trained my eyes back on this a second time.
I am still not seeing any kind of like hue or like red or yellows or any kind of color difference like that.
I'm just mostly seeing some gray tonal difference so the albedo changes.
between those three distinct albedos that I talked about before, kind of a light tone swirl, medium tone swirl, and then all set across the darker backdrop of the Mare Inginii region.
The slope now has changed a little bit from
What I think I described earlier, the slopes and the structure that really stands out to me is now mostly at the six to nine o'clock.
I'm starting to pick up a lot of different features that I didn't see the first time I looked at Mari Injani and really starting to appreciate for how much that Terminator coming closer and the
The photometric effect is making the observation different, but hasn't made the color any different, if that makes sense.
So the colors are about the same.
I'm just getting more textural differences, particularly across the southern portion of that crater.
The embayment that I described before, especially at the three o'clock into the hills at the three o'clock with those kind of like bunny ears or the Mickey Mouse ears that are headed towards the three o'clock.
Not as sharp as when I first observed them.
It was an earlier target.
I forget which number.
But I'm glad I trained my eyes back on this one and hopefully gave you guys some good observations.
But those photos are really going to be key to hopefully zoom in and determine any kind of other photometric effect that might be going on.
So thanks for turning me on to this one a second time and hopefully that observations helped.
### Transcript 016
Okay, here I am at window two and I think the next target on my list here is Buys-Ballott and I remember this one from training and I'll be honest, I'm pretty glad I get the chance to observe it because of
how unique it is.
It does have that kind of arrowhead shape where the point of the arrow is pointing to the south.
It has a long linear ridge in the middle that I would have believed is a central peak but it's so linear and stretched out it looks like it's rising above a relatively smooth terrain here.
Speaking of that smooth terrain, sort of the like upper northern end of the bottom of the crater looks pretty smooth.
It's got like some younger fresher craters that look like they've formed in the smooth mare.
They're dark
smooth patch.
But it that that sort of northern part is really, you know, quite smooth.
And then as you move to the south toward, you know, the other end of that linear ridge in the middle of the crater, it looks like rougher terrain.
And it almost looks like that rougher terrain ends in sort of like an arc.
that starts in the west, goes slightly up to the north, then goes back down to the east.
There's also another little, like, arc, almost like a slump or something on the east side of the crater.
I would say the east side of the crater looks, I think, like a shallower slope, whereas the west side is a steeper slope.
really interesting diversity in this crater from the sort of lumpy, hummocky texture to the south and the smooth texture to the north.
As for like color and albedo, I'd say the fresher or the smoother stuff is grayer, much grayer than the southern edge, which is like a lighter gray tone.
So I definitely see a kind of a distinct color difference there Looks like you guys want me to draw some comparisons about Lacus luxuriate to the south Man, that thing is is hard to kind of see and pick out.
It's much less Topographically notable than Buys-Ballott But really interesting feature here and
making sure I'm not missing any of your requests.
Yeah, the texture I think I covered.
We got the steep slope to the west, the shallower slope to the east that really has that hummocky slump-like terrain.
And again, rougher to the south.
And I mean, I still see some tiny fresher craters there in the southern rougher patch.
but much different than the sort of other smooth material in Lacus Luxuriae.
Really interesting crater and I'm excited to see what you guys make of it.
### Transcript 017
Okay, back at Dewar Crater.
I'm fortunate to get a chance to look at this twice.
I know these different illumination conditions that I'm experiencing now might bring out some different information about morphology and about
composition, as I recall.
So let me take a look here.
Again, we have Dewar Crater here.
And again, the albedo anomaly that I think I'm looking for here comes out to the south, to the east, and actually maybe in this viewing geometry, maybe more to the north than I had initially thought.
I'm still not seeing, you know, a ton jump out at me in terms of morphology of this albedo anomaly.
Dewar Crater has a pretty sharp and defined rim from what I
As you can see here, it looks like sort of the western edge of Dewar Crater.
let's see, a bit, um, maybe more like slumped than the, than the right side, than the east side of, of Dewar crater.
Um, the mid, but it is a pretty, um, sharp and beautiful crater boundary there.
Um, again, I'm seeing the albedo anomaly over top of it, some smaller craters, um, that are significantly smaller than Dewar all the way down to almost the resolution that I can see with my naked eye here.
seem to be on top of the albedo anomaly, just because they do appear to be sort of like brighter and don't seem to have that darker, that darker colored material on top of the brighter craters.
One of the younger craters at about three o'clock from Dewar sticks out particularly to my eye as being lighter in albedo than what it's sitting on, which is that darker material I described earlier.
Like I said earlier, I don't really see any morphology or texture that underlies the dark albedo material, but I do definitely see what you guys are directing me to look at, which is some really interesting material that, again, kind of looks like somebody threw a powder onto a surface, and it sort of originates from about halfway through Dewar Crater itself.
Thanks, and I'll move on to the next target.
### Transcript 018
Alright, this is Maria.
I'm gonna again talk through the Terminator because I did it once already but completely missed it the last time so I guess I'll just take a new mosaic.
So I'm gonna just take a higher resolution one.
I did just finish a mosaic before but I will do another one because I want to talk through the recording.
So, I am snaking my way up.
Oh, there's Mare Injunai.
I can really see that in the swirls there.
I'm working my way up from there, and then I'm going to snake over closer to the Terminator.
Right now, the Terminator is not in my view, but I'll get over there.
It's really interesting to see the depressions, the difference in the amount of depression that you see in these critters.
as I work my way up here.
I'm up near the North Pole now.
I'm gonna snake over a little bit more to the left.
Sounds like they're working on the toilet behind me, but glad they can get that checked out.
Now I'm up in Muscoviense.
I'm working my way back down.
There's that little tiny mare-filled crater not too far below it.
Now I'm working my way back down.
Making sure that I have- oh, now I'm back at Jules Verne with those scarps.
Back over to the left.
And now I have the Terminator in view.
There I am at that.
make sure that I get and now the moon is the earth is back in that view also absolutely incredible view here
### Transcript 019
This is Marie calling from the moon.
I was just looking out the...
out the window and I think I saw an impact flash.
I can't forget the name of it because I
don't not looking at my lunar targeting plan right now but it was just off of there over the side of the Terminator it was just really quick it lasts about a second not even but it did have like sort of a yellowish whitish hue it just came in really quickly right during the Jules Verne observation
And that's it.
Hope you guys can, you know, use our LRO friends to help us find out if we can see our brand new impact crater.