All right, this is our target number nine.
We're describing the moon in general.
And as I'll do this, I'm going to start big and then go from north to south and left to right.
So overall, on this side of the moon, I see a combination of grays and whites with a few mares in the south
east and a few towards the south-southwest.
That south-east is Orientale and south-southwest is Apollo Basin.
We still have a few mares to the north-east over there on the edge of the moon.
Now as I go from north to south and left to right, I'm seeing in the
top left quadrant there, medium gray type of fields with spots of white, very distinct blotches.
They could be craters, they could be upturned regolith.
And as I'm going from left to right in the north side, I'm seeing some cratering that is horizontal.
And there's a few white spots towards the north-north side, two of them that look like a pair in a vertical linear fashion.
And then as I go to the right, I'm seeing more white spots that are circular in nature, almost look like a pepperoni pizza with white pepperonis on a gray piece of cheese.
And now I'm finally getting to the dark mares on the edge on the east side or right side of my view.
And those are kind of like algae looking dark mares.
very thin along the eastern side and the northeast quadrant.
Coming back to the left, I'm glossing over, it looks like Oum crater with all of its rays, and then going to the middle point of the north side, there is more dark gray regolith versus white patches.
Then going over to Oum, I'm seeing
the star pattern rays, and then the features of the craters start to become more prominent as I'm looking right where Jackson is and then to the west side.
It looks very more distinct from an albedo perspective and feature perspective.
Now along the equatorial line, I see those craters on the left side, and they are more distinct but smaller in the equator.
And then as I go towards the middle, there's a large crater directly in front of us, normal to our view, that has an interesting star pattern, four points.
It's making an X that's in a diagonal form.
And then over to the right of that, there's a big white blotch in between Oum and Orientale.
That's a very interesting feature.
And then going to the southern hemisphere,
Orientale has a bunch of bright splotches to its 10 o'clock position and sweeping in the northwest quadrant of Orientale and then going back to the center in the mid latitudes of the south hemisphere.
There's not many features that I could tell probably because of my viewing angle as far as terrain but lots of albedo patches that are from the northwest down to the southeast and that kind of hovers right on the northeast side of
Apollo Basin.
And then as I get to Apollo Basin, there's a lot more dark gray albedo to the southwest.
And then there's more cratering that is seen because of the viewing angle to the southwest hemisphere that kind of blends into the Terminator.