Alright, this is Andre Douglas.
I'm at Target 7 here.
We're looking at Oum.
Oum is to the northwest of Orientale right now.
It is a fairly big crater and it has a bunch of streaks that radiate outward.
I would say mostly from the 2 o'clock to the 7 o'clock position to the southeast and then more from the 11 o'clock back to the 7 o'clock counterclockwise.
from the northwest to the southwest, almost like a butterfly pattern.
Over in the 11 o'clock to 2 o'clock, there's not really many rays.
There's a dark field of regolith out there that is somewhat, I would say, medium gray.
And as we're approaching the crater from the outside, I see a ring of dark gray terrain that is really highlighting the rim of the crater.
And it comes in and is slightly sharp,
as we go up and over the crater, and then walking in down towards the center, it goes to a brighter white with some albedo there, then another light ring of gray, and then a white center.
So it kind of has a bullseye effect.
And then in the center area, that overall whiteness albedo is not as white as another patch that is about five diameters to the
I would say 7 o'clock position or southwest position from OM.
There's another white albedo patch that doesn't look like a crater, but just a patch.
But inside OM is much grayer than that, but still it's a light gray.
So it's not necessarily the freshest impact there.
And I would say there's more of a whiter plane on the south side of OM, and then again, a darker gray on the north side of OM.
And that's all I have for that.