Okay All right, so just to make sure I'm on the right target it's the huge crater with lots of rays almost in a starship shape And it's got a it's a high albedo and
And I'm sort of in the north center field of view.
And I'm just doing target, not the whole moon, right?
And is that how you worked it, how you, one of you held the PCD?
No, you'd be going off of your own PCD.
Okay.
I mean, we can, I think if we're showing each other something, but I think the assumption is we're both initially orienting ourselves with this, and then we kind of wrap together if there's any question or I'm going to show you something I noticed, make sure you're going to exhibit it.
Oh, there's the arthritis.
All right, so I'm gonna talk into my microphone a little bit here too.
I'm observing the earth rise.
It took me a while to get the camera sorted, but now it's going.
Christina's working on Jackson Crater, I think still, but I am just trying to capture the earth rise.
So I see a half earth.
I can see a very white south pole of the earth.
And I can see a landmass sort of in the middle.
And you could turn your pass through off too.
But you don't want to talk.
Okay, I'm there as well
mhm
Hey, Dre, can you hit target 20 on that thing for me?
That's what I do.
at least one newer crater on it that's very well defined and it might be the darkest actual region.
So do you want to just point at what you think you were filming there?
Yeah, so I see Aiken, right?
And then what I did have a little trouble coming up from Aiken and finding the things in between Aiken and there on that picture.
Like I see a really dark deep crater right above Aiken on there.
It doesn't show up at all on this.
I guess it's that, yeah.
I think we're quite a ways further up, actually.
Oh, I see the two.
Go up, up, up, up.
Up, up, up, up, up, that dark one there.
And you see the two to the right of it?
Yeah, I think they're identifiable right here.
No, these overlap, actually.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking, yeah.
Yeah, I think I was a little low initially Yeah, okay anyway all good learning Yeah
Yeah, I felt like I started photographing Earthrise when it happened, so.
No, you had to.
We're doing Earthrise site 21.
The exosphere just prior to Earthrise.
Oh.
So that's good to know.
Seeing Earth come out of the darkness.
Oops, sorry.
The balloons really stand out.
They're almost like a... Oh, I can't see.
I wasn't doing that.
I was trying to set up a five-minute timer.
Okay.
You know, because approximately,
It doesn't seem like the right thing to do.
Okay.
I have an idea on this because I think the social media and NatGeo people are perfect to just answer what they're seeing and leave the science people alone.
We really don't think we'll see out the other two windows?
Is that true?
I think you may see it out of that one.
I don't know that you're going to see it out of the side ones.
Really?
Oh, interesting.
Okay.