No, you're fine.
No, no, you're okay.
Hi folks.
Do you want to sit?
I can hand it to you then.
You have control.
Okay, so I'm picking up... I think he did it already.
I'm picking up on 24, the Terminator.
So, just having a look here.
I want to describe the way the Terminator highlights the moon's craters and other features in the moon.
So, looking along the crater of the big photo.
I guess if I start in the, I'm gonna, just one sec here.
All right, so I see the most identifiable feature to me near the terminator is the Aiken crater just south of the equator, and it's fully lit in the current
phase of the moon and on the west side of Aitken Crater it's completely black from the the rim of the west side of the Aitken Crater.
But then as soon as you move north from there I can see quite a bit further west probably one or two hundred kilometers further west I can see some high points sticking out to the northwest of Aitken Crater.
And then as I come up further, I notice there is a very dark crater where the rim is highlighted from the 10 o'clock position down to the 6.30 position, but the western edge of that rim is not visible.
And then coming up from there, I start to move further east, following some highlands that are lined up with the west edge of Aiken Crater.
and they're the last part that's visible.
And then just to the north of that is a crater where I can see from 7 to 11 and then I'm missing a gap until noon and then I can see from noon to five o'clock.
And then to the north of that there's a very
well-illuminated crater where I can see the entire west wall down into the inside of the crater.
It looks like there's a central peak in that one that's sticking up.
It's a bright spot in the middle of the dark shadow of that crater.
and coming north from there I see a very kind of somewhat uniform altitude terrain for probably an eighth of the moon.
The terminator it's obviously not flat but it doesn't have any doesn't seem to have any huge peaks or huge valleys in that area.
And then there's a region with just a ton of craters right around the
Terminator, so we're about a quarter of the way down from the top of the moon on the Terminator.
I got a lot of small craters with lots of details of their rims all together.
And then going north of that gets into sort of an undulating area with not much to point out until you get to the very large crater that's right on the Terminator line near the north pole of the moon with a few small craters north of it.
And then down from Aiken Crater, we get some significant mountainous area type terrain.
I've got some very sharp, bright peaks to the southwest of Aiken Crater, and then a big valley, and then another peak to the south.
And then I can see, the last thing I can see below that, but above, I guess this is the, I don't know what the name of that crater is actually.
interesting observations though, but just to let you know that the next two are impact clashes on the dark side and deep space, so I think you've got more to determine.
All right, so the next thing is that Mare Swirls, Igni and Swirls area, which is very visible.
I can see the full large crater that all the smaller impact areas are inside of, and then down into the Schrodinger Basin.