Christina cook observing site 3 Mari in Guinea and swirls This site is Fairly difficult to identify because it is right on the Terminator.
Of course that gives us some good observing options and in order to make sure that I have it I
I am going to locate it relative to Apollo and Aitken.
It is kind of like on the 90 degree between Apollo and Aitken if you were to draw a square encompassing them.
It is direct due west of Apollo and due south of Aitken, which I can identify on here.
So the crater shape is kind of appears almost hard to tell but I would I would describe it as a little bit trapezoidal but also kind of lily paddish with areas inside the crater that have almost little walls or terrain as well defining it.
The colors are difficult to discern, but I don't make out a lot of the swirling that is more easy to see when it is lit.
In fact, from this view, it's pretty difficult to see any brighter patterns.
I'm seeing a lot of dark and shadow.
But what I can see is that there is terrain almost tracing out, kind of tiling the crater, if you will, in almost hexagon type things that I can imagine are each about one-fifth the size of the crater.
Kind of like making biscuits in a small cast iron skillet.
In terms of color, I would say that the darkness doesn't really have as much of a discernible hue, definitely not any kind of tan or pink, just pretty dark without hue.
And I think that's all I can offer on this one.