Christina Cook annotating site 5, Sundman 5 crater.
We weren't able to 100% identify exactly this crater, but it does say the line of craters, so I'll describe the line of craters that is in this area near the limb.
Nothing distinctive on the limb itself, no views of the exosphere.
The craters themselves appear to be pretty new, just because they're very round.
They all are some of the smallest visible craters on the surface of the moon.
From the view looking at the moon with my eyes, I am not able to discern any one crater being deeper, more distinctive, or more shadowed than the others, as is evident on the photo in the lunar targeting plan.
So that's one thing to note.
I do see a lot of distinctive dots in this area that are little dots of high albedo areas and what is otherwise a medium gray tones in an area that doesn't have a lot of mare, but also to the west of the big mare sort of field.
I'm also not able to make out a very distinctive line of craters in this particular area.
There are some lines of craters that all sort of follow lines of radiation out from ohm.
This one would be, if it were one of those at about the four o'clock position, I can see several other lines of craters that do appear like they're scattered from ohm.
Most of those lines of craters are equidistant apart and of the same albedo, each one of them in the same size.
If this one is from that line just
per the picture, it would be distinctive because of its clearer shape and depth.
But again, I'm not able to see that on the moon itself.
I don't see any differences in color in this area.
There could be a slight basin shape that is kind of inside the isosceles triangle of lighter areas here.
A circle that is about the height of the isosceles triangle, a little shorter, with its upper left quadrant being defined by a little dark
spot that appears to be Mario and not Shadow.
That's all I'm going to say about that.