Christina Cook recording the full moon albedo and full moon observations site 23.
So in this view of the moon it is almost exactly a half moon with the eastern half lit.
The prominent features are ohm
crater and I would say two other high albedo areas south of Oum, one of which is close to equatorial and the other which is a few degrees latitude south of equatorial and more diffuse.
Overall the darker regions of the moon are in the north and south with several more darker mare patches that are of
diameter... I wish I had a diameter here.
Let's see if I can get one.
Maybe 50 to 100 kilometers in the southern region at about the 60-ish latitude area.
Kind of like, almost looking like little, like scarrings, darker mare scarrings down there, whereas the northern hemisphere doesn't really have those marks in that same way.
The higher albedo regions are all very centered in the east along kind of that eastern horizon and limb.
Those are in addition to the three prominent high albedo spots that I talked about earlier.
So in general it goes from a low albedo at the terminator which
to higher albedo on the east, and that isn't just because of the shattering of the Terminator.
Even when we're out of those high shadows of the Terminator, you see some of that same pattern.
The southern hemisphere, you can really make out the overall darkness of the South Pole-Aitken Basin.
There really aren't any high albedo areas in that southern area at all.