All right, this is Andre, and I'm doing my target six.
This is the Oriental annular ring.
As I'm looking at Oriental, I'm at the, oh, thank you.
Cool.
All right, so for Oriental, I have it identified.
It's got the outer ring and the inner ring.
There is a dark mare in the middle.
It's a dark gray overall.
There's some shades of lighter gray as well.
And then on the 7 and 8 o'clock position of Orientale, I see the annular ring.
I kind of describe it as a kiss mark or a lipstick mark.
is there's a darker mare on the inboard side of the annular ring at that 7-8 o'clock position and a lighter mare on the outboard side of the annular ring on the edge there.
Those are where the lips would be and I'm noticing that the annular ring is on the
edge of the Orientale Basin where it doesn't look like the outer ring is very prominent or high.
It looks kind of flat maybe because it's lower in elevation and on the opposite side at the two or three o'clock you can see Orientale's more prominent features, rugged terrain, but more on the southeast side it looks flat
And as I notice on the most outward piece of this ring for the bottom lip, I'll call it, on the kiss, it actually starts to, as you move outward, narrow into a triangle.
And then it looks like there's a small point that's somewhat separate of this bottom lip, almost like a bottom lip ring, I would say.
So that's an interesting feature.
where I never noticed that until looking at it in detail here, the extra dark patch that's outboard of the kiss itself.
And then in between the kiss and the dark mare of orientale, there's just a very light, very small crater or patch of albedo.
So I'm not sure if that's a crater that would be above the upper lip on the left side.
And then to the left of that, there's a little
white plain field as well.
And I think that's mostly it for this annular ring, but very interesting feature.
###Douglas Full Moon Mosaic
All right, this is our target number nine.
We're describing the moon in general.
And as I'll do this, I'm going to start big and then go from north to south and left to right.
So overall, on this side of the moon, I see a combination of grays and whites with a few mares in the south
east and a few towards the south-southwest.
That south-east is Orientale and south-southwest is Apollo Basin.
We still have a few mares to the north-east over there on the edge of the moon.
Now as I go from north to south and left to right, I'm seeing in the
top left quadrant there, medium gray type of fields with spots of white, very distinct blotches.
They could be craters, they could be upturned regolith.
And as I'm going from left to right in the north side, I'm seeing some cratering that is horizontal.
And there's a few white spots towards the north-north side, two of them that look like a pair in a vertical linear fashion.
And then as I go to the right, I'm seeing more white spots that are circular in nature, almost look like a pepperoni pizza with white pepperonis on a gray piece of cheese.
And now I'm finally getting to the dark mares on the edge on the east side or right side of my view.
And those are kind of like algae looking dark mares.
very thin along the eastern side and the northeast quadrant.
Coming back to the left, I'm glossing over, it looks like Oum crater with all of its rays, and then going to the middle point of the north side, there is more dark gray regolith versus white patches.
Then going over to Oum, I'm seeing
the star pattern rays, and then the features of the craters start to become more prominent as I'm looking right where Jackson is and then to the west side.
It looks very more distinct from an albedo perspective and feature perspective.
Now along the equatorial line, I see those craters on the left side, and they are more distinct but smaller in the equator.
And then as I go towards the middle, there's a large crater directly in front of us, normal to our view, that has an interesting star pattern, four points.
It's making an X that's in a diagonal form.
And then over to the right of that, there's a big white blotch in between Oum and Orientale.
That's a very interesting feature.
And then going to the southern hemisphere,
Orientale has a bunch of bright splotches to its 10 o'clock position and sweeping in the northwest quadrant of Orientale and then going back to the center in the mid latitudes of the south hemisphere.
There's not many features that I could tell probably because of my viewing angle as far as terrain but lots of albedo patches that are from the northwest down to the southeast and that kind of hovers right on the northeast side of
Apollo Basin.
And then as I get to Apollo Basin, there's a lot more dark gray albedo to the southwest.
And then there's more cratering that is seen because of the viewing angle to the southwest hemisphere that kind of blends into the Terminator.
###Douglas Ohm
Alright, this is Andre Douglas.
I'm at Target 7 here.
We're looking at Oum.
Oum is to the northwest of Orientale right now.
It is a fairly big crater and it has a bunch of streaks that radiate outward.
I would say mostly from the 2 o'clock to the 7 o'clock position to the southeast and then more from the 11 o'clock back to the 7 o'clock counterclockwise.
from the northwest to the southwest, almost like a butterfly pattern.
Over in the 11 o'clock to 2 o'clock, there's not really many rays.
There's a dark field of regolith out there that is somewhat, I would say, medium gray.
And as we're approaching the crater from the outside, I see a ring of dark gray terrain that is really highlighting the rim of the crater.
And it comes in and is slightly sharp,
as we go up and over the crater, and then walking in down towards the center, it goes to a brighter white with some albedo there, then another light ring of gray, and then a white center.
So it kind of has a bullseye effect.
And then in the center area, that overall whiteness albedo is not as white as another patch that is about five diameters to the
I would say 7 o'clock position or southwest position from OM.
There's another white albedo patch that doesn't look like a crater, but just a patch.
But inside OM is much grayer than that, but still it's a light gray.
So it's not necessarily the freshest impact there.
And I would say there's more of a whiter plane on the south side of OM, and then again, a darker gray on the north side of OM.
And that's all I have for that.
###Douglas Terminator
All right, this is Andre Douglas, and we're in Target 8 for the Terminator.
Looking at the Terminator on the left side of the moon currently.
And man, it highlights a lot of terrain features.
I'm seeing a lot of prominent craters that look much deeper than they do anywhere from the middle and to the right.
And so as I get and start from the, I would say, dark side of the Terminator,
I can see just hints of crater rims that look like small crescent moons.
That's probably on, uh, touching some of the light from the sun.
And as I'm coming from left to right, I'm starting to see more of the left side of the craters that are most prominent with very, uh, it looks like high walls because of the way that the sun is hitting.
Um, and then as I start from the south side of the moon along the terminator,
Those craters do not look as prominent as the ones that are a little bit in between the south and the midline, the equatorial part of the moon.
Those craters seem to be very distinct and prominent.
And so as I get more towards the equator from the south side, these are the craters that I'm talking about.
They're very sharp and featured, rugged in terrain.
There's a lot of them concentrated at like the
I don't know, below 22 degrees or so before you get to the equator.
As you get towards the equator, they start to trail off and there's just a few.
There's not as many prominent features at the equator as there are right below and then now right above.
As I go right above the equator, they start to increase in frequency.
Not as much as the south, but you definitely see prominent features along the terminator.
And then as I go towards the north side, I am seeing more increase in frequency of craters, but less terrain feature distinctions.
And then as I get towards the top of the terminator, it looks like either a mare or a large crater, a big circular object, very dark, can't see the left side white edge of the crater like in the other ones.
But that looks like it's a bigger feature than some of the other things towards the mid-north latitudes.
I cannot see any signs of light that helps eliminate the backside of the Terminator and the dark side there.
I think most of those features that are coming in past the average line are from the sun itself.
It's just that those features are higher than normal and you catch those glints.
##Hansen Full Moon Mosaic
Thanks for watching.
and more diffuse.
###Hansen Recording While Photographing
Okay All right, so just to make sure I'm on the right target it's the huge crater with lots of rays almost in a starship shape And it's got a it's a high albedo and
And I'm sort of in the north center field of view.
And I'm just doing target, not the whole moon, right?
And is that how you worked it, how you, one of you held the PCD?
No, you'd be going off of your own PCD.
Okay.
I mean, we can, I think if we're showing each other something, but I think the assumption is we're both initially orienting ourselves with this, and then we kind of wrap together if there's any question or I'm going to show you something I noticed, make sure you're going to exhibit it.
Oh, there's the arthritis.
All right, so I'm gonna talk into my microphone a little bit here too.
I'm observing the earth rise.
It took me a while to get the camera sorted, but now it's going.
Christina's working on Jackson Crater, I think still, but I am just trying to capture the earth rise.
So I see a half earth.
I can see a very white south pole of the earth.
And I can see a landmass sort of in the middle.
And you could turn your pass through off too.
But you don't want to talk.
Okay, I'm there as well
mhm
Hey, Dre, can you hit target 20 on that thing for me?
That's what I do.
at least one newer crater on it that's very well defined and it might be the darkest actual region.
So do you want to just point at what you think you were filming there?
Yeah, so I see Aiken, right?
And then what I did have a little trouble coming up from Aiken and finding the things in between Aiken and there on that picture.
Like I see a really dark deep crater right above Aiken on there.
It doesn't show up at all on this.
I guess it's that, yeah.
I think we're quite a ways further up, actually.
Oh, I see the two.
Go up, up, up, up.
Up, up, up, up, up, that dark one there.
And you see the two to the right of it?
Yeah, I think they're identifiable right here.
No, these overlap, actually.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking, yeah.
Yeah, I think I was a little low initially Yeah, okay anyway all good learning Yeah
Yeah, I felt like I started photographing Earthrise when it happened, so.
No, you had to.
We're doing Earthrise site 21.
The exosphere just prior to Earthrise.
Oh.
So that's good to know.
Seeing Earth come out of the darkness.
Oops, sorry.
The balloons really stand out.
They're almost like a... Oh, I can't see.
I wasn't doing that.
I was trying to set up a five-minute timer.
Okay.
You know, because approximately,
It doesn't seem like the right thing to do.
Okay.
I have an idea on this because I think the social media and NatGeo people are perfect to just answer what they're seeing and leave the science people alone.
We really don't think we'll see out the other two windows?
Is that true?
I think you may see it out of that one.
I don't know that you're going to see it out of the side ones.
Really?
Oh, interesting.
Okay.
###Hansen Swirls 22
Okay, so I'm looking at the Murray Swirls, south of Aiken Crater, and I see a very large crater environment with at least five distinct circles inside of it, with lots of rim features inside that larger rim feature.
And I can't make out anything about the swirls specifically, but I'm in that area and it's right on the terminator.
###Hansen Terminator
No, you're fine.
No, no, you're okay.
Hi folks.
Do you want to sit?
I can hand it to you then.
You have control.
Okay, so I'm picking up... I think he did it already.
I'm picking up on 24, the Terminator.
So, just having a look here.
I want to describe the way the Terminator highlights the moon's craters and other features in the moon.
So, looking along the crater of the big photo.
I guess if I start in the, I'm gonna, just one sec here.
All right, so I see the most identifiable feature to me near the terminator is the Aiken crater just south of the equator, and it's fully lit in the current
phase of the moon and on the west side of Aitken Crater it's completely black from the the rim of the west side of the Aitken Crater.
But then as soon as you move north from there I can see quite a bit further west probably one or two hundred kilometers further west I can see some high points sticking out to the northwest of Aitken Crater.
And then as I come up further, I notice there is a very dark crater where the rim is highlighted from the 10 o'clock position down to the 6.30 position, but the western edge of that rim is not visible.
And then coming up from there, I start to move further east, following some highlands that are lined up with the west edge of Aiken Crater.
and they're the last part that's visible.
And then just to the north of that is a crater where I can see from 7 to 11 and then I'm missing a gap until noon and then I can see from noon to five o'clock.
And then to the north of that there's a very
well-illuminated crater where I can see the entire west wall down into the inside of the crater.
It looks like there's a central peak in that one that's sticking up.
It's a bright spot in the middle of the dark shadow of that crater.
and coming north from there I see a very kind of somewhat uniform altitude terrain for probably an eighth of the moon.
The terminator it's obviously not flat but it doesn't have any doesn't seem to have any huge peaks or huge valleys in that area.
And then there's a region with just a ton of craters right around the
Terminator, so we're about a quarter of the way down from the top of the moon on the Terminator.
I got a lot of small craters with lots of details of their rims all together.
And then going north of that gets into sort of an undulating area with not much to point out until you get to the very large crater that's right on the Terminator line near the north pole of the moon with a few small craters north of it.
And then down from Aiken Crater, we get some significant mountainous area type terrain.
I've got some very sharp, bright peaks to the southwest of Aiken Crater, and then a big valley, and then another peak to the south.
And then I can see, the last thing I can see below that, but above, I guess this is the, I don't know what the name of that crater is actually.
interesting observations though, but just to let you know that the next two are impact clashes on the dark side and deep space, so I think you've got more to determine.
All right, so the next thing is that Mare Swirls, Igni and Swirls area, which is very visible.
I can see the full large crater that all the smaller impact areas are inside of, and then down into the Schrodinger Basin.
###Koch 1
This is Christina Cook doing my verbal observation of Grimaldi Crater.
Grimaldi Crater is right on, from our view, I'm going to say the east side.
Again, I'm going to be speaking from our view, where east is on my right, west is on my left, and north-south is standard north-south.
From this view, Grimaldi Crater is a very distinctive dark mare area.
It's about the same darkness as a mid-grade inside of Oriental.
It's not as dark as the darkest of Oriental.
It does not have any kind of a hint of a hue.
It just has a very similar gray to the other grays of the moon.
would say that there's a gentle gradient of its darkness where the northern end is a little bit lighter than the southern end and it so that the the darkest part of the mare is the southern part.
From this oblique view it does appear to be fairly circular.
There's also a
an obvious second, much smaller mare, maybe about a fifth of the size of Grimaldi at its, I would say, 10 o'clock position.
It's northwest of Grimaldi.
And I don't see any kind of evidence of other terrain, any evidence of magnetic swirls or rays.
There may be some rays that
that kind of bisect Grimaldi, but they're not visible inside the mare.
There's kind of one line, looks like it maybe even could have been an old ray line from Oriental or something that transverses it.
But I think that it, the Grimaldi crater is newer than that.
It is on top of that.
That's about all I could offer in observations that there are some lighter points around it.
And he goes again, just straight into it.
Okay, I'm gonna go to my second target.
Hey Mark, this is Jackie.
I missed the first part of your call, but I thought that you wanted
So it is really on the edge.
In fact, it's not even visible past a couple of minutes here.
So, um, I would say the best thing we could do is just for photography, just, um, maybe they really want it as it's on the edge, like to see if there's any terrain or something.
So I think the best you could do is just like photograph that Mario area.
And I would do the actual limb.
Let's see.
terrace complex mostly flat crater does have a central piece so maybe you can get that this this view is near the north left limb yep it's in Oceanus Procellarum describe the colors and features exosphere so this is exosphere so yep all right highest zoom available crater and the limb so I would just dice that limb yeah okay mm-hmm
before I take my next set, I'm going to put like something as, think about the photos that we get a second shot.
Yeah.
I'll put like a two up and then I'll take pictures.
Perfect.
Okay.
I love it.
Yeah.
And yeah, that's great.
And then people also know it's you cause they see your hand.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, I need 14 hands.
Yeah.
That's funny.
You could do the four sideways.
But I don't know if that would work.
All right.
OK.
And.
###Koch 2
Okay, this is Christina Cook.
I'm describing Target 2, Silicus Crater.
This crater is on the limb, so we're really observing some of the limb features here and trying to see if there's anything discernible about the exosphere at the limb here.
So, and this crater is a light patch in a mare right at the limb and
What I can tell you about it is that its albedo is not as bright as some of the other ones that are visible.
For example, there's one directly due west of this crater that is very bright white, and this is not as white as that.
But it is the most bright thing in that mare.
From this oblique view, it looks like just a little stripe.
I'm not able to see any terrain with the naked eye that is on the limb to indicate height above the ground or anything like that.
And in terms of any hues, I don't see any strong hues, doesn't look any more pink, green, or brown than the areas around it or the white around it.
than, like I said, it's just not as bright as some of the brightest spots.
I would say if I was going to give it a hue, I would give it a tan hue.
Comparing it to other areas of the limb around it, it doesn't necessarily stick out except for its brighter albedo compared to the mare around it.
There's no difference in the exosphere in this area based on whether it's over a dark spot or a light spot.
I think that's all I'm going to describe on this crater.
###Koch 3
Christina cook observing site 3 Mari in Guinea and swirls This site is Fairly difficult to identify because it is right on the Terminator.
Of course that gives us some good observing options and in order to make sure that I have it I
I am going to locate it relative to Apollo and Aitken.
It is kind of like on the 90 degree between Apollo and Aitken if you were to draw a square encompassing them.
It is direct due west of Apollo and due south of Aitken, which I can identify on here.
So the crater shape is kind of appears almost hard to tell but I would I would describe it as a little bit trapezoidal but also kind of lily paddish with areas inside the crater that have almost little walls or terrain as well defining it.
The colors are difficult to discern, but I don't make out a lot of the swirling that is more easy to see when it is lit.
In fact, from this view, it's pretty difficult to see any brighter patterns.
I'm seeing a lot of dark and shadow.
But what I can see is that there is terrain almost tracing out, kind of tiling the crater, if you will, in almost hexagon type things that I can imagine are each about one-fifth the size of the crater.
Kind of like making biscuits in a small cast iron skillet.
In terms of color, I would say that the darkness doesn't really have as much of a discernible hue, definitely not any kind of tan or pink, just pretty dark without hue.
And I think that's all I can offer on this one.
###Koch 4
Christina Cook, annotating for site 4, Glushko Crater.
This is a very light area.
It is near the eastern limb and it is near a mare but distinct from it.
It has what appear to be rays.
But most distinctively, especially different from some of the other high albedo, I'm going to do that in real life, high albedo spots on the moon, it has an area around it that is also high albedo that's not distinctive line rays.
And that area is almost like another concentric circle around it.
The diameter of that second concentric circle around it is
about two to three times the diameter of Glushko Crater, the white spot in the middle.
And it's also not 100% uniform.
There's an area at about the 12 o'clock position from the crater, 12 to 1130, that is a darker area, not quite as dark as the mare fields, but about mid-grade between a very high albedo and the darker mare.
So in other words, overall, this crater is a very high albedo center, a two to three diameter times that diameter of a light gray with one speckle of a darker gray on it, and then some rays out from there that are the same color as the wider of the light grays.
None of those grays have any hue to them.
They are all kind of the same hue, which is a very gray gray, no green, tan or pink.
And I'm not able to make out any terracing features or any terrain features.
From this view, it does seem pretty flat.
The one exception to that, if I squint, I can kind of see almost like a target pattern within the very inner high albedo area.
That's hard to say if that's really there.
Okay, that's five minutes on that one, so I think that's about it.
###Koch 5
Christina Cook annotating site 5, Sundman 5 crater.
We weren't able to 100% identify exactly this crater, but it does say the line of craters, so I'll describe the line of craters that is in this area near the limb.
Nothing distinctive on the limb itself, no views of the exosphere.
The craters themselves appear to be pretty new, just because they're very round.
They all are some of the smallest visible craters on the surface of the moon.
From the view looking at the moon with my eyes, I am not able to discern any one crater being deeper, more distinctive, or more shadowed than the others, as is evident on the photo in the lunar targeting plan.
So that's one thing to note.
I do see a lot of distinctive dots in this area that are little dots of high albedo areas and what is otherwise a medium gray tones in an area that doesn't have a lot of mare, but also to the west of the big mare sort of field.
I'm also not able to make out a very distinctive line of craters in this particular area.
There are some lines of craters that all sort of follow lines of radiation out from ohm.
This one would be, if it were one of those at about the four o'clock position, I can see several other lines of craters that do appear like they're scattered from ohm.
Most of those lines of craters are equidistant apart and of the same albedo, each one of them in the same size.
If this one is from that line just
per the picture, it would be distinctive because of its clearer shape and depth.
But again, I'm not able to see that on the moon itself.
I don't see any differences in color in this area.
There could be a slight basin shape that is kind of inside the isosceles triangle of lighter areas here.
A circle that is about the height of the isosceles triangle, a little shorter, with its upper left quadrant being defined by a little dark
spot that appears to be Mario and not Shadow.
That's all I'm going to say about that.
###Koch 19
Okay, this is Christina Cook.
I'm doing an observation for site 19 Jackson Crater.
Visually tracing the rays from the center of the crater, I'm gonna describe how they change as they move away.
I think a really neat thing about Jackson Crater is they are very predominant rays, and they all kind of peter out at about the same radius from the center of Jackson Crater, which makes it almost look like a starfish.
that distance from the center of the crater is probably about six crater diameters away, five to six crater diameters away.
One ray that extends a little farther than that is the one that goes down to what I think is Korolyov
crater or basin and a high albedo little spot that's above it, that ray is a little longer than the others.
It almost also appears as if two rays that go out the top of Jackson Crater a little bit towards the northeast almost crisscross.
Difficult to say whether that's albedo or if that's terrain that makes it look like it, but
there is kind of an area on the northeast and triangular shaped area of Jackson that kind of is almost like a continuous ray blob, if you will.
Like I said, they all kind of peter out after that or turn very, very light and are more difficult to trace after that.
And I think that's all I'm going to talk about for Jackson.
###Koch 20
Okay, this is Christina Cook, audio recording of observations from Site 20 Dewar Crater Region.
This region is in the Terminator, so it is fairly darkened and a little bit difficult to discern.
Might get a little closer.
But in general, the crater region
kind of right in the center of the Terminator is where I think that we are looking for this Dewar Crater region.
So in this dark, small region,
colors that you can see with the naked eye are a pretty similar color.
They are pretty gray, not a strong hue of orange or tan or green or pink.
If I had to pick a hue I would pick a little bit on the
green to tan side and I would say that the hues don't really change but there is a slight albedo change where the southern area is a little bit of a lighter higher albedo.
I don't see any real evidence of swirls but I do see some differing color areas and differing albedo.
but nothing overly remarkable in this region.
Recognizing that it has some volcanic history, I can see that it is almost like a lighter version of a small mare, but not as distinctive as some of our other mare regions.
The relationship of it to other features, I do think there's at least one newer crater on it that's very well defined.
And it might be the darkest actual region when we're not thinking about, you know, not counting the shadows in this area.
And it is also pretty smooth other than the one distinctive crater that's kind of on top of it.
And that'll wrap up my recording.
###Koch 21
No, you had to.
Yeah, I'm gonna do a little voice recording.
So this is Christina Cook doing Earthrise site 21.
The exosphere just prior to Earthrise.
Oh, so that's good to know.
Seeing Earth come out of the darkened side of the moon was absolutely incredible.
The exosphere wasn't notable.
I didn't see any glow, like apparent glowing or
you know, raised particulates or levitated, you know, ion region or anything like that.
The colors of Earth look very bright as they popped out of the eclipse of the moon.
the blues really stand out they're almost a deeper darker almost like a royal to aqua blue
###Koch 22
Christina Cook observing site 22, the Mare and Swirls.
This is a lot more evident than earlier when it was more in the Terminator.
We can see some of the swirling and the colors are a little bit more apparent as well as the terrain on the western side of the Mare.
There is quite a bit of uplift all around the crater, well-defined.
those tiles that tiling feature that I was talking about my first observation is just as apparent but now I can see that it's kind of primarily only on the eastern half of the crater as I can see right now the swirls are also not very apparent if you look very closely you can see some color deviations but not it's not super obvious
And it's not clear to me if they follow the same lines as that inner tiling that I talked about.
That wraps up this observation.
###Koch 23
Christina Cook recording the full moon albedo and full moon observations site 23.
So in this view of the moon it is almost exactly a half moon with the eastern half lit.
The prominent features are ohm
crater and I would say two other high albedo areas south of Oum, one of which is close to equatorial and the other which is a few degrees latitude south of equatorial and more diffuse.
Overall the darker regions of the moon are in the north and south with several more darker mare patches that are of
diameter... I wish I had a diameter here.
Let's see if I can get one.
Maybe 50 to 100 kilometers in the southern region at about the 60-ish latitude area.
Kind of like, almost looking like little, like scarrings, darker mare scarrings down there, whereas the northern hemisphere doesn't really have those marks in that same way.
The higher albedo regions are all very centered in the east along kind of that eastern horizon and limb.
Those are in addition to the three prominent high albedo spots that I talked about earlier.
So in general it goes from a low albedo at the terminator which
to higher albedo on the east, and that isn't just because of the shattering of the Terminator.
Even when we're out of those high shadows of the Terminator, you see some of that same pattern.
The southern hemisphere, you can really make out the overall darkness of the South Pole-Aitken Basin.
There really aren't any high albedo areas in that southern area at all.