All right, this is Andre Douglas, and we're in Target 8 for the Terminator.
Looking at the Terminator on the left side of the moon currently.
And man, it highlights a lot of terrain features.
I'm seeing a lot of prominent craters that look much deeper than they do anywhere from the middle and to the right.
And so as I get and start from the, I would say, dark side of the Terminator,
I can see just hints of crater rims that look like small crescent moons.
That's probably on, uh, touching some of the light from the sun.
And as I'm coming from left to right, I'm starting to see more of the left side of the craters that are most prominent with very, uh, it looks like high walls because of the way that the sun is hitting.
Um, and then as I start from the south side of the moon along the terminator,
Those craters do not look as prominent as the ones that are a little bit in between the south and the midline, the equatorial part of the moon.
Those craters seem to be very distinct and prominent.
And so as I get more towards the equator from the south side, these are the craters that I'm talking about.
They're very sharp and featured, rugged in terrain.
There's a lot of them concentrated at like the
I don't know, below 22 degrees or so before you get to the equator.
As you get towards the equator, they start to trail off and there's just a few.
There's not as many prominent features at the equator as there are right below and then now right above.
As I go right above the equator, they start to increase in frequency.
Not as much as the south, but you definitely see prominent features along the terminator.
And then as I go towards the north side, I am seeing more increase in frequency of craters, but less terrain feature distinctions.
And then as I get towards the top of the terminator, it looks like either a mare or a large crater, a big circular object, very dark, can't see the left side white edge of the crater like in the other ones.
But that looks like it's a bigger feature than some of the other things towards the mid-north latitudes.
I cannot see any signs of light that helps eliminate the backside of the Terminator and the dark side there.
I think most of those features that are coming in past the average line are from the sun itself.
It's just that those features are higher than normal and you catch those glints.