Okay, this is Christina Cook.
I'm describing Target 2, Silicus Crater.
This crater is on the limb, so we're really observing some of the limb features here and trying to see if there's anything discernible about the exosphere at the limb here.
So, and this crater is a light patch in a mare right at the limb and
What I can tell you about it is that its albedo is not as bright as some of the other ones that are visible.
For example, there's one directly due west of this crater that is very bright white, and this is not as white as that.
But it is the most bright thing in that mare.
From this oblique view, it looks like just a little stripe.
I'm not able to see any terrain with the naked eye that is on the limb to indicate height above the ground or anything like that.
And in terms of any hues, I don't see any strong hues, doesn't look any more pink, green, or brown than the areas around it or the white around it.
than, like I said, it's just not as bright as some of the brightest spots.
I would say if I was going to give it a hue, I would give it a tan hue.
Comparing it to other areas of the limb around it, it doesn't necessarily stick out except for its brighter albedo compared to the mare around it.
There's no difference in the exosphere in this area based on whether it's over a dark spot or a light spot.
I think that's all I'm going to describe on this crater.