This is Christina Cook doing my verbal observation of Grimaldi Crater.
Grimaldi Crater is right on, from our view, I'm going to say the east side.
Again, I'm going to be speaking from our view, where east is on my right, west is on my left, and north-south is standard north-south.
From this view, Grimaldi Crater is a very distinctive dark mare area.
It's about the same darkness as a mid-grade inside of Oriental.
It's not as dark as the darkest of Oriental.
It does not have any kind of a hint of a hue.
It just has a very similar gray to the other grays of the moon.
would say that there's a gentle gradient of its darkness where the northern end is a little bit lighter than the southern end and it so that the the darkest part of the mare is the southern part.
From this oblique view it does appear to be fairly circular.
There's also a
an obvious second, much smaller mare, maybe about a fifth of the size of Grimaldi at its, I would say, 10 o'clock position.
It's northwest of Grimaldi.
And I don't see any kind of evidence of other terrain, any evidence of magnetic swirls or rays.
There may be some rays that
that kind of bisect Grimaldi, but they're not visible inside the mare.
There's kind of one line, looks like it maybe even could have been an old ray line from Oriental or something that transverses it.
But I think that it, the Grimaldi crater is newer than that.
It is on top of that.
That's about all I could offer in observations that there are some lighter points around it.
And he goes again, just straight into it.
Okay, I'm gonna go to my second target.
Hey Mark, this is Jackie.
I missed the first part of your call, but I thought that you wanted
So it is really on the edge.
In fact, it's not even visible past a couple of minutes here.
So, um, I would say the best thing we could do is just for photography, just, um, maybe they really want it as it's on the edge, like to see if there's any terrain or something.
So I think the best you could do is just like photograph that Mario area.
And I would do the actual limb.
Let's see.
terrace complex mostly flat crater does have a central piece so maybe you can get that this this view is near the north left limb yep it's in Oceanus Procellarum describe the colors and features exosphere so this is exosphere so yep all right highest zoom available crater and the limb so I would just dice that limb yeah okay mm-hmm
before I take my next set, I'm going to put like something as, think about the photos that we get a second shot.
Yeah.
I'll put like a two up and then I'll take pictures.
Perfect.
Okay.
I love it.
Yeah.
And yeah, that's great.
And then people also know it's you cause they see your hand.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, I need 14 hands.
Yeah.
That's funny.
You could do the four sideways.
But I don't know if that would work.
All right.
OK.
And.