Christina Cook, annotating for site 4, Glushko Crater.
This is a very light area.
It is near the eastern limb and it is near a mare but distinct from it.
It has what appear to be rays.
But most distinctively, especially different from some of the other high albedo, I'm going to do that in real life, high albedo spots on the moon, it has an area around it that is also high albedo that's not distinctive line rays.
And that area is almost like another concentric circle around it.
The diameter of that second concentric circle around it is
about two to three times the diameter of Glushko Crater, the white spot in the middle.
And it's also not 100% uniform.
There's an area at about the 12 o'clock position from the crater, 12 to 1130, that is a darker area, not quite as dark as the mare fields, but about mid-grade between a very high albedo and the darker mare.
So in other words, overall, this crater is a very high albedo center, a two to three diameter times that diameter of a light gray with one speckle of a darker gray on it, and then some rays out from there that are the same color as the wider of the light grays.
None of those grays have any hue to them.
They are all kind of the same hue, which is a very gray gray, no green, tan or pink.
And I'm not able to make out any terracing features or any terrain features.
From this view, it does seem pretty flat.
The one exception to that, if I squint, I can kind of see almost like a target pattern within the very inner high albedo area.
That's hard to say if that's really there.
Okay, that's five minutes on that one, so I think that's about it.