Okay, this is Christina Cook, audio recording of observations from Site 20 Dewar Crater Region.
This region is in the Terminator, so it is fairly darkened and a little bit difficult to discern.
Might get a little closer.
But in general, the crater region
kind of right in the center of the Terminator is where I think that we are looking for this Dewar Crater region.
So in this dark, small region,
colors that you can see with the naked eye are a pretty similar color.
They are pretty gray, not a strong hue of orange or tan or green or pink.
If I had to pick a hue I would pick a little bit on the
green to tan side and I would say that the hues don't really change but there is a slight albedo change where the southern area is a little bit of a lighter higher albedo.
I don't see any real evidence of swirls but I do see some differing color areas and differing albedo.
but nothing overly remarkable in this region.
Recognizing that it has some volcanic history, I can see that it is almost like a lighter version of a small mare, but not as distinctive as some of our other mare regions.
The relationship of it to other features, I do think there's at least one newer crater on it that's very well defined.
And it might be the darkest actual region when we're not thinking about, you know, not counting the shadows in this area.
And it is also pretty smooth other than the one distinctive crater that's kind of on top of it.
And that'll wrap up my recording.