All right, we are recording for a minute.
We're in the ESCO lab looking at the lunar target guide and visual cues.
And you'll see impact crater is located on the far side with sharply defined rim, a complex central peak structure, terraced wall, and expansive ray system.
So now you know that.
Let's see, lunar geography review.
We have some tabs in here, view, general notes.
Guidance for imaging and observations, we have our cue card tab, and then our cue cards have, they're not filled out, so I can't read those.
But in theory, there will be specific things in these cue cards.
Now I don't know how long I've talked, 50 seconds, 51, 52.
And we'll record for a minute, and then we'll stop it.
Three more seconds, two, one, and.