Okay, this is Christina Cook.
I'm doing an observation for site 19 Jackson Crater.
Visually tracing the rays from the center of the crater, I'm gonna describe how they change as they move away.
I think a really neat thing about Jackson Crater is they are very predominant rays, and they all kind of peter out at about the same radius from the center of Jackson Crater, which makes it almost look like a starfish.
that distance from the center of the crater is probably about six crater diameters away, five to six crater diameters away.
One ray that extends a little farther than that is the one that goes down to what I think is Korolyov
crater or basin and a high albedo little spot that's above it, that ray is a little longer than the others.
It almost also appears as if two rays that go out the top of Jackson Crater a little bit towards the northeast almost crisscross.
Difficult to say whether that's albedo or if that's terrain that makes it look like it, but
there is kind of an area on the northeast and triangular shaped area of Jackson that kind of is almost like a continuous ray blob, if you will.
Like I said, they all kind of peter out after that or turn very, very light and are more difficult to trace after that.
And I think that's all I'm going to talk about for Jackson.