All right, I am going to do a recording of mare ingenii.
So I am looking at the crater.
It is partway down to the South Pole.
It's really easy to see the swirling that we have in mare ingenii here that looks like white streaks, curly, swirly streaks going across.
It seems like those swirls are most prevalent in the bottom half of that mare field.
As you go up a little higher, actually the whole, it almost looks like an eyeball.
And so if you see that darker part of the mare pond, it is darker in color.
It doesn't really have as many of those swirls.
But when you look around the outside, it's almost like where the iris of the eye would be.
You can see those swirls very similarly to the veins that you would see in your eye.
The texture along the right side of the crater, it's sort of a rubbly texture.
You can tell that there's just a lot of broken down material near where the crater rim would have been.
And the interesting thing is also just looking at this, I see a lot of that orange brown rusty color that matches some of the other mare infills that we see in South Pole Lake and Basin.
It's really cool to see these swirls in exactly where they're supposed to be and they really do look similar to what we are seeing in Muscoviense as well.