Okay, I went ahead and annotated my first impact flash observation.
Back at the camera, back out looking at the window.
Gonna try to take a photo every 30 seconds or so as this Terminator slowly walks across while also looking through the viewfinder.
Using the camera as kind of monocular to look for Impact Flashes.
while also capturing a nice time sequence at the same lens zoom.
I'm not going to change that at all, just going to capture the whole field of view of the moon from north to south and watch that Terminator just cross
Still really impressed by that crater with the central peak in it, Tsiolkovsky, I think, and it's really just going into the Terminator now.
It's amazing how you can see that rim highlighted, but the darkness of the Terminator just to the west of it.
Central peak is still really popping out, but also trying to train my eye towards the
the part of the moon that's in the Terminator, making sure that I don't miss any impact flash again.
That last one was just this bright green streak that kind of did this Z shape.
Tried best to capture it in the annotation using the appropriate color pen that I could get close to that bright green.
Didn't do it justice, but it definitely was not a point source.
more of a streak, so not sure how to explain that one.
I think for file size reasons I'm going to go ahead and end this audio file.
and continue to observe in this manner, but let you know if I do see any other Impact Flashes during the remainder of the time that we have here on target 27.