start on Ryder Crater.
I got really distracted during Earthrise and so I'm gonna get going on this one right now.
I can see it's down along the southern, the southern limb and the South Poleaitken Basin Acon and so I'm using this again Marie.
I'm looking for Ryder with my camera along the southern rim.
I'm looking to see
So it's definitely sort of hard to pick this one out.
So I have this high albedo spot that I'm looking for here.
I don't have too much time, so it should be, I can see where, Teosca, is that what there?
Okay, I can see the peak right next to it there, and I can see their bright spot now.
I found that peak.
I found that bright spot, so I'm going to zoom in and get some good images there of that area.
Let's see how that, looking at that with the rest of the South Poleaitken Basin Aiken Basin area.
And so, yeah, I can see exactly that crater with the peak ring.
So I'm really looking to see if I can see that bright spot
The brightness is not standing out as much as I would have expected right now.
So that is sort of surprising.
It's not surprising because it's right on the Terminator there.
So that brightness didn't really help me find it.
More of the morphology did.
So making sure that I'm in the right spot.
There's the two double right above it and then the mare.
So I definitely got some images of that material there.
But really cannot see any of those ejector rays.
And looking for...
There's definitely... Yeah, it's definitely slightly lighter.
But really hard to just pick out much more of that texture of that small area besides like...
Sort of looks like a dome-y material.
Sort of raised a little bit.
Slightly lighter than the area around it.
Is that a volcano cone right there?
Probably not, but pretty interesting.