Okay, Kelsey here.
Target 17, Dewar Crater Region Crater Region.
I will say that my voice recorder app is misbehaving.
Last time only a power cycle fixed it, but if I power cycle, I will risk losing target 18, which is high priority.
So I am going to hope that my experience last time wins out and the recordings are still there, even if I can't hear them back.
So here I am, Dewar Crater Region is the next,
target I have.
Let's see on the LTP, it's kind of like on a line between Aitken Crater Crater and Muscovy End.
So I'm gonna follow it up.
Yep, I think I see it there.
So let me see, go to the 400 millimeter.
What am I looking for?
Low albedo anomaly, maybe cryptomare.
Okay, so let me see here.
All right, so in the window, I am actually, my head is pointing toward sort of the right east side again.
I understand it's the western limb, but it's to my east.
And so the camera is pointed 90 degrees from the last pictures I took.
I'm going to zoom in here.
Do a regional, yeah, really pops out beautifully in the zoom.
OK, going all the way to 400 here.
And in that zoom lens, I can really see there's a diffuse patch of that darker material.
Here, I'll get a picture of it.
I'll get a picture of it with some context here.
And let me see.
Yeah, so it looks, it is diffuse, and it's especially diffuse as you move out from it.
It's almost like several layers of diffusivity where it's darker in the middle,
and then slightly less dark, but still darker than the surrounding terrain coming out.
I think there are fewer craters on it than the surrounding area, suggesting, well, that doesn't make sense if it's Cryptomare, but I'm telling you, I don't really see a higher density of craters.
It's just kind of the same as the surrounding terrain.
So the only indication of anything really is that albedo color.
I don't even really see
relationship between the dark albedo and topography here.
Take a nice picture and I'll move on to the next high priority target.