Angela here.
OK, I am back with you and I see my next target is 14 Oppenheimer Basin.
It's a high priority, so let me get great image coverage of it because I have the camera at the moment.
Right, I'm gonna.
Look at.
Apollo.
And then I'm going to zoom in and make sure that I can get Alpenheuer, which is right next to Apollo.
Yep, just double checking my LTP that it is the cluster of three.
Well, actually, what's obvious to me is that it kind of looks like three Mari patches within this
within this greater crater.
So I'll just make sure I get focus on some of the low points and the higher points so hopefully you can get that good mosaic of it.
I will make sure to get Apollo and Oppenheimer Basin in one single frame.
I just saw that target.
Yeah, let me try to compare these two.
There's a lot more diffuse boundaries in the Oppenheimer Basin Mare patches than the Apollo Mare patches.
They're much more distinct and sharp.
in Apollo versus Oppenheimer Basin, which is, again, that diffuse type of boundary.
I'm also here.
If I get at a better angle, maybe I can see this.
So now I'm kind of clocked a little bit.
differently, so if you see that change in angle, that's why.
I'm just trying to focus on the crater ray that's coming from Crook's that's separating these two craters.
Let me zoom out a little bit just to make sure I get Crook's in the photo, but then I will just like kind of slowly zoom in and then I'm at my max zoom now focusing on that.
crater ray, which is almost at the boundary of Apollo and Oppenheimer Basin.
In general, for the color tones and differences between Oppenheimer Basin and Apollo Basin, I would say Oppenheimer Basin has darker, deeper tones than Apollo.
The deepest of the tones is of the three kind of dark patches that are within Oppenheimer Basin.
The top one is the darkest.
Let me just make sure I'm on timeline still.
Okay, I am.
Okay, I'm gonna leave it there and take a few more pictures.