And then I can see a little bit of that.
There's sort of a dull, sort of orange-brownish that is the background grey.
The very bright, greater rays are overlapping that.
I can see the ones from Jackson and Ulm.
And it cooks very brightly here.
I can see how that Jackson Crater Ray goes all the way down into a cave basin.
My general impressions is that I'm just chiming on, looking here, just knowing that we are passing the moon.
Just seeing the colors, I can really see the darkness there of the Mari.
So I can see those pretty large features from both that South Lake and Bay Sand.
It's sort of a different hue behind sort of a dark horn here than some of the colors that are behind.
the moon like this and all of its glory it's just amazing it's really happy to be standing here like this let's see I can really really start to see some of those are there some um the train there
So I think that is the end of my first recording.