Okay, quick one on Ryder Crater, our target Foxtrot.
Just running out of time and I want to make sure I get some of the higher priority targets.
So this will be a quick one.
I did take a long look at the LTP to make sure that I was able to train my eyes in on Ryder.
And I think I've nailed it just below that larger crater that has a ring structure and a mare.
I see Ryder pretty distinctly just given its higher albedo and some topography that's now popping out along the Terminator.
And as I zoom in on the LTP and flip back and forth, I can definitely match up the two pretty similar diameter craters under the crater that is larger just above Ryder.
and be able to trace that down.
And then there's a similar three or four craters kind of in a square that allow me to pick up Ryder with the higher albedo of those four.
Other than that, I can't say too much about Ryder other than it has that higher albedo visibly by my eye and it is really distinct.
with some of the topography around there.
Don't know how to explain it, but there's a very distinct topography, almost looks like deeper crater in that area.
I think that's one just to the west of Ryder, the higher albedo one.
As I zoom in, yeah, for sure, the one that looks like a deeper crater is to the west of Ryder, but there's a series of four craters there that make about the same diameters to each other.
And rider is that higher albedo one, which my eye does pick up out the window.