All right, I'm starting Sudman Crater, target number seven.
Taking a look now for locating it on the limb just above Oriental.
This one's definitely at the extent of the human eye.
I can't for say, using the LDP, flipping back and forth, that I for sure am seeing Sudman, target number seven.
There is a few white specks out there above Apollo Basin that I can try to index off of, but really hard to pick up Sudman for sure.
So let me just try to index again.
I see the Apollo ring.
I'm just not 100% sure as I zoom in on the LDP and flip my eyes back and forth.
Um, that I am indeed being able to pick up Sundman J Crater.
So, um, hopefully Marie's picking that up in the camera, um, at the highest focal length that she can.
Uh, there is a lot of albedo little specks of white and kind of a medium gray field out there.
Not a lot of topography is picking up in these illumination conditions, except for that rim of Apollo.
Um, and.
I'm sorry, Oriental.
So every time I said Apollo previously, it's Orientale Basin.
So just right above Orientale Basin, just that field of speckled white in that medium gray and just not able to pick out Sudman for sure.
The rays of one of the crater in there maybe are a little distinct.
So, but I don't think it's Sudman.
I think it's more towards Ohms Crater and
Yeah, with that I'm going to close out target number 7 and move to 8 just because I'm not 100% sure that I'm seeing Sudman.