All right, back with you on target 22.
Now back over into the window number two with the camera and the long lens.
And so just taking a look now and getting set up, but I'm gonna leave the audio on.
So forget a few little ramblings here as I get set up on target 22.
So I'm looking for that crater region and luckily have the long lens to help me get there.
So gonna,
index off of Jackson.
Make sure that it's about in line with the southern part of Muscovian Basin.
Again, forgive my rambling here as I make sure that I'm getting the right target and the right focal length.
So it looks like you want highest focal length surrounding dark plains and central images of the region.
So I'm gonna make sure that I've got the right
Target, I think I've got the right target because I See a distinct darker region in that that I can pick up off the 200 milliliter 200 millimeter image in the lunar targeting package, so gonna go ahead and start with a Center image and work my way in with that focal length all the way to the highest so first image and
is gonna capture both Jackson and Muscovian basins and work my way into what I believe that crater is.
And I can really start to pick up that darker region.
Really appreciate the camera now after trying to view some things with the naked eye.
And so I'm gonna do that whole sequence of images again, working my way in.
with the camera slowly changing the zoom lens but keeping the central focus spot in the same area.
This looks like it's, just double checking where my next highest priority target is, Muscovian Basin, so looks like I'm good, so I'm gonna take a few more shots.
Trying to keep at the highest
focal length and kind of surround that area with a number of images.
Changing a little bit the camera orientation relative to the window of Orion to just make sure I get some glare out of there.
And double checking my shroud to make sure I don't have any light seeping in.
Capturing a few good images of that area, the target 22 area with Jackson also in frame.
It allows you to trace from Jackson to that area via some of the rays.
And one last image zoomed out to capture both the Earth and Moon as it currently
is oriented out window two and I'm just going to do another series with the camera oriented in vertical.
It's a little bit harder to stabilize the camera in vertical but does give you a little bit more north-south extent.
Man, Earth is beautiful out there so I'm just going to take a picture of
a few pictures of Earth while we have the opportunity.
Okay, a few bonus pictures of Earth there at the end, but I'm gonna close out.
Target 22.
and move on to Jackson.
### Transcript 002
Starting the voice recording for target one, Whole Moon.
We've just got visibility on the moon.
And so target number one, taking a look at the observation actions.
Now I'm gonna give you my general impression as I'm looking through the lens, as I'm capturing the Whole Moon with a mid-focus mosaic.
Starting now with a north-south pattern.
50% overlap.
Coming down the limb of the moon to the left.
Definitely could make out Muscovians very clearly in the lens.
I'm having to concentrate on the snake pattern
to get the 50% overlap and get high resolution images.
Sure is beautiful.
And getting really spectacular rays that my eye didn't pick up in the camera now that I'm zoomed in.
Just completed the second pass on the snake.
Again, very clear rays.
Concentrating on the 50% overlap, so it might be a little choppy on my voice comm here.
Near the southern part, I'm picking up a lot of the dark mari infill on some of those southern craters.
Gonna give a quick look at my screen while I have a target to index off of.
Targets look in focus on my D5 screen, so I'm gonna pick up on that target where I left off, continue the pattern up.
Certainly feel like I'm getting 50% overlap.
Overall, just concentrating on getting the mosaic well documented.
before I make a few other observations through the lens.
Picking up Apollo Basin now, beautiful in the resolution that I can see with this medium lens.
Okay, struggling on the
a limb that's to the three o'clock position out the window right now to just get the full mosaic and resolution.
Camera's struggling a little bit on focusing, so I'm having to target the center of the moon or at least further in on the moon to get the far limb at three o'clock.
Overall, I had the lens set at about 280, and taking a look at any other observation actions you want.
So the biggest thing that stuck out to me as I took that mosaic was the colors of those rays, specifically up in kind of the northwestern quadrant.
The albedo was a very stark difference
through the lens versus what my eye could pick up.
And the features across the globe are just spectacular and looking forward to getting into the next targets.
### Transcript 003
All right, starting target 19 still in window number three.
I've got a really good config with the PCD kind of set up in front of me where I can glance down at it and both look out window three and make the observations now.
So starting number 19 with the three of three of the Whole Moon.
I'll just kind of give you my impression from the Terminator going to
the bright limb, so essentially from west to east, and make some observations as I do that over the course of the next few minutes.
So right at the Terminator, I mean, it's black.
The hearth out there is beautiful still, so my eye is still drawn to those colors.
But deep in the Terminator, I can't pick out features until I get right to a pretty distinct line.
Right now it's at, I think, Sokoski.
The Terminator is really highlighting the terrain or the rim of Sokoski.
The western limb of Sokoski crater is just really highlighted and the central peak.
I can almost convince myself I'm seeing the shadow of the central peak of Sokoski on its western limb.
That would be really interesting to see through the camera.
Hopefully she's capturing some of that in the camera right now.
The topography is really popping.
Those craters are really distinct along the Terminator, north and south of Silkoski.
And it's not too far past Silkoski crater, maybe one or two Silkoski crater diameters away that the terrain starts to lose some of that sharpness that the illumination provides.
Another beautiful area, make sure I'm getting
my orientation right is like the, there's Muscovians basin, which is starting to, starting to get some of that topography advantage from the illumination.
So I'm really looking forward to keeping an eye on that one as we continue to terminate or continues to move towards Muscovians.
But also that larger basin that's to the south and a little bit west of
Muscovian basin that's about the same size is really just it's amazing how flat and stark that is across the center of that larger crater.
As I move more mid in line with the lunar surface, you know, the reflections and albedo are pretty dramatic in that area.
So I can definitely pick out some of the high
albedo crater rays.
There's one that looks almost like a perfect little star, a five-pointed star, almost central on the moon.
It doesn't show up in any kind of images that I see.
And moving down to the crater that's just south of that, I think that's Mari Injani, if I double check in here.
Yeah, so it's around Aitken Crater, Mari Injani area.
That terrain starts to get a little bit darker and albedo and maybe a little bit more sharp in the topography in that area.
Not sure why my eyes are picking up a little bit more, maybe because of just the darker albedo of that area.
I see the topography maybe a little more.
Jackson Crater right now, if my eyes move back up, is just
gleaming almost white with those crater rays just stretching across at least a third or half of the moon.
Again, I mentioned previously that wedge of Jackson that seems like it's missing from eight o'clock to about two o'clock.
Just cannot pick up any rays in that direction, but a lot of distinct other rays in the other cardinal directions.
And then finally, the full eastern limb is pretty high albedo or high illumination right now.
Just totally lose the topography along that rim as expected.
And really hard to pick out any major craters, features, basins as my eyes move towards the east.
Just one more quick word about the Earth out there.
There's really great shot out the window right now with Earth kind of standing off in the distance, but still within frame of the moon.
And this Terminator really makes a dramatic image that we're hopefully capturing for the world to see.
So with that, I'll end Target 19 and take a look at here at Aiken and get started on our next targets.
### Transcript 004
And then I can see a little bit of that.
There's sort of a dull, sort of orange-brownish that is the background grey.
The very bright, greater rays are overlapping that.
I can see the ones from Jackson and Ulm.
And it cooks very brightly here.
I can see how that Jackson Crater Ray goes all the way down into a cave basin.
My general impressions is that I'm just chiming on, looking here, just knowing that we are passing the moon.
Just seeing the colors, I can really see the darkness there of the Mari.
So I can see those pretty large features from both that South Lake and Bay Sand.
It's sort of a different hue behind sort of a dark horn here than some of the colors that are behind.
the moon like this and all of its glory it's just amazing it's really happy to be standing here like this let's see I can really really start to see some of those are there some um the train there
So I think that is the end of my first recording.
### Transcript 005
All right, starting number target two, the limb out at Ocea procularis.
So gonna try to cover this in a series of photos at the highest focal length right along that limb.
So that's about where I left off on target one.
The highest focal length, trying to make sure the target's sharp.
As I work down, trying to get almost 75% overlap.
I'm also gonna give that more of a context by zooming out, targeting the center of target two.
And do that again with another series of images at about 75% overlap.
Definitely can see the darker parts of that target.
All right, on the limb, don't noticeably see a lot of topography picking up just based on the illumination right now.
Through the highest zoom of the lens,
Definitely see a lot of albedo change across the transition.
Take a few just centered in right on the limb, kind of pressing the extremes of the camera focus.
And again, gonna take a fully zoomed out but centered image
on that target and just work inwards.
He's in the same center spot, but just changing the zoom.
Okay, quick look at the observation actions.
I covered a lot of the focus changes that I was making.
The color is pretty stark in that area, goes from the dark
black of the part of the target that is centered on the target image seen in the LTP, and then has a pretty stark transition from that dark area into the lighter albedo areas, kind of towards Ohm Crater Crater as you make your way out that way.
I could pick it up, the resolution of Marius Hills, but not as much topography as I thought I would see along the
that complex rim.
I'm going to end voice recording here and move on to target three.
### Transcript 006
All right, starting target three, Orientale Basin.
Looking for a mosaic of the entire feature, west to east snake pattern with 50% overlap with the highest focal length.
So I'm at the 400 focal length.
First off, I'm gonna take more of a context photo of Orientale Basin with the red square dead center, and then start that mosaic.
So that should provide context for a mosaic.
I'm almost gonna go for 75% overlap and really blast across the top of Oriental, west to east.
Second pass.
Across the center of Oriental.
third pass across the bottom of Oriental.
Had a couple camera fires there that only caught one or two images out of the three stack.
And again, finishing off that target with a context photo at about mid-zoom level, about 200.
So I see that's a high-priority target.
It captured everything at least at 50% overlap.
Saw a lot of the annular ring and ejecta structure as I was taking those photos.
I'm also gonna make an annotation since that's a high-priority target with a wavefowl.
Standby for that, but incredible target overall.
The annular ring does start to pick up in that illumination condition.
In fact, I'm going to take a few more photos just zoomed in right on the part dead center that I see the annular ring sticking up the most.
That's kind of at the three o'clock position.
Hip north is up the window north.
Also some spectacular topography seen at the smaller craters that are in Oriental.
And a really good contrast between the
the darker regions at the base of Oriental, the darker rim of Oriental, kind of from the 12 o'clock to the three o'clock.
And that topography really stands out, as I said, in this illumination condition.
Took a few more zoomed in pictures that just capture the entirety of Oriental.
I'm gonna try one using the camera in a vertical position.
And I'm going to end the recording here and put an audio recording to mark that in the D5.
### Transcript 007
So now, this is Marie, I'm doing my observation of Orientale Basin.
I can see the rim, the rings of Oriental.
I can see the Rooks ring on the, the Cordillera ring on the outside and the Oriental.
And I can also see that dark annular ring around about five, about six o'clock.
So I can see that the,
There's not as much topography that I can see here that it really looks like the higher parts of the rings are a little bit lighter while there looks like there is the darker mare material that's sort of like hugging along the edge of that second ring that we are seeing there.
Inside Orientale Basin, we see different mare patches.
There's definitely two of them that look like they have different colors.
It's almost like a horseshoe bottom of the inner part.
I'm sort of like a, like a fatter horseshoe there.
Um, and so that has sort of a gradational boundary as well as, um, and so I can see that that is sort of a darker gray, but then above that sort of filling in a little bit of that horseshoe, um, and going in around like one to two o'clock, um, it's a little bit lighter in color.
Um, you could see sort of the rubbliness, especially on the, on the ring features.
probably around like six, seven, eight o'clock.
And so that's, it's more definitely rubbly, or you can see that the brightness sort of going off of that material as well.
If I look to that annular ring, so it does look like that lipstick mark, but what's really interesting is that the top lip of the feature, the one closest to the mare, definitely has a darker, is darker in color than sort of the mirrored part on the lower lip of the feature.
Um, I can tell that there is sort of a gradational sort of boundary there.
Um, and it looks like it might be almost dispersing in a very lightweight on top of the rim.
Um, the ring feature that we see there, uh, you, it also does not look like the two parts of the annual ring are actually touching.
Um, sort of like they're separate just a little bit of where the crease of the lips would have been.
I'm sort of seeing this as it's approaching the limb and so I'm sort of seeing it on the edge a little bit.
So definitely I'm sort of seeing into the raised rim from about noon till 3 and then sort of flatter there below.
So I'm going to stop this one so I can get back on time.
### Transcript 008
All right, moving on.
Again, I'm in window two with the camera and the shroud.
Moving on to target four, Jackson Crater.
I'm looking at capturing this in the highest focal length.
So I've got the lens cranked over to 400.
First gonna start out with Jackson dead center at 400.
I cannot get the entire extent of the rays.
So I'm gonna zoom out, capture one that captures the visible part of the rays, which is almost two thirds of the moon at this point.
Still targeting the center of Jackson Crater.
And then go back to 400 and capture a mosaic that is at least 75% overlap across the top of Jackson.
Snaking west to east.
Gonna come back through Jackson.
And then a third pass just below Jackson.
I'm gonna go ahead and make a fourth pass from east to west.
Jackson now is not in the field of view, the crater proper, but the braid system from Jackson is.
And just to make sure that I continue to see rays extending to the south, so I'm going to make one last pass at 75% overlap, 400 zoom lens to make sure I capture the extent of any ray system coming out of Jackson.
Going to close out that photo, documentation of Jackson again from centering Jackson with the red square at the full extent out on the zoom and slowly zoom in, keeping Jackson centered all the way to the 400 millimeter portion of the lens.
Incredible crater, incredible rays.
very distinct in the camera lens.
Maybe with my eye I can actually distinguish some of those rays a little bit further than what I was seeing in the camera lens, just based on these illumination conditions.
And I really hope I captured Jackson appropriately in the camera because it's a beautiful sight to see via the naked eye.
equally as impressive through the 400-meter lens.
I wish I had a little bit more time to stare at it and pick up the nuance that the camera lens does afford me to look at, especially around the rim and some of the crater rings, or sorry, the crater ejecta rays to the south.
Really interested in that wedge that's between
uh 10 o'clock and two o'clock that doesn't look like there's any rays going to the to the north and west um kind of interesting just thought provoking as i kind of stare at it more through the camera lens took one last photo there i'm also gonna annotate that with the time stamp via the camera as soon as i close out this
audio file and it looks like, take one last check at the observation actions and looks like I'm good on Jackson.
Again, gonna capture a audio note in the camera and hopefully get you some of these photos down at the soonest possibility that we have.
### Transcript 009
Alright, so this is Marie.
I'm now on Jackson Crater.
I can really tell where Jackson Crater is.
It's super bright in my Lunar Targeting Package.
And it's ray system is very bright.
So I'm observing this with my eyes.
I don't have the camera right now.
I can see it sort of looking at about like the 10 o'clock and then about the distance of
oriental in from the western limb.
And so the inside of the crater is actually really bright, a super white, like dense, opaque white in color.
And as you go a little bit further out into the crater basin, you can actually, that color sort of dimishes, almost like a lighter gray halo surrounding it.
Um, I can see the rays of Jackson.
They can go all the way, almost over.
Um, not all the way to Muscovy and say, but they have about the, the size of Muscovy and say, um, Mari is about the distance between the edge of the, um, the Western most ray to the Muscovy and say.
Um, I can follow trace those rays across almost down, um, over towards, I think I can trace it almost over towards Ohm Crater there.
Um, so they reach over and those rays are crossing and then looking at the rays that go to the South.
I can see it go all the way into South Polacan basin.
Um, what's really interesting is that the, the ray system cuts and dissects SPA.
Um, but it looks like there are some areas that actually have a denser, um, sort of ray amount of rays.
So like the area between like one 32, probably like one 30 to like four ish is a very dense ray.
It almost looks like part of a bow tie sticking out there.
And then we have another really dense area.
pretty much from the 5 p.m. 5 o'clock to like the 7 30 ish range so that we can see there and then there is that one ray system that comes through those rays are super bright they look like they're on top of a lot of that other sort of darker gray material and looks like they're just sort of laying on top you can see the brightness of these rays they sort of
some of the other rays, especially the ones below in Crookes Crater.
Looks like they're definitely on top of the ones from Crookes Crater and they look a little bit brighter there.
And then also looks like there might be a secondary set ray that actually comes down as well.
I really can't pull out any structures because I'm looking at this like straight on with nadir and the edges of the rays, they
They are not like very sharp, but pretty sharp.
I get, I would call it pretty sharp between the rays and the background material that I'm able to see there.
And then the brightness of some of these smaller, brighter craters, they, they do still stand out on top of the ray system as well.
Let's see, this is really neat to see how bright this is.
I think the center of this crater is definitely one of the whitest spots that I can actually see on the moon right now, and then sort of fades outward from there.
### Transcript 010
All right, made a quick switch there, so I'm now looking out window number three.
I've got myself bungeed back down and got a clear view of the moon.
Not as square on as I was when I was taking pictures with the camera, but it definitely is not interfering at all with observations for this next target coming up, which is target five, Crookes Crater.
This is the first one of two of Crook's and
I'm immediately wishing I had the camera to actually try to find crooks.
I'm indexing now, taking a little bit of time to index up from Apollo to about 11 o'clock, 10 o'clock to find crooks.
The camera definitely does allow you to pick up some nuance that helps you navigate to the crater pretty quickly, but got my eyes on crooks.
and gonna take a look at the LTP to double check.
One thing that is definitely sticking out to me is the larger crater that is just at the three o'clock of Crook's or the two o'clock, definitely is not sticking out as much as I look out at the moon as it is in the 200 millimeter image on the LTP.
So it's a little hard to find Crook sitting on the edge of that crater.
but I definitely think I've been able to locate it just looking up from Apollo.
And right now it's hard to distinguish much topography given the illumination, but I am able to see a lot of color and albedo changes.
The texture looks pretty flat without the topography popping out at me, but the albedo around Crux is a lighter tone,
I'm almost seeing three different tones there, almost from a light gray to a mid gray to a darker gray as you get about two or three crooks diameters away from it.
It definitely doesn't have any dark areas like some of the craters to the south that almost have the mare patches in the bottom of them.
But the interior of crooks, if I stare at it really closely, might have like a little dark patch
at the three to four o'clock.
It's kind of like one of those mid-tone grays that I described earlier.
If I look at the RAID system of crooks, I can extend it out about two crook crater diameters away.
to the north and to the south at about five o'clock.
There's one distinct part of Crookes Crater Ray that looks distinct, almost like a finger out to the four o'clock that I don't see in the LTP.
It definitely is not as
as vibrant of albedos that you see in the LTP images as you do as I'm looking out the window at the moon around that crater.
It definitely is striking and very similar to the crater to the northeast of it.
And so those two pairing look pretty closely.
That crater is about halfway
towards Jackson.
So between Jackson Crooks and that crater that's between the two, I don't know the Name of, they all have about the similar albedo and similar overlapping rate pattern.
### Transcript 011
All right, starting target 23 with the camera and Jackson.
Captured a lot of Jackson when I was taking photos of the target 22 crater region area.
So I'm a little behind on the timeline with Jackson, but I think I'll make it up here just knowing that I captured a lot of Jackson in that last crater or that last camera sequence.
Gonna double check to make sure I get everything that you want.
So you want photographs of the center of the entire ray system at the highest focal length and multiple overlapping images as needed.
So I'm gonna go ahead and make some observations of Jackson when I do that.
But again, look at all the images that I took of target 21, or sorry, target 22,
because there's a lot of great photos of Jackson in there based on some of that image.
Specifically going to try to target on some of the rays of Jackson with the highest imaging.
So I'm going to take, I've got a series of images that zoomed in on Jackson from lowest to highest zoom.
and I'm gonna take from the highest of zoom and work out some of the ray systems to the south and north of Jackson to the furthest extent that I can view them, which is a long, long way.
So I just took a series of six photos to the south, starting at the center of Jackson and going south.
at the highest resolution, did the same, a series of three going to the north, and then a series of five going to that ray that is headed towards Muscovian's Basin.
And last thing I'm gonna do here with Jackson is capture it in a context photo.
I've got a couple of these now,
Make sure that I capture the whole upper northern two-thirds of the moon.
And an image that is well-centered and frames all of Jackson Rays and includes Muscovian's Basin.
Gonna take a few in a couple different orientations with the camera.
Captures the whole eastern limb.
and close out Jackson.
Man, it's a really unique crater that the camera allows you to see some of the grade system like your naked eye does not pick up.
The albedo doesn't seem to change as you get away from that central crater, but the central crater is a high albedo, definitely distinct and really dramatic through the camera lens.
And with that, I will close out target 23 Jackson Crater and it looks like moving on to Jules Verne next.
### Transcript 012
Okay, so this is Marie.
I now have the camera in my hand.
I'm getting situated, getting ready to look for Crookes Crater.
I'm now over in the other window and now I have the camera in my hand.
I'm testing.
It looks like that I can definitely focusing if I go the whole way zoomed in and can see the whole disc as I'm fully zoomed out.
So I'm starting with Crookes Crater with the, as I can see is a photometric target.
Um, and so has some intense looking at the albedo and texture and the theme for exterior, um, craters.
And so I'm going to try to look in and I can see where Crookes Crater is.
Um, it definitely has some bright gray systems as well.
I can see that it's about halfway between Apollo and Jackson, which does match where it is on my LTP.
And so I've got this, um, I'm able to get zoomed in on it there and get some images.
And my, the bracketing that was set up is still working great.
Um, so I'm zooming out a little bit, making sure that you can see the difference between
Apollo to Jackson to really get that in there when I zoom in a little bit more I can see some I can't really see any of those Terra structures that are discussed, but I can see the gradation of the of the ray system so I'm trying to follow these rays all the way back up to Jackson and If these rays are actually they're a lot more dense around the center that we see here I
And they don't look as streaky as like some of the rays around Jackson.
It's sort of like a, they're almost looks like flower petals.
They're much more, um, lighter in color and sort of condensed as well there.
And so it makes it a little bit more difficult to like really see that streakiness.
Um, like I said before, I really can't see much of the, the, the morphology or the boundaries actually look pretty gradational.
in the ray system as well.
I'm not able to see any of those terrace slopes that we talk about.
That center is a really, really bright albedo.
And it's very similar, not as bright as the one that you can see above in Jackson, but a little bit more similar to the one that is a little bit more northeast that I could probably see.
um, with my laryngeography review, if I felt like opening that right now.
Um, and so I'm looking, I'm supposed to really look and see the relationship, the rays on the material.
Um, it looks like Jackson's rays actually come across, might cross this one a little bit more, but the rays are more defined along the darker, the light gray background of the moon that I can see there.
but they really don't extend that far, sort of about the, it's like, you could look like the ray system sort of fits inside something like, like Muscoviente can sort of cover that whole ray system right there as well.
So I'm gonna save this one.
### Transcript 013
All right, just starting Target 6.
It looks like I'm a little behind on the timeline, so I'll make this one a little bit quicker.
And I've definitely zoomed in with my eye, sorry, on Target 6, the Bose And Bhabha Crater Region and Bubba Crater, just south of Apollo Basin.
The illumination down there is a little bit darker right now, so it's hard to pick out those two distinct craters that are next to each other.
Actually struggling with that a little bit.
I'm just indexing off of a dark patch that looks like to be the dark patch at the bottom of Bo's crater, if that's the one to my left or the west in the image.
And that's the only one that I'm really picking up on is that Bo's crater to the left, if Bose And Bhabha Crater Region's to the right.
And so again, just to make sure I'm clear there.
So at three o'clock is what I'm calling Bose And Bhabha Crater Region Crater in the image in the LDP.
The one at seven o'clock is what I'm calling Bose And Bhabha Crater Region.
And it's Bose And Bhabha Crater Region that is actually popping out just below Apollo Crater.
I don't see Bose And Bhabha Crater Region that distinct as what's captured in the LTP image.
I will say a little bit more words about the color.
So just below Bose And Bhabha Crater Region Crater, I do see a light patch that I don't see in any of the imagery on our PCDs.
So there's a totally distinct little light patch just below Bose And Bhabha Crater Region that is starting to really stick out to my eye as I continue to look out the window.
One thing I will note is looking back and forth between the window and the,
and the PCD, my eye does take a few minutes or a few seconds to adjust to pick up those subtle differences.
So I've been trying to concentrate by looking out the window, but also make sure that I get the observations and actions in mind before I start the video recording so I can allow my eyes to adjust without looking down at the LTP too often.
So just again, to focus on the color, albedo, and texture, I think I checked the box there.
Texture's really hard to pick out in these illumination conditions.
The only interior thing that I see is the bottom of bows, and that's the only reason that it's able to pick that out at all is a little bit of darker patch at the bottom of bows.
And the relationship between the two is kind of what I described.
I'm really having trouble seeing
above a crater compared to Bose And Bhabha Crater Region and just really interested in that little white patch that's below Bose And Bhabha Crater Region.
But nothing else really to add there.
Kind of hard in this illumination conditions to pick that up.
So that concludes target number six.
### Transcript 014
Okay, this is Maria.
I'm getting ready to go to my next target now.
We are now looking for Bo's and Bose And Bhabha Crater Region Crater.
So let me get that one highlighted here.
So I'm looking a little bit below.
I now have the camera, so I'm going to start at Apollo.
and work my way down from here.
Let me see if I can find where this is.
I'm looking for the double set, a little snowman as I've heard some people call it before.
It's really hard to find these ones down here, especially without this strong morphology.
I can see I'm fully zoomed in on Apollo, and so I'm just gonna start taking some images around.
Oop, I didn't collect my whole bracket, so I'm gonna restart that one.
Go down by Apollo and do like a tiny little mosaic here.
And so I feel like it's in there somewhere.
Let me see if I can really focus on getting to where that is.
So it's right down there near the bottom.
Definitely a little bit hard to find without the morphology that exists down here.
And so I really can't find exactly where these two craters are next to each other.
hard to compare them maybe that's them right there I really can't pick them out I think this might be it but I really can't exactly pick them out for a comparison between the two so they're sort of blending in with the
I really can't tell, does not, looks like the mare patch that I can sort of see is right above right above bows so I think I can find that mare patch, there it is and so yeah I really still am struggling but I think I'm right now centered on it and got a picture there
Um, but not very well defined.
I really can't find any of those central peaks, um, that I'm looking for inside of there or the terraced walls because the morphology isn't really coming out even when I'm zoomed all the way in.
Um, and so it's definitely a little bit hard to see in this lighting environment.
So, um, I'm going to go back and, um, finish up this recording and
it a little bit more on time here.
One of the things that is really interesting now that I'm just down here in SPA looking at this with the camera you can really start to see like how some of these craters look a little bit more depressed like a little bit how they don't look very strong but you can see some of that brightness those albedo differences
That's sort of more representative of the rooms of the creators than actually the creators themselves.
I'm going to look one more, once more again.
Oh, maybe that is it.
But it's definitely pretty difficult to find down there.
### Transcript 015
All right, I'm starting Sudman Crater, target number seven.
Taking a look now for locating it on the limb just above Oriental.
This one's definitely at the extent of the human eye.
I can't for say, using the LDP, flipping back and forth, that I for sure am seeing Sudman, target number seven.
There is a few white specks out there above Apollo Basin that I can try to index off of, but really hard to pick up Sudman for sure.
So let me just try to index again.
I see the Apollo ring.
I'm just not 100% sure as I zoom in on the LDP and flip my eyes back and forth.
Um, that I am indeed being able to pick up Sundman J Crater.
So, um, hopefully Marie's picking that up in the camera, um, at the highest focal length that she can.
Uh, there is a lot of albedo little specks of white and kind of a medium gray field out there.
Not a lot of topography is picking up in these illumination conditions, except for that rim of Apollo.
Um, and.
I'm sorry, Oriental.
So every time I said Apollo previously, it's Orientale Basin.
So just right above Orientale Basin, just that field of speckled white in that medium gray and just not able to pick out Sudman for sure.
The rays of one of the crater in there maybe are a little distinct.
So, but I don't think it's Sudman.
I think it's more towards Ohms Crater and
Yeah, with that I'm going to close out target number 7 and move to 8 just because I'm not 100% sure that I'm seeing Sudman.
### Transcript 016
All right, I'm starting my next recording.
And so we're looking for Sun Moon Jay crater.
So let me get that one up.
I'm looking for some good certain images and looking for additional images of the rays, if I can find those there.
And so I'm looking for, let me turn my labels back on.
Sun Moon Jay, it's gonna be up along the rim.
or the limb here a little bit more above oriental.
So let's see if I can find this.
So I can see where Ohm Crater is, and then I can see oriental.
And so I'm looking for partway in between there.
so sort of using those as my guide points okay so i found um i found oriental and looking so i'm looking using this more as a rim target limb target um and so i'm going to start taking some images along the rim here the limb so i'm gonna go from oriental all the way up
But looking here at the limb, I think what's really interesting is that the seam's pretty sharp.
I don't really see too much of a change, sort of any fuzziness along that limb.
Yeah, so this is definitely a harder one to see, but really looking at that limb,
like I said before it's very sharp and so I can still see it's definitely a bit difficult to see there where it is but um and I really can't see I do see a little bit of the ray system that I saw there so let me I can see some of those chains of craters coming down I think it's that
Above that.
I think it's right in here And so I can see a little bit of that ray system.
It's a very faint ray system from where I'm looking at right now it does show it's sort of like a sheet sort of just like powder on top of Obviously the regolith of the moon but much more of that sort of powdery extent
I know my picture isn't turning at the speed the movie is so I can't really use it as well to know what it is with representative on the moon but that's okay.
Definitely I can see some of those crater chains when I am fully zoomed in here.
Very tiny chains.
I thought I saw one.
There's one right there.
So I can see some of those crater streaks.
Those impact little lines there as well.
I'm going to clean this one up and get ready to go to the next one.
### Transcript 017
All right, starting target eight, the Mari, Injani, and Swirls, the first observation of it.
I'll spend a few minutes before, a few seconds at least, before I got on the voice recorder to make sure I've located it.
It's more tucked in towards the Terminator, at least the West Terminator than I was expecting compared to the LTP.
image indexing off Apollo, able to make my way across Labintz and then pick up where Mari Ingeni and swirls are.
But given the illumination conditions right now, can maybe see just a little bit of the lighter tone swirls at the bottom of Mari Ingeni, but it is at the extreme of the Terminator.
So picking up that albedo is a little difficult.
What I do see there is a lot of the topography, so I do see the rim of Mare Injani.
Looks like a very mountainous region, especially to the east of it.
Concentrating a little bit more on the texture, I see a lot of texture also trending northeast from there towards some of that crater complex that is up from Mare Injani.
And it definitely is unique in that area for some of that texture between Lubinsk and Mari-Injanai.
One quick note, picking up at Lubinsk, there's a very, very bright spot kind of at the seven to eight o'clock of Lubinsk, a very bright spot.
It's pretty small, but again, seven to eight,
a clock from Lubinsk that's only right near the crater rim, not too far from the crater rim of Lubinsk.
Back to Mare Ingenii, so the albedo, just a few more words on that.
Like I said, the swirls at the bottom of Mare Ingenii are possibly being picked up right now with the naked eye, but it's a little challenging.
given its location, hopefully as the moon rotates or as we pass by the moon, we'll start to pick up that a little bit more direct on.
And so hopefully the second observation of Mare Ingenii will be able to pick that up a little bit better, or hopefully the camera will.
The rest of Mare Ingenii is pretty dark.
The Mare patches at the bottom are definitely some of the darkest down in that area as you track over from
from Apollo.
It's kind of at the same color as that dark patch at the bottom of Apollo.
And so just for a comparison between the two, between Apollo, Mare Ingenii, and Labintz, I would still classify Apollo as the darkest, Mare Ingenii pretty close to Apollo, and Labintz, the darker patches, as a little bit lighter of the three.
A few more words on Mare Ingenii.
Just a really spectacular area down there that as I stare out at the moon a little bit without looking down at the PCD, my eye starts to pick up those subtleties that you start to see in the topography.
Overall, one of the things that I'm really interested in is about that bright spot right off of Lubinsk at the 7 to 8 o'clock.
So hopefully follow up with you guys on that during the debrief.
So I'm going to end target number eight, Mari Injani in Swirls here, and I get that recording saved out for you.
### Transcript 018
Okay, so I am now going back to my Lunar Targeting Package for number 9, Mari Inchnai.
This is also the first of two observations for this target.
And so I am looking at some of the color, albedo, and texture variations, working to get some images.
And interesting to sort of look for, I know there are some swirls in this target, so I'm going to be looking for those there.
And so once again, I have the camera in my hand.
I can see Mare Ingenii.
Let me see.
And so I can see the Apollo there.
And now there's Leibniz.
And so I can see Leibniz.
I can see Mare Ingenii there, so I've been able to locate it now.
And so I'm going to work on getting a full zoomed in image here.
Yeah, so it's definitely a little bit hard to actually see some of the swirls that are in there.
I can see some of the terraced edges.
It's because it's right there on the limb right now.
It's sort of difficult to see some of those swirls and so I'm trying to make some good observations so when I come back around the next time that I could see these a little bit better.
Let's see.
I'm looking through the camera to compare some of the size here.
It's about the same.
That sort of mare material is very similar too.
It's like the three feet across from Apollo to Leibniz.
It's about also the size of the crater in Leibniz.
I'm looking for some of that bright spot that you can sort of see.
So it looks like, oh, I think I can see a swirl.
Let me get a picture focused on that right now.
And so, you can tell that Mare Anginae right there.
It's sort of that part of the core, like if you think of it like an eyeball, you can sort of see some of those veininess.
It's sort of like the Mare Anginae is divided into like the two separate spots.
And so there's the top part and the bottom part.
I can see the bottom part has a little bit of swirls.
They fit about right in the square of my focus.
So I can see on the limb right there.
I think we're going to get a better view of these when we come back.
But really interested for what those are looking at right now.
But what I want to compare is the color.
The color that I am seeing inside of Mare Ingenii, it is a little bit darker than the Mare that you're seeing in Leibniz.
A little bit closer the color that you're seeing in the middle of Apollo, so I'm going to try to get an image with all of those in there right now.
And so we can see between the two.
Looking at the boundaries there.
heavy and mungy.
It's sort of, parts of it, like around the bottom of that top part of Mare Injani, it does sort of have that sharp, that sharp edge there.
And then along the top part, as you get towards the brighter, like those brighter craters, sort of above the Mare, that sort of is a much more of a gradational boundary that you can see there.
It looks like some of the ejecta from those tiny craters might come on top of the mare there as well.
It's really hard to see any structures in here.
Right now as I sort of, though it's a little bit on the limb, I'm really struggling to see any terraced features.
I can see the rim, like the inner peak ring, sort of coming up.
And it almost looks like the
It's like a breached wall.
You know, it looks like some of the Mario material sort of breached underneath, sort of that raised rim-like feature there.
Alright, I think that's going to be the end of this one.
### Transcript 019
Target 9, Labintz.
So started to really take a stare out of the window at Labintz to follow up on my comments that I just had on Target 8.
I think I concentrated equally on the Mare Ingenii and the swirls as well as Labintz during my Target 8 description.
But I'm going to stare out at Labintz a little bit longer now and see, let my eyes adjust to that target.
Again, just to reiterate what I said about
target nine, or sorry, target eight, about target nine.
I'm really interested in the dark, or sorry, the light, highly reflective spot that is at the seven to eight o'clock of Lubinsk.
It definitely stands out compared to anything I've seen as far as a bright spot.
I'm not sure if that's an illumination condition or more of a fresh crater.
but it's right just outside the crater rim of Lubinsk and definitely is unique in that area as far as a brighter spot.
I mentioned previously during my description of Target 8 that Lubinsk, the base of Lubinsk has kind of like a mid-tone dark gray compared to the basement of
Apollo and Mare Ingenii.
It's kind of a mid-tone compared to those darkest areas that you see.
And Labinsk doesn't have as much topography around the rim as what I saw and described as the topography around Mare Ingenii.
Just look down at the LTP to see if I could pick up the small little crater with the naked eye.
in Lubinsk that's kind of at the 10 o'clock.
So inside the floor of Lubinsk, there's like a raised rim at the highest zoom.
You're gonna especially see it.
And I cannot see that with the naked eye, no matter how long I stare at Lubinsk, hopefully the camera picks that up.
I can see the crater that's kind of like the,
If it's a Mickey Mouse on its side with Lubinsk with the ears headed to the east, I can pick up the crater that would be the up or the northernmost Mickey Mouse ear.
I can see that.
I cannot see the crater that has the distinct central peak in it in the highest zoom lens on the LDP.
I cannot pick up that crater.
Unless I really concentrate and allow my eyes to adjust out the window, I can just barely pick up that crater.
And now actually I'm starting to pick up the central peak of that crater.
But again, it's that adjustment of the eyes as you allow them to adjust out the window and to the illumination of the moon versus looking down at the PCD.
Nothing else dramatic stands out to me about Lubinsk.
Again, the topography is pretty muted in these illumination conditions.
The albedo I described and some of the surrounding terrain.
The only really unique feature is that bright toned features impact maybe to the seven or eight o'clock.
### Transcript 020
Alright, so I'm looking up so Stefan L Crater L. It's sort of like another thing up on the limb there Just try to see is my poster supposed to change Okay, I was like I was like this is Get a picture of this limb before it goes away and all of a sudden it's not there anymore
Let me show you what's happening up here in the cabin.
There it is.
So I'm looking for Stephan L. Yeah, so looking for Stephan up there.
It's sort of around the 2 o'clock on the rim.
I can still see that the edge is a little bit hazier.
And maybe we should do the changeover, because it looks like they need a little bit of assistance here in the reconfiguration time.
Yep.
### Transcript 021
This is a test.
Test, test, test.
I see my button oscillating.
That's good news.
Hopefully my PCD is in the right configuration.
### Transcript 022
Okay, this is Kelsey here.
It is 1546 and I'm just coming on to observe the moon here.
Excited to be here.
My first target here is taking a look at the entire moon and I have to say this isn't the objective of the task but I see the Earth as well and wow does it look beautiful.
So orient myself to the moon here is I think what I'm supposed to be doing.
I will say it is gorgeous and as the LTP says it is indeed not made of cheese.
I do see color variations starting to pop out you know I see at first glance I see the bright white
Craters really popping out, especially those beautiful rays extending across the entire face of the moon that I'm looking at.
I see what I believe to be South Poleaitken Basin-Aitken Crater Basin, which looks a little browner in color and inside SPA.
There seems to be dark mare patches, but not all the patches are the same color dark.
They really range in albedo across the spectrum of grays.
Muscoviens is right there popping out beautiful at about 10.30 PM on a clock, and I am facing my head where lunar north is to the top of my head right now.
I will say the standout features that I see I kind of already mentioned are
Muscovians, the South Poleaitken Basin-Aitken Crater Basin, and just the sheer variety of albedo you see across the surface.
I'm going to go into my geography review tab here.
just take a look.
And what I'm really seeing is Jackson and the rays of Jackson extending beautifully over this far side view.
I am also seeing crater rays extend in places all the way down into the South Pelican Basin and across the South Pelican Basin.
I see Aiken popping out to the sort of upper left, maybe, again, like 1030 if the clock is SPA and I am pointed to the north.
And it really pops out beautifully.
And I actually see some albedo, some bright white material that's extending out to sort of the, again, the southwest of Aiken crater.
Again, my orientation is that I am facing toward the lunar north pole.
Let's see, what else did you want me to cover in this description?
Comparison of features across the globe.
I definitely see what you guys are talking about, about illumination angle and what you can tease out on the surface of the moon.
For example, sort of right in the middle of my view, I can just really see a ton of albedo variation from those craters and the crater rays.
But then as you look over sort of to the, again, Kelsey left side,
You see a lot more topography and morphology start to pop out.
You see crater rims really start distinctly over on the limb there.
And there's some beautiful views that I'm getting both of the albedo in the middle and the topography over on the left.
Let's see.
Starting to see Zolkowski crater pop out on the left here.
Looking forward to getting a view of that later.
I'll leave it here for now and go on to the next target.
### Transcript 023
All right, this is Angela and I am starting target 10, two of three, which is the Whole Moon.
I have the camera and so I'm going to start my north to south sneak pattern.
Mosaic was 50% image overlap.
I switched the camera to my SD card, which I can't remember the Name, number of it, but I'm sure it's written somewhere.
Okay.
And you want me to be at mid focal length.
So standby.
All right.
I'm around, uh, I'm just going to go up to 300.
Uh, no, 200 seems to be perfectly adequate.
All right.
Starting from the north and starting my snake now.
Yeah, I'm sitting upright at the moment, so the north to south snake should look pretty straight.
So as I'm snaking, I can really tell
the stark differences in albedo between the rays.
I think of Jackson and of Crooks overlapping kind of the mar beneath.
It's really quite stunning.
Alright, so, kind of just snaked over Apollo's basin.
And now I'm right about around Crook's.
Passing over Jackson.
It's really difficult to keep the camera
steady.
My body is very tense so I can keep it still and get that 50% overlap that you guys are looking for.
I'm on my last snake now.
I realize I probably made some pretty tightly packed together snakes, but I think you'd enjoy that.
Okay, now I'm just gonna kind of look through my camera and give you some general impressions, which is, wow, yeah, the morphology on the Terminator is just really, stands out a lot more in my zoomed camera.
General impressions, it's just
that some of these colors are really subtle.
There's a little bit of like an orange tone that I'm seeing like orangish red in Muscovy Ents that's standing out.
Same with the
same in Apollo Basin.
But yeah, I think the thing that kind of dominates the landscape right now is just the craters of Jackson.
They have just, they reach not quite Moskowience to the west.
They reach
definitely up until crooks and they're just big and bright and beautiful I'm sure there'll be more to come oh I see Earth let me yeah as I'm as I'm still on this Whole Moon I almost almost missed it
but for the first time I can see Earth and I'm gonna take some shots of it even though it's not in our plan.
It's just so beautiful.
Hey, it's nice to see you all the way over there.
And those are pictures of the screen and not the poster board.
Alright, I'll end it there and pick up at Bavilov.
### Transcript 024
Okay so I'm going back to my lunar targeting package to finish up my last one before we switch over which is Leibniz crater and so I this is still Marie I can still have the um the camera in my hand
I'm zooming in to do that.
I got some good pictures of this last time, I think with, um, in between the Marianginae and Apollo before, but I'm going to really focus on observations of Leibniz this time.
And so what I can see in here is there is that brighter circular feature in the middle and sort of like the halo circle on top.
And that's sort of in this, you can see that little raised rim in our lunar targeting packages.
And so I'm going to be focusing on seeing if I can see the swirls in here and describe them as well.
And so I'm now centered on the target.
I can look and sort of see the sort of swirly spot in the middle.
It's definitely, it's definitely brighter than the surroundings, but it's definitely still hard to piece out.
Um, so it's sort of like, it's not super sharp and you gotta look at it for a while to really see if I can see those, um, pieces there.
It's almost a little streaky, um, which is interesting to me.
I'm looking at the wall of the coder.
You can tell it's sort of like got a sharper wall there.
I'm just going to take a couple of photos.
I can see that one rim that's in there, that red circular, is really well preserved.
It's just like a perfect little halo.
Crater very circular and it's like uniform the entire way around interesting I'm comparing that Crater rim that's around 11 to like the one that's around like 9 839 ish so that one is a little bit of a brighter.
It doesn't look as well preserved
It's brighter, but it doesn't look as like as strong of a uniform rim as the higher one up here There's definitely some craters around here that It's hard to tell that sort of one of those that's about four o'clock looks like it is superimposed on top of Leibniz and then we have the And then we have that bright
that bright crater ejecta exactly probably around the nine o'clock area that we can see there so it's definitely a little bit difficult to see in there looking to see if I see any textures inside that mare does look pretty smooth we see a little bit those white streaks sort of going
within there, but it's almost like little wispies.
So we see that circular center wispy, but it almost looks like I could potentially see one that's sort of like radiating from it as a slight wispy as well.
And then the crater rim sort of degrades and becomes part, the whole Leibniz rim itself is not as sharp as what we have elsewhere.
It's really hard to pick up on a lot of this morphology there, so really
using the albedo here.
And so the albedo that I can see, um, it's similar to the mare, um, of the crater below it.
Definitely the, the, from about noon to like two is a little bit darker of what's in there of that C shape.
Um, and from about 11 down to like seven ish, it's a little bit of a lighter, but you really don't have a distinct motion moment in between them where you see those boundaries crossing.
So I'm going to, I'm really excited to have finished this first set of observations for you all and can't wait to keep looking at the moon and get back to it on the other side.
### Transcript 025
All right, Houston, Angela here.
I am, I was troubleshooting Kelsey's PCDs, so I definitely missed Babaloff.
Trying to get quickly back into Earthset, because I see it right now.
So let me get some pictures of Earthset.
And I'm taking them of the screen.
Yeah, okay, as I am,
Looking closer, you want me to focus on an Earth atmosphere.
I'm not seeing, it just looks like a perfect, clear-boundaried marble.
Oh, yeah, maybe I'm seeing a little bit of blue reflection coming from, only I can totally see it when I'm zoomed in.
but perhaps a little bit of this kind of neon, maybe not neon, like a, how do I describe that?
Just like a true blue.
And I'm checking my camera viewfinder to make sure that that color comes through, but I'm definitely seeing some
blue.
This is hard.
In terms of atmospheric patterns, I see some swirling of moons.
The bright white of Antarctica is much of a truer white than the gray
of the of the highlands and so the the clouds and those are polar ice caps are a great comparison for a true white because now that I'm looking at those in comparison to the highlands especially when I'm kind of zooming out a little bit we'll call it the thing that's the the truest color is actually the
the dead center of Crooks is probably what I'm seeing as like the truest white when I compare it to the clouds on the Earth.
It's sad to see the Earthset behind the moon, but I know I'll see it on the other side.
I got some pictures
I'm just gonna make sure I get some of the all zoomed angles.
It's really great to have it have the lens zoomed in as I can watch it go but also kind of step back and see
with it, with my naked eye.
And this is the moment where the moon fully disappears.
That was a beautiful, beautiful thing that I just got to witness.
Okay.
### Transcript 026
Okay, starting a new recording.
I'm glad I was able to capture Earthset.
Let me actually make sure I can tag that picture.
This is me tagging this picture.
Okay.
Uh, successfully did that.
Sorry.
This, that was information from Earthset and not my current target, which is target 13.
Korolev Basin Basin.
So let me get oriented on the objectives for Korolev Basin.
Yeah, it's a little bit difficult to tell because Okay, I'm in my lunar geography review just to help get the colors back Yeah, definitely
I see Crooks and I see Jackson and Korolev Basin is right underneath the high albedo crater.
Okay, I think I've oriented myself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Just making sure I'm taking pictures of the right thing, but okay.
Understood.
Feedback received.
Let me go get some shots of Korolev Basin.
It's actually easier to find Korolev Basin through my camera now that I can zoom in, so I probably should have done that earlier.
Alright, so yeah, because even up here, even if I'm not 100% sure,
that I'm looking at it, I will 100% get the photo.
Because in my highest zoom length, there's a lot of overlap in this area.
So I'm going to make sure I have good coverage of this zoom.
OK, so trying to focus.
in and let me figure out what you still want.
Okay, let me look at some of this.
The topography, which it's actually just it's just not that obvious, honestly.
I wish it stood out a little bit more, but it's not.
Um, I definitely have pictures of Korolev Basin in my viewfinder, um, but I'm just really not seeing any, um, of these kind of cryptomare, um, versus just like any of these, these textures that you're, um, kind of indicating on the, on the LTP.
I'm honestly still not 100% confident that I'm observing the specific crater.
It's just a little bit difficult to tell.
But I can promise you that I have several overlapping pictures of this area.
But in terms of description, even my zoom lens of my naked eye, there's not great topography that are showing up.
So with that, let me continue to move on.
### Transcript 027
Okay, Kelsey is back with you here.
My PCD just froze up on me, so I had to hard reset the PCD.
And because of that, I missed several targets.
I missed Babaloff, and unfortunately I did miss Earthset.
But here I am at Korolev Basin Basin.
I will say at first glance, it is very hard to see Korolev Basin with the current view that I have.
I can see Favaloff, which is of course one of the targets that I missed, but Korolev Basin is nearly impossible to detect.
I'm going to take a minute and try to get oriented here, especially since I just kind of got out of observations to try to troubleshoot the PCD.
You know, I do see
understand I'm looking for kind of a smoother spot that's looks to be younger because it has fewer craters but at the current view right here all I'm really seeing I don't really see topography due to the the illumination angle right now and I'm looking and you know I see go back to my geography review here
I'm trying to switch around my views to see if there's anything I can kind of do here.
Figure that out.
I think I can see Crooks beautifully, and I understand that Korolev Basin should be to the upper right of it, but it is swamped out by the sort of really bright albedo colors of a crater that's unlabeled in the geography review.
That's sort of just to the upper left of Korolev Basin by upper left.
I am still oriented in the window such that I am My head is facing lunar north.
So it's just to to sort of the upper left left of Korolev Basin So, let me see here
It's nearly impossible to identify any topography.
All I see is sort of a white albedo patch in the area where I think Korolev Basin should be.
It's not as bright white as the two craters on either side of it.
It sort of just appears to be, you know, honestly, if you would have asked me to pick an area of the moon in my naked eye view right now, it's sort of the least distinct feature
least distinct part of the moon that there is in my current view.
So I'll take a look here and see if there's anything I can give you about your observation actions.
But honestly, I can't really see any of the things that you're asking me to look out here with Korolev Basin.
All right, Kelsey out and I'll move on to the next target.
### Transcript 028
Angela here.
OK, I am back with you and I see my next target is 14 Oppenheimer Basin.
It's a high priority, so let me get great image coverage of it because I have the camera at the moment.
Right, I'm gonna.
Look at.
Apollo.
And then I'm going to zoom in and make sure that I can get Alpenheuer, which is right next to Apollo.
Yep, just double checking my LTP that it is the cluster of three.
Well, actually, what's obvious to me is that it kind of looks like three Mari patches within this
within this greater crater.
So I'll just make sure I get focus on some of the low points and the higher points so hopefully you can get that good mosaic of it.
I will make sure to get Apollo and Oppenheimer Basin in one single frame.
I just saw that target.
Yeah, let me try to compare these two.
There's a lot more diffuse boundaries in the Oppenheimer Basin Mare patches than the Apollo Mare patches.
They're much more distinct and sharp.
in Apollo versus Oppenheimer Basin, which is, again, that diffuse type of boundary.
I'm also here.
If I get at a better angle, maybe I can see this.
So now I'm kind of clocked a little bit.
differently, so if you see that change in angle, that's why.
I'm just trying to focus on the crater ray that's coming from Crook's that's separating these two craters.
Let me zoom out a little bit just to make sure I get Crook's in the photo, but then I will just like kind of slowly zoom in and then I'm at my max zoom now focusing on that.
crater ray, which is almost at the boundary of Apollo and Oppenheimer Basin.
In general, for the color tones and differences between Oppenheimer Basin and Apollo Basin, I would say Oppenheimer Basin has darker, deeper tones than Apollo.
The deepest of the tones is of the three kind of dark patches that are within Oppenheimer Basin.
The top one is the darkest.
Let me just make sure I'm on timeline still.
Okay, I am.
Okay, I'm gonna leave it there and take a few more pictures.
### Transcript 029
Okay, Kelsey back with you.
It's 1607 here.
And my next target is a high priority target.
It is Oppenheimer Basin Basin.
Let's see what I'm looking for here.
I'll orient myself.
Let's see, I see again Aiken Crater's been such a helpful guidepost for me.
So I'm coming down to make sure I hit it.
And wow, this one's a little hard to see as well.
I do see Apollo Basin and it almost seems like Oppenheimer Basin is obscured.
Let's see here by a, let's see, by a bright crater ray that's coming down from the direction of Crookes Crater.
I see in the geography review Oppenheimer Basin should be just to the left.
of that beautiful bright crater ray from Crooks that is totally dominating my field of view here.
And I have to say, this is a challenging one to be able to identify, but I know how important it is to you guys.
So I'll give it my best shot here.
Looking at Oppenheimer Basin, to me with the naked eye, it looks like just an area where there's several smaller craters that are sort of nearby to each other.
The smallest of which in my lunar targeting plan in the screenshot there, I see the tiniest, darkest crater in the LTP is also the darkest feature to my naked eye as well.
It's hard for me to see morphology, honestly,
because of the illumination angle, it's really the albedo that's popping out to me more than anything.
So as for shape and size, it's a challenge to sort of pick that out.
But I guess as I'm looking at it longer, I'm starting to see, I'm tilting my head to the right and I sort of start to see almost like a little face that's made by just eyes and a nose, a little face of three darker mare patches
that are in close proximity to one another.
As for the sense of scale, let me look at my scale bar here on the targeting plan, and it looks like the darkest of those patches is probably, oh, I don't know, 40 to 50 kilometers across.
As for what I'm supposed to be looking at, which is basin structures in the fractured floor, I mean, I guess the only insight I can provide in terms of the question about pyroplastics is that
darkest patch that's kind of like in in the 10 o'clock area if Oppenheimer Basin Basin were a clock with north as 12 o'clock is that that is more irregular.
It appears to be not totally infilling an impact crater but rather its own unique patch with sort of rougher non-circular edges to it.
I see here that I'm supposed to compare
this to looking at similar deposits with Apollo which is I know the next target but I'll just say while I'm giving this target here that the darker patch in Apollo Basin is similarly irregularly shaped and so it again appears like perhaps similar processes formed them or at least that that's an interpretation but they do look similarly irregular.
I will say
The picture in the LTP is a little misleading because it makes it look like that, again, that crater at like 10 o'clock, if Oppenheimer Basin were a clock, is much more circular and distinct than what I'm actually able to see with my naked eye here.
So the best I can really provide to you is a look at color and sort of distinctness of the boundary of the feature.
Hard for me to tell spatially, which is younger or older,
If you had to make me guess, I'd say that it appears to be sitting on top of a lot of surrounding features in the area.
And I'll see if I can make some annotations in the OneNote, because I know how important this target is to you guys.
### Transcript 030
All right, I'm starting this next target a little bit later because I took some time to go into the OneNote and sketch something in Oppenheimer Basin, although to be honest, I'm not totally sure how useful it was.
But now I see my next target is the Apollo Basin.
I know I talked a little bit about that in the Oppenheimer Basin description.
Unlike some of the other targets in sort of my block of targets here,
Apollo Basin, I have no trouble identifying.
It is, you know, of course, near the edge of the South Poleaitken Basin-Aitken Crater Basin.
I can see it again in my current view, which is again, I'm pointed toward lunar north.
I see it marked especially by its sort of irregularly shaped dark patch in the middle of it, which I believe to be mare.
It's a little bit harder for me to pick out the ring structures that you guys are asking me to look at.
Because again, I just really am not seeing much topography in this naked eye view on this sort of half of the moon right now.
But I do see sort of the center mare patch.
And I also see sort of that, I don't know, horizontal to my current view mare patch.
That horizontal Mari patch is probably 125 kilometers long, and maybe again using the scale bar on the LTP, like 25 kilometers, you know, in height, so to speak, from where I'm oriented right now.
three little fingers coming out to the bottom left at about seven o'clock from the bottom left of that dark linear mare patch.
They look like fingers to my naked eye.
Looking at the picture in the LTP, I can see that they appear to be bounded by some sort of topography there in the rim, but I don't see that topography from my view.
All I see is those little fingers stretching down.
There's also a third Mari patch that's much smaller and narrower, sort of oriented vertically.
That's in relationship to the dark Mari patch in the middle.
It's it's out to the left toward the sort of Western Rim Western from my current frame of reference view toward Oppenheimer Basin Basin.
And again, it's it's less like dark gray.
It's a lighter gray and it's also more diffuse.
All three Mari patches thinking about sort of
geologic relationships here.
With the naked eye, I don't see a ton of craters in those mare patches, suggesting to me that it might be younger than a lot of other features in this area.
In comparison to the Oppenheimer Basin volcanic deposits that you asked me to observe earlier, those two larger mare patches in Apollo are probably
darker, darker gray in color than the mare patch in Oppenheimer Basin Basin.
I don't see many structures or slopes or textures.
Frankly, all I really see is color and albedo in this target.
### Transcript 031
All right, Angela, back with you, starting on Target 15, Apollo Basin.
Now, I talked a little bit about Apollo when I was describing Oppenheimer Basin, and I'm gonna continue to do so.
I'm gonna make sure I have some good full view pictures.
Body position wise, I am clocked slightly.
I'd be like 90 degrees to the right.
where the zero is the top upright windows of Orion.
So just took a few pictures focused on the fullest zoom out and now I'm kind of clocking in focusing on the margins between Apollo Basin and Oppenheimer Basin
And now I'm going to take a few pictures focused just directly on Apollo Basin, because that is the target I want to focus on.
Oh, this is fun to look at.
It's actually kind of hard to stabilize.
So I'm just going to not.
I'm just going to put my feet up to help stabilize myself.
As I'm zoomed in on Apollo Basin,
Um, it's really cool to see the, um, the bright mare crater that's above, if you call it like the eye, the right eye above that.
And it's got some really good pictures of just making sure.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
They, they, they come through in the pictures of the crater, um, the light tone crater ray, um, kind of over top of that.
of that dark mare, so I'm glad that that comes through.
I will focus on the mare in the center and the ring structures.
Okay, yeah.
I will focus on that right now.
It's interesting that it seems like that mare in the center is actually to the right, but it is true now that I'm
of looking at my naked eye and know that in the topography that mare is not the right but it's actually in the center.
I'm going to take a few more pictures focusing on that ring to the north because it's actually not that obvious.
I was expecting that topography to stand out a little bit more
But it doesn't.
So I've taken a few photos focused on the center but also did a few around the edges of that crater.
So as I'm just continuing to zoom in and I focus on that center mare, there's definitely
like a another ring that's to the to the right of the center more.
And I think that, yeah, that shows up in the LTP topography as well.
Let's see texture wise.
The base of this crater looks quite smooth.
Oppenheyer next to it looks more rough.
So I would say Apollo Basin is the smoother one.
And again, the mare has very sharp boundaries that are not diffuse.
Let's say I got a little distracted by the beauty that is Apollo Basin.
So let me double check.
I think I'm right on time.
Oh, all right, I'll keep recording for a second.
All right, Kelsey, you want this camera?
Here, switch SD card.
All right, let me give you my SD card.
And this way, I can actually record what SD card I have, which is SD card 1026.
Slot 1.
Huh?
Nope.
I don't know if it matters.
All right.
I don't know what to do with this, but this seems important.
Oi, oi.
Could you put that in the Ziploc?
Now I guess I'll pause my recording.
Oh, do you need to be in this window?
I sure do.
Window two.
She's a beauty.
She is a beauty.
I've found that putting your feet on here helps stabilize the shifting of the chair.
### Transcript 032
Alright, Kelsey back with you here.
I have now swapped windows with Angela and now I have the camera.
I have put my SD card, my own SD card into the camera.
I forgot to look at the number of that so I'll report that at the end of my shift here.
And I'm moving on to my next target which is a
high priority target.
It's the South Polar region, which is of course super exciting for future surface missions.
And I'll just take a minute to kind of get oriented with what I'm seeing here.
Let me just go ahead and zoom in.
Oh, wow.
Having the camera is such a different view.
It's gorgeous.
Okay, I've got some pictures here and zooming in.
I see the South Poleaitken Basin-Aitken Crater Basin with that, I don't know, it really kind of looks right now in my view almost smoother than, it does look a bit smoother than the rest of the moon, which is interesting because I know it's much older.
Let me see, I'm zooming in on the targets I just described before I had the camera, Oppenheimer Basin and Apollo, and all those mare patches pop out even more now, making me think that the descriptions I gave to you of those targets were not nearly as useful as the descriptions looking through this viewfinder here.
Those albedo differences pop out so much better, and I can even start to see some of the topography that I was lacking with the naked eye view.
I know my near-term focus is on Oppenheimer Basin and Apollo because I just described it, but I'll expand my focus.
Let's see what I'm supposed to be looking for on the LTP here.
Topography along the lunar horizon and illuminated rim of Schrodinger.
Oh gosh, it's hard to see Schrodinger.
Yeah, it's really hard to pick out Schrodinger.
I don't really think I can see it in this view.
But I will take a look at the topography along the horizon.
Let me see here.
Yeah, I'm starting to see more topography pop out, certainly along that horizon.
Again, the crater rims stand out so beautifully.
I'm going to zoom in here and take a picture.
And I'm just seeing dark mare patches, both circular and less circular in nature, pop out across the South Polar region.
I'm going to take a few pictures highlighting the diversity of the mare patches that I see in the South Polar region.
Those images just captured some bright white, very tiny, high, high, high albedo
features that might indicate that they're young, fresh impact craters, which is, I know, of interest to the science team.
Oh, look right here.
That image I just took, I think, captured a crater that has significant diversity of mare in it.
There's that beautiful Albedo ray from Crooks coming down in the middle of Apollo and Oppenheimer Basin.
I'll zoom in on the sort of extent of it down to the bottom.
Let me see what else I'm supposed to be.
I'm supposed to be taking a mosaic of the entire illuminated region, north-south snake pattern.
All right, and that looks like my...
I'll take a minute and just get oriented.
It's such a better view with this viewfinder.
You can pick out so much more detail.
I'm looking at it through the viewfinder.
Alright, so now I'm going to take my mosaic.
Let's see, I'm going to start here.
And 50% overlap north-south.
Still taking my mosaic here.
Okay, I'm probably taking way more images here than is warranted, but hey, it's the South Poleaitken Basin, it's exciting stuff.
All right, so I'm gonna go in, I think this is my last picture of this, so I'm gonna go in and add the WAV file, but I'll go ahead and stop the recording.
### Transcript 033
Hey, Angela, back with you.
I am looking at high priority target 16 South Poleaitken Basin Region, one of two.
I don't have the camera anymore, so I will probably take some annotations now that I have my hand available.
It was very difficult to do annotations with the camera.
It's South Poleaitken Basin Region zoning in.
Yeah, I'm looking at it.
I wish I had the camera so I could see a little bit more detail.
So let's see.
I guess I can see a little bit of topography on the horizon.
It's not quite right dead south,
pole but there's some topography differences if I look to the east.
I see a little bit more ruggedness in the in the perimeter and then a little bit more ruggedness in the boundary just when I'm looking west just because of the Terminator shadow.
Okay, let me try and locate Schrodinger.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I see.
So that area where there's some topography differences in the perimeter on the western, the west of the South Poleaitken Basin is closer to the Schrodinger Basin zone.
Actually,
Now I'm trying to convince myself that I'm not seeing more of Schrodinger than what the picture in my LTP is showing.
Yeah, sorry, I'm just trying to take it in and identify if I can tell Schrodinger.
I'm not sure if I can but and it's a little bit cut off in my video so I can't see the exact tip but I was I was taking pictures of the screen
there they didn't look good but if you wanted Earthset pictures I needed to take picture of the screen yeah it's interesting to think about the like
us landing on the South Poleaitken Basin, but honestly, with my naked eye, I'm not entirely sure if there's much more I can say.
### Transcript 034
Okay, Kelsey here.
Target 17, Dewar Crater Region Crater Region.
I will say that my voice recorder app is misbehaving.
Last time only a power cycle fixed it, but if I power cycle, I will risk losing target 18, which is high priority.
So I am going to hope that my experience last time wins out and the recordings are still there, even if I can't hear them back.
So here I am, Dewar Crater Region is the next,
target I have.
Let's see on the LTP, it's kind of like on a line between Aitken Crater Crater and Muscovy End.
So I'm gonna follow it up.
Yep, I think I see it there.
So let me see, go to the 400 millimeter.
What am I looking for?
Low albedo anomaly, maybe cryptomare.
Okay, so let me see here.
All right, so in the window, I am actually, my head is pointing toward sort of the right east side again.
I understand it's the western limb, but it's to my east.
And so the camera is pointed 90 degrees from the last pictures I took.
I'm going to zoom in here.
Do a regional, yeah, really pops out beautifully in the zoom.
OK, going all the way to 400 here.
And in that zoom lens, I can really see there's a diffuse patch of that darker material.
Here, I'll get a picture of it.
I'll get a picture of it with some context here.
And let me see.
Yeah, so it looks, it is diffuse, and it's especially diffuse as you move out from it.
It's almost like several layers of diffusivity where it's darker in the middle,
and then slightly less dark, but still darker than the surrounding terrain coming out.
I think there are fewer craters on it than the surrounding area, suggesting, well, that doesn't make sense if it's Cryptomare, but I'm telling you, I don't really see a higher density of craters.
It's just kind of the same as the surrounding terrain.
So the only indication of anything really is that albedo color.
I don't even really see
relationship between the dark albedo and topography here.
Take a nice picture and I'll move on to the next high priority target.
### Transcript 035
All right, Angela, back with you.
I am starting Dewar Crater Region Crater Region.
I don't have the camera.
I'm looking with my eyes.
All right, let me try to identify Dewar Crater Region Region.
It's a little bit
hard because the base map in my LTP isn't like, is more topography based versus the albedo color.
Ah, OK. Yep, I got it.
I see it now.
Oh, if I look away, I almost lose it for a second.
But I can.
No, I lost it again.
No, I got it again.
OK. All right, all right, all right.
We're back.
I can see Dewar Crater Region.
um what i'm really focusing on is the sharp perfect looking crater um fresh looking oh just kidding i lost it again sorry guys i'm really having a hard time trying to get
Doer It's almost like I really wish I had a camera to zoom in I definitely
I mean I can see I'm poking back to my lunar geography guide because the image there is a little bit better for me no I don't know what that Name is it's just I'm using the crater within a crater that's butting against another crater that's around the same diameter and then trying to look straight up from that
to identify Dewar Crater Region?
Okay, I think it's a darker mare patch in this area.
Okay, now I am confident I am looking at Dewar Crater Region.
The way I'm clocking it is the two craters that are around the same diameter and looking straight up at the darker region and then below this kind of light, very light and bright crater
above it, so I'm very confident I'm looking at it right now.
Again, this mare in Dewar Crater Region is very diffuse and it's also lighter in tone.
It's not as obvious as the rest of them, especially Aiken is pretty dark and so is Moskavians, but I'd say Dewar Crater Region is
Maybe what I'm looking at, maybe some of the lighter, lightest toned mare, if that makes sense.
Um, again, very diffuse, um, the extent of it.
Actually, maybe I can take a screenshot cause I feel like the image that I'm looking at is not accurately cubbying the full extent.
So standby as I take a tour region.
Oh yeah.
I can just annotate directly in to here in the LTP.
Okay, so I'm just drawing what I'm seeing as the boundary of this mare.
And then there seems to be another, maybe a slightly different tone of mare that's in an irregular shape around.
I drew the annotation.
Hopefully, I just want to show that there's a little bit of a boundary in the tones of the Mari in CoreLab.
But again, these are, in general, pretty diffuse boundaries, but there is a slight tonal difference.
So I wouldn't take that line as super sharp, but I can see a distinction in those shapes.
### Transcript 036
All right, coming up on my next, and I believe last target before the swap, wow, that time flew by, it's Tsiolkovsky Crater here and the Terminator.
So let's go in here and see that I'm looking for Tsiolkovsky, which is right along the Terminator.
I actually can see it fairly decently popping out along the Terminator now.
And I can see that the central peak pops up in the middle.
Let me see if I can take a picture of that.
Let's see.
Same orientation as the last target.
So my head is pointing sort of toward the right here.
I'm going to take one all the way at 180.
And I'm going to zoom in to 400 here.
I will say, a couple times the cameras bumped the microphone, so I don't know how well that's going to impact audio quality.
But man, that central peak of Silkoski is beauty.
I can see why it's Reed's favorite crater.
Let's see.
Mosaic of Hull Terminator.
Okay, let's see here.
Highest focal length for individual features.
Oh boy, that's gonna be a lot of images.
As I'm saying this, I think that that South Polar Region mosaic wasn't necessarily all the way zoomed in, so I apologize for that.
All right, I got that mosaic.
And now I'm looking at, for Tsiolkovsky, color-albedo texture variations, crater interior and exterior.
Let's see here.
So zooming in here, I do see, again, the crater, the inside of the crater is fully dark because it's in shadow, but you can see the central peak popping out, and it's nice and bright and white.
in the middle there, right in the middle of Tsiolkovsky's o'clock.
I can't tell, but it seems like in the sort of 10 to 11 p.m. if Tsiolkovsky was o'clock.
No, sorry, it's about nine o'clock if Tsiolkovsky was o'clock from my current body orientation.
There seems to be a light albedo patch.
I can't tell though if it's just because it's coming into the sun or not.
I'm gonna take a picture of it, see what you guys make of it.
All right.
### Transcript 037
Angela with you.
I got so distracted by my drawing at Dewar Crater Region Crater.
I didn't realize I had a high priority target up next.
So I think I'm a little bit, I'm definitely behind in my Sikofsky observations.
So apologies about that, but I hope you'll like that, that drawing.
Okay, I am,
trying to find Sikovsky yeah because I'm a little bit late to this observation I pretty much see the entire outline of Sikovsky and then the so like the rim of the west rim of Sikovsky is illuminated and the central peak is illuminated
That's the view I'm seeing right now.
So I missed the initial where it was just behind the Terminator because it looks fully outside of the Terminator.
I think the only, oh, and now that I'm looking at it, there's a little bit more of the basin of the crater that's illuminated.
So to the north of the central peak, there is a slight color that comes through.
I will screenshot it and, oh, wait, actually it's already in my, I keep forgetting that it's already in my LTP.
Are we taking a break?
Is it time?
### Transcript 038
All right, we're back with you in window three.
We just did a successful switch over to have a little chat with the outgoing shift, and they're going to send up a sign set up here in a little bit.
But I'm going to start with the exosphere dust get ahead target, target delta, because I see a little bit of a phenomena that's happening right on the Terminator, just proximal to
Muscovy Ents.
So I'm going to go ahead and try to describe that while I draw a little diagram of that area.
So I'm looking at Muscovy Ents and if I go 10 o'clock towards the limb, the dark limb from there, I'm seeing a little bit of color change along that horizon.
It's like a slight glare, but I could convince myself that it's maybe a little bit of
phenomena of dust lofting or some kind of exospheric phenomena that my eye is picking up only in that area.
I've looked along the entire Terminator from north to south, and that's the only area that I see that popping out at me.
So I'm going to go ahead and end this audio for that delta exosphere get ahead target and try to get some of that annotated in the OneNote.
### Transcript 039
Alright, it is Marie.
I just got back into the seat.
I'm going to try to look along the exosphere.
Just sort of look and see if I can see any light coming up.
So I have the camera in window 3 and window 2.
The one without the cab cam.
The one where I should be with my camera.
So I'm going to start looking along the limbs here.
I think Earth is going to be coming from.
Looking to see if I can... oh my camera isn't on.
My camera is on.
We're still doing a little picture wise.
We got our new card inside.
That is card 1029 is in my slot 1.
so i can actually now getting organized here so i'm going to be looking along the the rim and the exosphere trying to look and see if i can see any evidence i don't really see too much right now this looks a little bit fuzzy but it's it is hard because we know the Earth will be coming up from behind
an area that is in darkness so it's still really hard but if I look at the disappearing limb taking some images as I look at that as well just going up and down oh I could see a little spot of something off in the distance there and that's very interesting a little white spot off of the limb
I'm not really sure what that is but it's sort of like coming over from Jackson, halfway between Jackson, like following that about the 430 ray down.
It goes towards where that little light area is.
So that's the end of my...
### Transcript 040
All right, we've got Earthrise coming up, and I can just hear the shutter clicking away over there, so I know Marie's on it.
It's beautiful coming up.
We're starting to see the blues and a little bit of continental browns, some atmospheric whites that are very dynamic.
The Terminator line across Earth is extremely sharp and very dynamic.
And that's all on the target.
number Echo and man is it beautiful coming up.
It's right in the right place and so it's right south of where I was seeing that exospheric phenomenon or a little bit of dust lofting that I described in my previous audio stamp for Delta.
Man is it rising a lot faster than I expected.
I think I see Australia so
Good day to all you out there and everybody on Earth.
It's good to be back with you.
And hopefully you've got us back in communication and we can get you some of this beautiful data coming down.
What a fabulous pass.
And man, is it really cool to see Earthrise coming back up.
It's changed a little bit of my perception of the moon with the colors.
My eyes are adapting to the lights now.
of Antarctica and some of that cloud deck and again seeing just such a sharp Terminator across Earth and it's really moving.
I guess my first impression is how fast it's moving up or maybe how fast we're moving relative to these two beautiful planetary bodies that we've had a chance to explore.
It is about
two-thirds of the way up right now and continuing to change my perception the more that I see the whites come up and really spectacular view of the blues.
Blues are just so dynamic, even more dynamic than
our observation of Earth from ISS.
I think it's just really cool to have so much black space with our beautiful blue Earth out there.
And that blue is just so striking just with the gray tones of the moon in our foreground and the Earth in the further foreground or the background.
It's really dynamic.
And so just now
The final little bit of Earth is creeping out from behind the Terminator, and we now have the full view of Earth with its own Terminator on it, probably about 80% of Earth that we see right now with that Terminator along the western rim.
Overall, just fantastic opportunity to catch that Earthrise and really changed
our view on some of the colors of the moon that we're seeing, but also changing our view on our place in the solar system and universe.
So with that, hopefully we'll move on to some of those other dynamic targets that we've got coming up for the lunar observations and close out this last shift with a bank.
### Transcript 041
Getting ready for Earthrise.
I'm watching for it.
I think I know where it should be coming from, but I'm not sure.
So I'm just gonna keep looking right over the edge here.
I'm just sort of waiting to see.
Make sure that I can just keep imaging until hopefully that I can see it appear.
It should be coming pretty soon here.
Uh, maybe not right away.
Um... Earthrise, yeah, it's now inside the Earthrise target.
And so there it is, I can see it coming.
There.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I'm making sure that my focus is on the actual illuminated moon so that way I can get a good moon focus photo.
Oh my goodness, hello friends.
This is so neat.
I can start to see the browns coming up and a little bit of the white.
Definitely those blues of the ocean coming up.
You can really see looking at the limb of the Earth.
Looking at the limb of the moon, it's very sharp.
I don't really see any fuzziness there.
So it's really just bisecting the Earth as it rises.
Oh, here's some white that's coming up.
I can now start to see
A little bit of Africa is coming.
Is that Africa?
Nope, actually it's Australia.
Good to see you all on the other side.
I can now see the white of Antarctica.
Let me start to zoom out and try to get that width.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Oh my goodness, I think it's just, this is just one of the most amazing things I've ever witnessed in my life.
Just here we are waiting for you all to return and just seeing our perfect little neighbor out there.
I've seen it from, just absolutely incredible.
We've looked back at the Earth a lot on this trip, but nothing like seeing it come out of the darkness on the other side of the moon.
I'm gonna readjust my Pelotour real quick.
Try to get back and get some more photos.
Every little bit helps, right?
The one thing, so like I can, to really tell you what I'm seeing here, I can see about the, it's coming out about the 930 position to the left of the moon, on the west side of the moon.
I can see Antarctica, Australia, a little bit of Asia over there, definitely some clouds in the cloud system.
Now that I can see the orange of Australia, that's really combining into some of the browns.
Let me try to get that all in one photo.
The browns in Australia are sort of bringing out some of the browns that I see in the South Poleaitken Basin-Aitken Crater Basin, like definitely around like
Mare Anjanai and over from Apollo, sort of those browns are coming out.
The blues definitely up with Muscoviense.
Those blues sort of help match what we're seeing up there.
Absolutely incredible to see it.
It looks like the Earth could just fit so perfectly inside the Mare patch from Muscoviense and just absolutely incredible day.
Oh, I'm so happy to
see you all on the other side just a beautiful planet we have here and so contrasting after just looking at the as it was put from um apollo 11 the beautiful desolation of the moon is really in contrast with that beautiful dynamics of the Earth
I'm going to make sure I get a mosaic of this Terminator too.
Oh, I got it.
So I'm going to start with the from north to south.
I got my Terminator at the edge of my screen.
Let's see on my 50% overlap.
Now going a little bit closer to that limb.
Going right back up.
Trying to make sure I get some focus on me.
Get the focus spots.
Absolutely stunning.
### Transcript 042
Okay, quick one on Ryder Crater, our target Foxtrot.
Just running out of time and I want to make sure I get some of the higher priority targets.
So this will be a quick one.
I did take a long look at the LTP to make sure that I was able to train my eyes in on Ryder.
And I think I've nailed it just below that larger crater that has a ring structure and a mare.
I see Ryder pretty distinctly just given its higher albedo and some topography that's now popping out along the Terminator.
And as I zoom in on the LTP and flip back and forth, I can definitely match up the two pretty similar diameter craters under the crater that is larger just above Ryder.
and be able to trace that down.
And then there's a similar three or four craters kind of in a square that allow me to pick up Ryder with the higher albedo of those four.
Other than that, I can't say too much about Ryder other than it has that higher albedo visibly by my eye and it is really distinct.
with some of the topography around there.
Don't know how to explain it, but there's a very distinct topography, almost looks like deeper crater in that area.
I think that's one just to the west of Ryder, the higher albedo one.
As I zoom in, yeah, for sure, the one that looks like a deeper crater is to the west of Ryder, but there's a series of four craters there that make about the same diameters to each other.
And rider is that higher albedo one, which my eye does pick up out the window.
### Transcript 043
start on Ryder Crater.
I got really distracted during Earthrise and so I'm gonna get going on this one right now.
I can see it's down along the southern, the southern limb and the South Poleaitken Basin Acon and so I'm using this again Marie.
I'm looking for Ryder with my camera along the southern rim.
I'm looking to see
So it's definitely sort of hard to pick this one out.
So I have this high albedo spot that I'm looking for here.
I don't have too much time, so it should be, I can see where, Teosca, is that what there?
Okay, I can see the peak right next to it there, and I can see their bright spot now.
I found that peak.
I found that bright spot, so I'm going to zoom in and get some good images there of that area.
Let's see how that, looking at that with the rest of the South Poleaitken Basin Aiken Basin area.
And so, yeah, I can see exactly that crater with the peak ring.
So I'm really looking to see if I can see that bright spot
The brightness is not standing out as much as I would have expected right now.
So that is sort of surprising.
It's not surprising because it's right on the Terminator there.
So that brightness didn't really help me find it.
More of the morphology did.
So making sure that I'm in the right spot.
There's the two double right above it and then the mare.
So I definitely got some images of that material there.
But really cannot see any of those ejector rays.
And looking for...
There's definitely... Yeah, it's definitely slightly lighter.
But really hard to just pick out much more of that texture of that small area besides like...
Sort of looks like a dome-y material.
Sort of raised a little bit.
Slightly lighter than the area around it.
Is that a volcano cone right there?
Probably not, but pretty interesting.
### Transcript 044
starting my Whole Moon target so this is our last Whole Moon looking at Whole Moon and SPA basin I'm gonna work on doing a mosaic here and so I'm gonna do north to south snake pattern starting at the disappearing limb at a mid a
mid focal length so I'm gonna go at about 200 here it's gonna be my starting point so I'm gonna start right over at the limb uh near the north pole that's disappearing so I'm just gonna start my mosaic here just looking at all the the rays I can still see um and Jackson and Crookes Crater on my way down here all the way down to Apollo Basin as I go across I can see that
Ray from Jackson's still really well in the South Poleaitken Basin-Aitken Crater Basin area.
I guess I'll try this methodology also.
Oh, I moved.
That was dumb.
I'm gonna restart my mosaic.
Gonna start again from the top.
Because I moved mid-thing, so I wanted to make sure that you all can make this mosaic much better.
So I'm gonna work on going through this again.
Now back down to Apollo Basin.
Going over, I can still see Apollo Basin as I work my way up.
Still see the limb sort of on the, still within my frame here.
Back up to the top.
go work my way down.
I'm really starting to see how these rays are over going the terrain behind it and also how a lot of these craters they don't look as sharp as I would have thought.
So as I get closer to the Terminator that I am those morphologies is becoming much more
Defined and just looking in all these different Mari patches.
You see some of those wider streets especially between my engine I and looking up at Muscovy and I'm right in the middle of the NC working my way back down snaking around Tioskovsky with that big Mari pond Mari and I you can finally start to see those swirls better than I could see them in the first I
First time around and then working my way back up.
Hang on, come right back down on the Terminator.
Get a little bit of Earth in my view.
Alright, I finished that whole mosaic going through, so I'm actually pretty excited about that.
I did, like I said before, I did restart it, but did pull it through, sort of seeing that transition between the different areas that I looked at.
Yaskowski right there on that rim.
Really incredible to be looking at the moon like that.
### Transcript 045
starting target 20 with Aiken and some of the regional scarps.
It took a few seconds to make sure I was located basically off of Mari Injanai, so thanks to the LTP for getting me there.
Mari Injanai did allow me to trace up really quickly to Aiken's crater that really has one of the darkest Mari patches in my current view.
Really amazing how that
color changes as the spacecraft moves and the moon moves with us.
But yeah, Aitken Crater is really showing some dark albedo in the base of it.
There's one bright spot also in the base of Aitken Crater Crater that doesn't show up as bright in the LTP.
So if I have time, I might do a quick annotation of that.
For a quick note, it's the 400 millimeter
image that's in the LTP is right above or right below the numeral 20.
So it corresponds with that either central peak or central impact in Aiken Crater.
That feature is a lot brighter by naked eye than it is in the image in the LTP.
And also notably around Aiken Crater is like high albedo, slight rim highlights that go from about the 10 o'clock all the way around to the five o'clock.
I don't see it at the other cardinal directions or clock directions, but I do see that highlighted rim with Aiken from that 10 to five o'clock.
If I concentrate a little bit on the regional scarps that are northeast, I'm looking for any visibility of those and with the naked eye, I cannot pick anything up.
Although I will kind of stare at that region, try to let my eyes adapt to the northeast again of Aiken Crater and see if any of those regional scarps pick up.
I'll say broad terms with the naked eye, I haven't been able to.
verify that anything I've seen is a scarp, nothing has stood out to me as like a, oh yeah, barely that is a scarp.
But concentrating specifically in that northeast region of Dakin Crater that's highlighted by the LTP and not picking anything up there.
So hopefully the camera does or hopefully that that tells you something about what our eyes can pick up and whatnot, what they can't.
I'll do a quick check of LTP, make sure we've got all the observer actions covered.
Swirls, so swirls in Aiken.
Again, it's got that dark Mari Piatch at the bottom, but I don't see any swirls with the naked eye.
So no swirls, no scarps by the naked eye on Aiken.
And with that, I'll close out Target 20.
### Transcript 046
Alright, starting on my next one, I finished that Whole Moon.
I'm going to go to Aitken Crater Crater, and then what I'm going to be looking for here is the Compact Split Crater with Mare infill.
So I'm looking to see if I can see any evidence of that scarp, the Raka X scarp.
And so I want to get in the highest resolution that I can.
So let me focus in on...
There is Mari Injani.
There's Mari Injani.
there oh I can definitely see those swirls now and I work my way up to the mare pond of Aitken Crater Crater and I can really see that and so what I can see when I look in this mare pond of Aitken Crater Crater I can see that high point pretty in the center the rim of the crater is not very well defined
but that mare pond is really well defined.
And if I look in there, I can see some later sort of swirling also in there.
There is the crater that is about the six o'clock position of that mare pond.
And, um, and a little bit above that, it's almost like an upside down octopus.
Uh, you can sort of see some of that coloring.
It looks like the mare pond sort of flows around the
It flows around the peak inside.
Why can't I think of that word right now?
And it has that little offshoot to the right from there.
Okay, so I'm definitely going to go try to look for that scarp right now.
I can see, almost looks like you can see those little swirls.
Let me see if I can maybe draw those in a second too.
But if I'm looking for that scarp, it is.
It looks like that scarp is sort of bisecting the crater next to it.
So I go there.
I go across to this crater and see if I can
Resolve that scarp.
I think that is the one.
There.
Okay, again.
It's very...
I'm taking images of where it is.
It's very hard for me to resolve that right now in the light.
But I'm following the craters that it would be bisecting there.
But it really isn't popping out as evident without like some of the shadows that would make it pop out a little bit more if it were closer to the Terminator than it actually is.
And so I really can't see any of that tectonic activity there.
But it is worth looking for and hopefully, I wish we could definitely have seen that for you all.
Um, let's see.
### Transcript 047
Target 21, Mari Injani, round two.
I've allowed my eyes to adapt to that area after locating it with the LTP.
Again, thanks for targeting me right in on Mari Injani.
And I've got the 400 millimeter image up and trying to let my eyes adapt, but also looking down.
quickly to where the swirls are in the image versus what I see with the naked eye.
I can definitely see the swirl that kind of looks like a tadpole that's swimming from west to east into the southernmost crater that's circled by the green 21 on the lunar targeting package.
I can pick that guy up as probably the most distinct by the naked eye.
Um, it has a little bit of a muter tone, so a little bit grayer than the image on the LTP.
Again, it depends, I guess, on the brightness of this, um, uh, PCD screen, but, uh, the, the, I wouldn't been able to say yay, verily that that is a swirl without knowing to look for it.
Based off the image and the naked eye, but now that I know there's a swirl I could definitely pick it up and I can then translate that color that albedo up to
the crater that's kind of to the north of the Mare Ingenii and Swirls area that's circled in that 400 millimeter lens image that's on the LTP.
And I can pick out a patch of about three smaller swirls that are set pretty distinctly against that darker mare patch.
And that's about it for swirls and Mare Ingenae is the large one to the south and the three that dot the northern crater.
The basin overall from when I observed it before seems about the same type of topography.
Maybe it's the illumination, maybe it's just the topography in that area.
I don't see anything distinct on the crater walls or
the base of that crater given the current illumination conditions.
What I will say is when I look down at the image, 400 millimeter image on the LCP, I don't see that crater structure that is in the image in this illumination condition.
Seems pretty flat right now, which is consistent with the other things along that same kind of
semi-circular trace on the moon.
You just don't see the topography that you do as it gets closer towards the Terminator.
Overall, other distinct things around Mare Injani is a couple bright spots, maybe younger craters towards the rim of that northern Mare patch.
I can definitely pick up that there's a brighter crater there
I can trace back and locate in the LTP image.
And so all those craters that are, I don't know what a good size reference are, but all those smaller craters that are in Mare Injani can barely pick up, but can certainly pick them up based on their albedo and some of the topography that's starting to show up.
So even though the overall, I guess what I'm trying to say, even though the topography is pretty muted across there compared to the image,
You can pick up the craters that are in that smaller diameter based on some of their color and albedo differences.
I think that's all I'm going to be able to say on mare ingenii, but between
The first and second observations of that, I think maybe it'd be interesting to go back and evaluate my first and second observations.
I think the first time I had the camera and the second time was just by naked eye, so probably some things are a little bit distinct based on the observations between those two mediums.
Okay, closing out Mare Injani, target 21 now.
### Transcript 048
Okay, I'm back.
I finished Aiken.
Now I'm going to do, um, number, going to number 21, Amari Anjanine Swirls.
Really excited about this one.
I saw them peeking out a little bit before, um, when I was doing my Whole Moon Mosaic.
And so I'm excited.
I had looked at the Amari Anjanine Swirls during my first pass.
And it was really tough to pull out those swirls, but as I'm zooming in now, I can definitely pull out those swirls.
I can see a lot of those different S features.
And so I'm using the camera fully zoomed in here, and it really does start to look like an eyeball to me.
That Mari patch looks like the iris, and these swirls sort of look like the veins.
I think you have that main mare patch.
You've got some of the outbreaching from there.
So those mare flows, they sort of lobate in the end on the right-hand side, and then the out channel on the left-hand side.
And you can see how the mare material sort of disperses in through the crater basin.
And then looking into those swirls themselves, they're definitely the ones sort of...
So if I can look at that maripon and sort of go out from there, sort of like straight out to the left like the 9 o'clock, the swirls are much more faint.
But as I go down towards like the 7 or 8 o'clock, they're much more defined.
You get a couple of different shapes of the swirls.
I sort of see things that look like sort of C shapes, some that look like backwards S's, some that are just like squiggle worms.
It's pretty neat to be able to see that.
I'm also looking at some of the textures that I see in the rim.
I can see them on the wall there as well.
So I just really, really need to see these.
These swirls really are the best to find ones that we've seen.
Like I've seen a couple other, can sort of see them in
I could seal a couple and leave knits and I can get those sort of both in the same frame.
Here I've got it centered between the two and like definitely comparing it up to see if I see any swirls in.
Yeah, I really can't pick them out too much in Muscovy and say not like can MRI engine.
I just absolutely incredible What I can see there Make sure that I mark that take a really good image, and I'll make sure I mark it with my With my indicator here, so I might get a good one with it right centered in the middle Okay, so I'm going in
I can now see that in Mari Injani.
Let's see if I was able to get that.
Mari Injani.
Let me make sure that this is actually recording.
Mari and Janai.
All right, I was able to get the recording.
I see my music note now.
So what I can, one of the things that's really interesting to me is that I really couldn't tell those squirrels before and how this time around they're just so distinct.
They're just popping out much better than they were able to be before.
it's just looking at like how some of them really seem skinnier versus some of them have a thickness and the skinnier ones look like they have a much more defined um boundary but the ones that sort of like in the bottom like the one that sort of almost looks like a a worm with a giant head um there it just really looks
like the the rounder part of the lighter color swirl is much more diffuse.
And if you look at the bottom one there and then look inside the Mari patch itself it looks like there's some more of those little diffuse wispies that are not as defined as the swirls.
So definitely it looks like there is like areas that mixture is happening in a lot of different places but not as defined in some and much more defined in others.
### Transcript 049
All right, so I am getting ready.
Now I am back.
I am over in the, in window three that has CapCam 2.
I'm now just focusing on my observations, not with the camera anymore.
So it's so nice when you're able to zoom in so much.
And now I'm back to looking at it as a whole and looking at the entire complete disk is still really
really need to see.
So I'm going to go and be looking for By's Ballot.
It is up by Jackson Crater.
So I can see Jackson there.
I can see where Lacus Luxury region is.
And so then I'm looking for that.
I know it's a weird shaped.
Lacus Luxury is that dark spot, which I can see.
which really helps me find Bai's ballot.
And so I have been able to find it.
And so I'm just looking with my eyes right now out the window.
And so I can see this in the, it's the rays of Jackson sort of go all the way from the limb almost over to essentially just above
Bayes-Ballot region and so the Bayes-Ballot I think it's just like 72 kilometers in diameter so it's a pretty small guy but the shape of it is definitely weird and so I can tell that shape sort of using the brightness of the
of the wall of that crater.
And so the brightness is much stronger on the western side than the eastern.
And then underneath we have the Lackus Luxury region, which is a darker spot.
That dark spot sort of looks like the, you know, when we found the parachute on the surface of Mars from the Curiosity and Perseverance rovers, you can sort of see all the strings that held the rover.
That's exactly what it looks like.
And so the darkness of that looks similar to what we can see over at Muscovy and say there.
The boundaries of that, they definitely sort of streak and it's gradational.
It's much stronger in the center of that lattice luxury, but we don't see anything sort of a emitter like
Well, now that I've sort of acclimated a little bit, I can see sort of a gray or brownish.
So on the bottom, that looks very similar to the highlands material that is being overlaid by the Jackson Crater rays.
And so I don't see too much else in that structure there.
And I'm running out of time because we had to switch.
So I'll finish this one up.
### Transcript 050
Okay, so I am now finished up on that gonna go back to Jackson Crater So I'm just looking at this I want to be able to annotate Well, I'm gonna work on an annotation during this one because I won't be able to annotate the extent of the ray system Including the furthest reaching areas of the rays And so I'm gonna work on opening up my OneNote
I could definitely still see the brightness of Jackson and where it's rays are going.
It's getting closer to the disappearing limb.
It's probably about 200 or so, maybe a little less kilometers from the disappearing limb.
And so I'm trying to look and I can see where these, let me open up my OneNote.
Oh, already drawn things that I didn't need to draw yet.
So I'm gonna try to draw what I can see from Jackson here.
I'm going to use a... Get a good color going.
I'm gonna use...
Definitely like I'm gonna use sort of a Reddish pinkish color to sort of show my rays here And definitely try to make them a little bit thicker And so I can definitely tell that there is This one that goes around Aiken crater here
So you can definitely see them sort of go past that.
I can see them going almost to Mare Injani is sort of where the end of my rays are in that direction.
I can still see that ray that goes all the way into like South Poleaitken Basin Aitken Crater Basin.
That one is really sticking out.
And then there's the one that goes just above
The Lacus Luxury region that I was looking at before and then the one that goes a little bit over to the limb and I'm definitely drawing this in my OneNote so you can start to see these pretty well.
It looks like they're still going over the bit from Crookes Crater and so you can really start to see it going off the edge and then that other crater right there whose Name I forget at this moment.
It looks like the one that sort of goes around Aiken, it sort of spreads there and sort of goes all the way to, like sort of surround Mare Anjanai.
Let me see if I can sort of show that a little bit with just sort of some lightness here.
So I got some good annotations there that really show the extent that I can see
Coming from that crater.
It is so bright still that center is so is the brightest white thing that I can see Still on the moon, and so it's pretty neat to be looking at that Let me go quickly to my lunar geography review Trying to get the The far side get the Jackson and
at them yeah that is definitely Crookes Crater right below it that I could still have in some really good rays that I can see as well so I'm gonna head back to make sure that I got everything that I need for my targeting plan and so yeah I can really start to see that like
there it almost feels before as the brightness the first time I looked at this the albedo was some of the big um the albedo was much stronger and it's sort of uh disappearing those rays that like you can definitely still trace it into SBA but it would have been harder to trace than it was earlier um and so I can definitely see how uh as the
as things approach the rays get closer to the Terminator it's much harder to see them now.
So I will finish this one up.
### Transcript 051
Okay, starting target 25 Jules Verne crater.
I'm just kind of centered up on that.
Oh, there's a few minute break between 24 and 25.
So it looks like I got a little extra time on Jules Verne.
So going to go ahead and capture this one right.
The LTP has like a five minute break between 23 and 25.
So it seems like we're missing 24.
And so hopefully the LTP is right.
I'm going to keep going with 25 with Jules Verne.
Give me one second to get right back onto the target list.
So looking for centered photographs at the highest focal length of Jules.
And I've got pretty good eyes on it, was able to index off of Silkowski pretty easily.
And so we're going to go ahead and start shooting some photos.
that includes Tsiolkovsky, so you can also index off of it just like I did towards Jules.
Overall, Jules is starting to become highlighted by that illumination of the Terminator.
Topography is really starting to pop, especially to the north of it at 10 to two o'clock.
There's a central little mare patch there.
It's like the size of a cashew nut that starts to really stick out, distinct in its albedo.
One of the things that just my eye keeps getting drawn to is that central peak of Silkoski, so trying to capture a few images of that while I can.
just because it's so dramatic on the limb.
Just taking a quick look back to make sure that everything's set up for this final little stretch and try not to miss Muscovian base and a high priority target coming up.
Really one of the things that stuck out to me on Jules Verne is that distinct topography that's starting to pop in the illumination conditions.
I've got plenty of photos that are at the highest resolution or highest zoom of the lens, 400 millimeters.
A couple different orientations to try to capture that topography.
My eye does pick up on the mare patch a little bit better.
When I look above the camera, I can see that mare patch, that little cashew nut shape
a little bit better than what I see through the window and through the lens.
So just a note there that my eye is actually picking up that distinct color.
I'm sure once you stretch these pictures a little bit, they'll be better than what my eye is seeing through the viewfinder.
Okay, I'm gonna call that.
good with Jules Verne target number 25 because I know my next high priority is 26 with Muscovian Basins, a high priority target for you guys.
So closing out Jules Verne 25 now.
### Transcript 052
Okay, so now I had finished.
I am starting number 25, Jewel's Fern.
So I'm looking for Jewel's Fern over between Tioskovsky and to the west of Mari Injani.
So I can definitely see this.
This is the one with the C-shaped Mari patch.
in the center of it just west of Mare Injani.
And so I'm about, let's see, about 200, 250 kilometers from the Terminator on the left.
That's where I am too.
And so I can definitely see that.
And so I can tell there.
And so what I really want to do is sort of look for any history of fractures.
And so they have potentially some four fractured critters in here.
I can't really see any of these fractures.
I can tell from my LTP, they're sort of along the edge of that C. But from this view right here, I can't resolve those.
Really, it's the
the dark mare patches that are much easier to see.
That C shape looks so much more distinct right now than it actually does in my...
I can sort of see some of those raised rims in there, but as we're getting closer, the small craters that are around Jules Verne are becoming much more defined with their limbs, their rims,
It's definitely sort of, you can see the morphology starting to come back.
The Jules Verne crater is circular, is mostly circular in shape.
The mare sort of has that sharper boundary, especially on the bottom, the bottom part of the outside of the sea.
But as you go up towards the top,
especially right where that crater is, like around the 11 o'clock and the boundary of the Jules Verne, you really start to lose that distinct boundary of that mare patch.
The gray inside is sort of the lighter, is a bit of a lighter gray up top and that darker gray the bottom.
That two-tone is very similar to what I can see on Muscovy and say with that lighter tone on the bottom and that darker tone on top.
the the shadows are starting to show up especially there's that brighter spot just north of like about the 10 30 position um and so i can start to see that that part oh this part of the moon's falling down um and start to see that bright area along the top very high
Bright albedo and so you can start to see that a little bit of that Rim brightness.
I really can't pull out too much of the texture that is in there from this perspective But it is Just Is my timeline
Looks like I actually was a little bit ahead.
That's okay.
I'm still looking at the Jules Verne right there.
Um, and one of the things it's like those sort of brighter areas as you go around.
Do you see one like to the north?
You definitely see it.
If I go to my OneNote here for my Jules Verne.
Oh, made a line.
I see the like one bright zone.
I'm going to draw it in here on my page.
I see the one bright zone below, but the area that's a little bit brighter above it doesn't really show up as much in my LTP.
And so it's like just around these two craters.
I've sort of highlighted them.
It looks like a little beret on top of my crater right now.
Um, and so I can see where that brightness is.
It's almost like I can follow that brightness around sort of like, you know, when you sweat and like the saltiness sort of makes the sweat stains that stay on like your workout clothes or like a swimsuit.
That is sort of how like sort of these bright patches look.
They're like very granular, um, sort of raising up a little bit, but very delicate on top.
um sort of these white braids almost look like white veins going around um the moon.
Um let's see it's really hard to see any slopes in there and um I think that's pretty good for my jewel's fern.
Just really neat looking at the moon this way after like looking at it so close up with my camera.
So taking this step back again and looking at it from a distance and comparing the areas to each other in one full swoop.
This really is a really neat view to be able to see.
Especially like looking over and like as South Polacan Basin is sort of disappearing off the limb.
That's sort of like the yellowish tint that's like around
Apollo Basin.
It's sort of like a very light yellow.
That's really neat to sort of see that bit of color over there against the stark grayness that is along the Terminator.
That I'm pretty, pretty impressed with as I start to go through and look at these and watching Jackson and these really high albedo rays start to disappear as well.
It's pretty incredible to have gone from when we first started looking at this we had that full disc and now we're just looking at a section of the moon and it's pretty neat.
### Transcript 053
All right, starting high priority target number 26, Muscovians Basin.
Specifically going to center some images and capture that entire basin.
Might make it a few little mosaics of it.
It's really starting to pop now as it comes closer to the Terminator.
So this is great lighting conditions to capture it.
Definitely can give you guys some words on the structure, texture, and variations of any color and albedo.
And I'm going to keep a close eye out for lava flows.
The basin rim right now is really starting to pop.
So hopefully those come across in the images and any swirls.
So lots to look at for, lots to look out for in Muscovian basin.
And I'll double check that I've captured any notes after I start shooting some pictures here.
So I might go quiet for a little bit as I capture some Muscovians.
glamour shots here.
Okay, at the highest resolution, so at 400, I can capture all of Muscovian's ring structure with a little bit of the Terminator in there.
And so I'm gonna capture a couple photos
a couple 20 or so in different orientations, different things in the frame of the photo for context.
So a couple with the limb in there or with the Terminator, sorry, in there and a couple with the limb in there.
Again, all at 400 millimeters.
Now I'm gonna do a quick little mosaic.
About 75% overlap.
Realizing I'm doing an east-west snake.
Probably should have done a north-south one given the Terminator conditions right now, but shouldn't matter too much.
Okay, so there's a mosaic in there at 400 millimeter, that east-west snake across Muscovians, a tier of three from north to south.
Again, using the camera lens kind of as a binocular now, or a monocular,
I can maybe see some really nice terminations of the mare, you know, the lava coming up against some of the rim structure to the west side of Muscovians.
Specifically, starting around the one o'clock to four o'clock.
Seems like it comes the closest to the rim there.
Take a few more photos.
Really concentrating on trying to keep the camera steady, take out any shakes and not cram the camera too much into the window while I'm doing this.
Albedo wise, the highest albedo is right at the crater rim at the, I'll say 1030.
Between 10 and 11 o'clock is the highest albedo on the crater rim.
The darkest albedo is at the base of the crater about one o'clock.
There's a crater down there that's at two o'clock that's right around there seems to be the darkest part of that mare patch.
Everything else is a couple of tones of gray in between.
Didn't see any distinct colors other than shades of gray at this time.
I'm taking a quick look at the LTP and allow my eyes to adjust back inside of the cabinet.
So I definitely got a good centered images, captured the entire basin, captured the basin with some different things in context, and also a small little mosaic there.
I'm not going to make any annotation here because I didn't see any
strong color difference and I hopefully described the albedo context best I could.
But I want to keep my hands on the camera here and get on to the next image and close out strong.
So that's it for target number 26.
### Transcript 054
Okay, this is back to Marie going to our high priority target of Muscovy and Sea Basin This is gonna be I think one of our last Last targets we're getting close to the end of our time together me and my Pelotor headset and so I'm really excited to I've been using Muscovy and Sea as a Definitely one of those anchor points like you can tell why it's one of our 15 this whole entire time
It's probably been my best scale bar throughout the entire day.
Just that distinct mare patch really is covers, you know, like four, four and a half, one, two, three, four and a half of them really cover the width that I can see in that line of the moon right now.
And so that's been pretty neat to use that as my scale bar throughout the day.
I am going to look at this and sort of one of my goals is to look for color and albedo effects within that mare patch and really look to see if I can see any of those swirls very similarly to what I was looking at in like mare and janai.
And when I first look at it here I can start to see now that I've been staring at just it again for a while I can start to see
that sort of two-tone tie-dye-ness within that mare patch.
And again, I'm looking at this with just my eyes, not my camera.
It's a very circular basin, and that mare patch within it is very well constrained on one side by the raised rim feature, the raised inner peak ring.
And then you sort of see how the mare flows outward from there.
And so it sort of looks like that breach that is going outward.
And it doesn't make it all the way to the outer basin rim.
And so it sort of stops a little bit short of it.
It looks like it's sort of got that low bait sort of boundary to it.
And it is a bit of that.
And so it just looks like it sort of disperses into the rest of the basin.
I'm going to sort of try to work on my one note here.
So I've got that zoomed in and looking to see if I can draw out some of these differences that I can see in the colors.
Let me get a good...
I'm gonna see if I can use maybe this
see if I can use my highlighter to really help here it's really that inner part that you really can't see that highlighter at all so let me let me undo that highlighter let me try again with something different I want to use a pen I think it just sort of like a lighter blue is gonna help me here these are the lighter areas and so I can really tell this center spot
I need to zoom in a little bit so I'm trying to not let the not let it bias me too much here so I can really see this like this lighter part out here and then there is another later part coming out from
around this like between these two craters that I am drawing and then I can sort of get that low bait sort of feature as it goes into that other what I know to be that like floor fracture craters I can't really see those fractures here at the resolution that I am looking for
It's definitely a little bit of just sort of like that tie-dye.
It almost does look like those swirls slightly when you start to look, especially this one line that is above the crater that you can see around the one o'clock, like one to two o'clock part of that basin.
You can start to see a little bit of line.
The longer I look at this, the more I convince that I see
see more pieces of that light and darkness.
It's really not as defined as you could see in Mare Ingenii, but sort of similar to how there were those sort of wispiness that you could see during parts of Mare Ingenii.
It's sort of very similar to what I am seeing here as well.
And I
The morphology that I can see here is that I can see these two craters that are about the 10 o'clock and the 8 o'clock position and then the one that's about the 7 o'clock and the 6 o'clock
There's a really bright spot in the rim.
I'm gonna draw in with like a different color here.
It's like a pinkish color that's like a really high albedo spot.
That's really up by this one crater here.
Let me see if I can see exactly where it is.
That's that rim.
It's like in this area, I'm surrounding it by pink, definitely some higher albedo, small impacts right there.
Let's see how I'm doing.
I definitely still got another minute or so on my timing.
Just that, just knowing the power that it would take that lava flow prize, just really neat.
I'm gonna try to finish this one up.
It's been fun for looking for targets.
I'm just gonna probably just talk your ear off as I look for Impact Flashes.
### Transcript 055
All right, I'm still in window two.
I'm using the camera to look for Impact Flashes, but while I do that, I'm gonna capture a full frame of the moon when this dramatic, like, half-Terminator thing creeping across the moon.
I'm gonna use the camera to keep an eye out for Impact Flashes.
Whoop, I just saw something in a wiggly line through the camera.
I wasn't holding down the,
the shutter at the time, but I saw a squiggly green line fly across the Terminator of the moon.
It definitely wasn't a point function, but it was a, maybe I saw kind of a streak, possible impact flash.
If it was, it was bright green.
It was in the northern third of the dark Terminator area.
Trying to take some pictures there, but I'll try to go ahead and annotate what I saw.
after taking a few more photos and then I'll get back to making observations.
So look out for a one note annotation from my observations of a green impact possible flash in the early parts of observing the target 27.
### Transcript 056
Okay, I went ahead and annotated my first impact flash observation.
Back at the camera, back out looking at the window.
Gonna try to take a photo every 30 seconds or so as this Terminator slowly walks across while also looking through the viewfinder.
Using the camera as kind of monocular to look for Impact Flashes.
while also capturing a nice time sequence at the same lens zoom.
I'm not going to change that at all, just going to capture the whole field of view of the moon from north to south and watch that Terminator just cross
Still really impressed by that crater with the central peak in it, Tsiolkovsky, I think, and it's really just going into the Terminator now.
It's amazing how you can see that rim highlighted, but the darkness of the Terminator just to the west of it.
Central peak is still really popping out, but also trying to train my eye towards the
the part of the moon that's in the Terminator, making sure that I don't miss any impact flash again.
That last one was just this bright green streak that kind of did this Z shape.
Tried best to capture it in the annotation using the appropriate color pen that I could get close to that bright green.
Didn't do it justice, but it definitely was not a point source.
more of a streak, so not sure how to explain that one.
I think for file size reasons I'm going to go ahead and end this audio file.
and continue to observe in this manner, but let you know if I do see any other Impact Flashes during the remainder of the time that we have here on target 27.
### Transcript 057
All right, back with you on target 27.
I've been probably spent about 80% of the time observing the moon through the camera lens at 90 on the zoom.
It captures the extent from north to south.
I've had the red center target right at the Terminator and been capturing photos every
three to five seconds to make sure that I capture that transition that's happening right on the Terminator while also keeping an eye out through the lens for any Impact Flashes.
While I'm doing that, the other 20% of the time has been looking down at the PCD and making annotations or saving off audio files.
Gonna go ahead and stick with this audio recording through the last few minutes we have here on
Target 27 for looking for these Impact Flashes.
Pretty jazzed that I did see one.
Pretty confused by its color and its characteristics.
But hopefully we captured some of that in the saw imagery.
And hopefully I annotated that pretty well to at least capture what I saw.
I'll be interested in, after we do the debrief, whether Marie saw the same thing.
Hopefully these series of photos every three to five seconds as the Terminator is changing are helpful.
I find it useful to not only use the camera as a optical device to look for the Impact Flashes, but also just watch that Terminator change and one to capture it for you guys as well.
If I would have thought about it before I got set up for this, I might have pulled out the bracket and got the camera set up so that I could go hands free and maybe even set the camera up so that it would take photos automatically at a set time.
Would have made a really cool video out of this if it was, if we weren't, if we didn't jostle the camera between that whole time sequence during this 10 minutes.
But I think that way I could have looked for Impact Flashes, but also captured this really cool time sequence that I'm trying the best that I can by hand.
But if I would have had the bracket set up, might've been a better sequence.
It's really cool to see some of these basins start to disappear into the Terminator and how they really pop right before they just go black.
Really missing seeing the Earth out of the window, that was pretty cool.
Some of those images of that blue Earth are just still going to resonate with me for the rest of my life.
And I see we're coming to the end of the impact flash observation, so I'm going to go ahead and end the audio here, stop the sequence of images that I've been taking every three to five seconds, and see whatever get-aheads that we have while we still have this beautiful view.
So, finishing target 27 now.
### Transcript 058
next I'm gonna look for some Impact Flashes myself just gonna stare at the moon for a bit it's really just embracing these last moments while I'm looking for waiting for these last moments well before they turn the attitude away I know that we're just gonna be able to so I'm really focusing on the part to the west of the Terminator that is in darkness
Because I know that's probably where we'd best be able to see it.
And I hope that we can find one.
It seems like Trevor saw something, but I was too busy trying to write my Name in the audio recording.
So I think I missed it.
But hopefully he had a really good observation there as well.
While he starts annotating that, I'm just going to keep my eyes peeled, keep looking for it as much as I want to.
continue just looking at the moon I'm really trying to just keep my eyes where there's darkness what a cool day just flew around the moon today how many people get to do that?
not that many we've trained for so long and so much stuff on this mission and
Here we are.
We're heading around and we're going to start coming back towards home.
Well, we are coming back towards home, but we are just making our way back now.
And I can imagine the excitement that's going on down there in the sur of all of these recordings.
I can't wait to get them on the ground and get these images on the ground.
I know we saw some really cool stuff today.
and just absolutely incredible I almost feel like right now I'm leaving somebody a voicemail and it's just sitting in their pocket and I'm waiting to see if they're home but I'll keep talking to you in case that I hear something else a solid 10 minutes of my voice as I just watch for things
I think one of my favorite parts of the day was just at this one point, you know, Angela got a bungee cord wrapped completely around her ankle and definitely we had to untangle her as we did our switching.
I'm definitely thankful right now that I ate a snack in between, but I know that we're all gonna sit down and have some really cool dinner conversation tonight.
Talking about all the things we saw.
I think some of my favorite parts were just especially some of these targets we got to do twice and like the differences between how hard I looked for how hard I looked for swirls at the beginning versus how easy it was to find them later is just really incredible and knowing that we were able to do that over the course of one flyby when it would take so long for other
sources to be able to do that.
Just seeing how things go from no morphology to this very distinct Terminator that we have with all of the morphology, the puckering of the surface, knowing that every single one of those impacts were made by a flash that I am waiting for right now.
But I'll probably never see it and that's okay because they don't come around that much.
And at least Trevor saw one.
That's absolutely so neat.
There's such that one little bright thing over by leafnets.
That's a really bright spot.
I'm sure that got captured earlier but it really hits out.
And there's this one little bright spot that's sort of off the edge of the Terminator.
It's like, I can tell it's like a central peak or something like that.
It just looks like it's this one little spot, this high point that's still getting the littlest bit of sunlight right now, but it looks like it's its own little, little ocean.
I wonder if I can draw that.
I shouldn't draw that somewhere.
It's like right in the middle.
You can see, you can see,
There's that big crater that's below.
Let's go in and see.
Kohlschlatter.
Around Kohlschlatter, towards the bottom rim of Kohlschlatter and over, right over the terminators where I see that bright spot that's got that high point that's probably a central peak.
So that's really cool to be able to see that as well.
I actually really like impact crater time.
Just looking, waiting to see if something appears.
I can hear still the shutter of Trevor's camera just constantly going.
And so I think he's hoping that he would at least catch something else.
But I know our SAW cameras are doing their jobs.
and uh at this point they're streaming all of this back to you so if you they'll catch it in there i just wanna i want to see it first though trevor already saw it first so i want to see it second right there when there are viruses in space there's viruses on trevor's pcd oh no
Wow you can really start to, you can still see that light yellow goldish in the SPA basin as I stand here.
Like I know it started disappearing.
It's just that very subtle tan goldish color that is in there.
It's really distinct from, it's like in the background compared to those darker mare patches.
the shadows just make these rims so distinct of these impact basins these impact craters it's really cool how you can really start to see the superposition one on top of the other you see the more dulled ones and then you can see the ones on top of them oh my eyeballs just switched all of a sudden craters look like mounds gotta put it back gotta put it back there we go
Gotta remember where my sunlight's coming from.
Now they look like craters again.
Okay, good.
Still no more Impact Flashes.
Still haven't seen one.
Gonna keep my eyes peeled, though.
It really does, like, at this point, it's just... You know, not spending the time looking at my, uh...
my recorder screen or my my pcd i really can just start to just get lost the the rotation is so slow it just feels like the moon is just standing still in front of us and you know feels like we're standing still right in front of it just amazing that i know the speed that we're going at to get back to you all and here we are
Just feel like we're just standing still.
I know that our time looking for Impact Flashes is nearing an end.
And so is the time of our flyby.
This is going to be a cool story to tell everyone.
What am I doing on my plan?
Trying to keep my eyes on it.
I still have lots of time.
This is a very long observation, this straight 10 minutes.
Gonna keep watching though.
This one I really wish I had like five eyes.
So I could keep two on the Impact Flashes and just spend the rest of the time looking at the rest of the moon.
Just gotta keep knocking that out for it.
Really is an amazing little piece of Earth we're looking at.
Still haven't seen anything yet.
So just really want one of those.
I can't let Trevor be the only one who saw one.
It's like, man, what a time to be looking down at my PCD.
I missed a new crater being born.
Alright, I'm gonna...
Pretty neat.
Yeah, now I can still just hear Trevor talking about how jazzed he was that he saw an impact flash.
So jealous.
But that's good for science overall and we are a team.
I think this is the coolest way to end a flyby, just staring at the moon like this.
Yeah, pretty cool, just watched Yaskovsky there on the Terminator.
I don't know, it's nearing the end of my Impact Flash time.
I still haven't been that lucky yet.
Still just enjoying watching the Terminator go by.
Ah, I see ya.
I heard about Tioskovsky.
There's a crater that is above it and below it it has like another little crater that looks like a little set of headphones.
That's pretty cool.
I think it's really nice to still have these noise-canceling Peloton headsets, Pelotor headsets on and just sort of immerse yourself in the moon.
I think it's actually a much nicer use being separated from the noise and the busyness of the spacecraft.
Knowing that our friends are keeping us
keeping you all updated on what they're seeing and what we're looking at right now.
I'm really curious about that color that's still there.
It would have been neat to sort of...
I know that you all have talked about it a lot, but just seeing that distinct color difference is really pretty incredible.
Alright, I think that ends my impact flash time.
Thanks for hanging on.
### Transcript 059
All right, looks like our last target before we get moving from this activity.
And I'm going to sadly miss it, but this is Get Ahead Target Hotel, the South Poleaitken Basin Region.
So what a good handoff to our future Artemis III friends and looking at the South Poleaitken Basin Region.
And going to take a mosaic of that in a west to east snake pattern with 50% overlap.
Tell you what I can see.
First I'm gonna capture a regional image of the entire South Poleaitken Basin area, about 1 5th of the moon.
Start to zoom in.
What I will say is that with the way the Terminator is right now, probably can barely see what the South Poleaitken Basin is happening right now on the west side.
So it's gonna be a challenging mosaic.
It's pretty much only a three shot mosaic at the 400 millimeter extent.
Take some 400 millimeter extents just centered on the South Poleaitken Basin, pretty dark down there right now based on that Terminator position.
Maybe if you stretch some of these images, it'd be interesting to see what pops out.
Going to take one along the entire Terminator with the camera in a horizontal position.
Yeah, as far as features down there, it's really challenging, even through using the camera lens.
I will say one of the craters down there, it looks like it has a little two eyes and a smiley face that is popping out right now based on the Terminator conditions.
The lighting is really illuminating its west face right now of that crater rim.
Pretty much the only one that I see topography, no color or albedo changes that are really striking right now just because of how dark it is down there.
The current conditions just aren't great for anything to be observed in that realm of color or albedo.
Just taking out some closing photos here of Target Hotel.
And yeah, just some few final thoughts.
It's just dramatic to see the moon like this.
I almost like seeing the moon more with this half Terminator just because of the topography that's popping out across the center third right now.
Yeah, it's dramatic when you see the full illuminated moon, but it's really also very cool to me to see this half moon with this dramatic Terminator and then think about the South Poleaitken Basin Region in our next Artemis mission that will go and touch the lunar surface exactly where my red dot is on my camera viewfinder right now.
Godspeed to Artemis 3 and closing out the final lunar targeting image now.
And hopefully see you guys back on the ground soon.
### Transcript 060
Alright, our very last one in my get-ahead is the South Poleaitken Basin Region.
I've been talking about it a little bit here, but definitely able to, now that I'm able to not be looking for Impact Flashes anymore, really focus on it some more.
You can really, the, sort of, it looks so flat and smooth compared to the Terminator region.
As I said before, that yellowish-brown tint is still there.
You can really tell it between Mare Anjanae and Apollo Basin.
You can really see that area as well as that sort of background color.
And so I can sort of follow the mari there definitely still have a slightly different color from this angle as well.
It's almost a little bit of a brownish tinge compared to like say up in Muscovy and say Basin.
Sort of that darker unit.
I just can't wait to know that somebody's gonna land there one day and
I hope that some of our images can help this as well and some of these observations.
Really be cool to get down there and get some boots on the ground and see what those footprints look like.
It's definitely that it's so much easier like on the closer to the limb to see that color difference.
And you could always see that sort of like ovular shape of South Polican before, but as you got a little bit closer to the Terminator, that difference sort of disappears.
You can't really tell where that color really stops.
It just sort of becomes overcome by the illumination environment.
I'm gonna look and see if I can find Schrodinger Basin down there.
Oh, maybe that is it Just there waiting for a Henderson et al 2025-2026 to come out.
I hear it's gonna be a good one I can see a little bit of it down there.
That'd be a really neat place to go with those cool pyroclastic deposits
see that the largest volcanic cone on the moon I can almost just pull I can maybe maybe I'm just fooling myself down there that giant cone um that's one of the things that I can't really see well there is um let me see
Yeah, I think it might be that point care region maybe that we're seeing right there.
Is that the one?
Maybe.
You can see down there the larger basin that's got the two smaller rims inside of it.
Definitely that bright high crest sort of hitting the
getting the light before it disappears into the darkness.
It's a pretty neat sight.
Just knowing that, that's definitely looks so different than the rest of the moon and we're going to be able to get a better view of it one day.
So I think this is it.
And next time that some human eyeballs are looking at this, hopefully they're, they're going to be getting ready to go on the ground and we can't wait to be a part of it.
Go team Artemis.