Angela with you.
I got so distracted by my drawing at Dewar Crater Region Crater.
I didn't realize I had a high priority target up next.
So I think I'm a little bit, I'm definitely behind in my Sikofsky observations.
So apologies about that, but I hope you'll like that, that drawing.
Okay, I am,
trying to find Sikovsky yeah because I'm a little bit late to this observation I pretty much see the entire outline of Sikovsky and then the so like the rim of the west rim of Sikovsky is illuminated and the central peak is illuminated
That's the view I'm seeing right now.
So I missed the initial where it was just behind the Terminator because it looks fully outside of the Terminator.
I think the only, oh, and now that I'm looking at it, there's a little bit more of the basin of the crater that's illuminated.
So to the north of the central peak, there is a slight color that comes through.
I will screenshot it and, oh, wait, actually it's already in my, I keep forgetting that it's already in my LTP.
Are we taking a break?
Is it time?