All right, Houston, Angela here.
I am, I was troubleshooting Kelsey's PCDs, so I definitely missed Babaloff.
Trying to get quickly back into Earthset, because I see it right now.
So let me get some pictures of Earthset.
And I'm taking them of the screen.
Yeah, okay, as I am,
Looking closer, you want me to focus on an Earth atmosphere.
I'm not seeing, it just looks like a perfect, clear-boundaried marble.
Oh, yeah, maybe I'm seeing a little bit of blue reflection coming from, only I can totally see it when I'm zoomed in.
but perhaps a little bit of this kind of neon, maybe not neon, like a, how do I describe that?
Just like a true blue.
And I'm checking my camera viewfinder to make sure that that color comes through, but I'm definitely seeing some
blue.
This is hard.
In terms of atmospheric patterns, I see some swirling of moons.
The bright white of Antarctica is much of a truer white than the gray
of the of the highlands and so the the clouds and those are polar ice caps are a great comparison for a true white because now that I'm looking at those in comparison to the highlands especially when I'm kind of zooming out a little bit we'll call it the thing that's the the truest color is actually the
the dead center of Crooks is probably what I'm seeing as like the truest white when I compare it to the clouds on the Earth.
It's sad to see the Earthset behind the moon, but I know I'll see it on the other side.
I got some pictures
I'm just gonna make sure I get some of the all zoomed angles.
It's really great to have it have the lens zoomed in as I can watch it go but also kind of step back and see
with it, with my naked eye.
And this is the moment where the moon fully disappears.
That was a beautiful, beautiful thing that I just got to witness.
Okay.