All right, Houston, I'm coming back to Ingenii.
So I did a pass on Ingenii in a more oblique view, and now I'm coming back at a more nadir view, now that some time has passed.
And it's super easy to find now, because I know exactly what I'm looking for.
So let's give you some descriptions here.
So first thing that pops up, this outer rim that I talked about, that looks like a bigger raised topographic high, that's
that was that sea but I didn't know if that sea connected and it does look like it's completely, I'd say roughly encircling Ingenii and then a crater that's around the same size as Ingenii and then a few other smaller craters in that.
So it's definitely within that boundary.
um let's see looking a little bit closer with my camera um yeah these light and dark toned albedo um kind of basin color variations it's definitely uh definitely seeing what you were describing as the lunar swirls here um i will say there's no real pattern that's coming out to me um but i am seeing some great uh variations at this angle that weren't weren't as clear in the oblique view so
I'll make sure to get you guys some pictures and you can you can tell me what you what you see And yeah these there's some craters that are popping out as well.
I wasn't a little sure before but now I'm there's like one crater That's like smack dab in the center of Ingenii and I could see that really really clearly Oh, there's another one.
That's like pretty distinct to that's
I called Ingenii like the octopus.
It's like in the northern leg of that octopus, where that elongated island is separating out the kind of northern legs and the southern legs, if you're picking up what I'm saying.
And there's a, in between, you know, kind of following along that rough boundary circular of Ingenii, I'm seeing another pretty bright crater.
And honestly, actually, it looks like there's some
light toned albedo kind of color that's associated with that as well.
And it's really associated with the, I guess it's the eastern kind of fan of that crater.
So there's a little bit of association with that crater there.
So I'll make sure to get some good pics of that.
Yeah, I noted a kind of wrinkle that I saw and I'm seeing that too.
There's actually another one.
that i'm seeing as well that's kind of close to the terminator but like more on the southern end of of engine eye but around the same strike um as that more prominent one um that's on the western side so that's pretty uh that's a little bit more noticeable now um there's also seems to maybe be like some uh
Some like lineations maybe, some alignments of maybe craters or like maybe it's a little bit hard to say, but maybe they're like these lighter tone kind of lines and those lines are going maybe like, hold on, let me think about what direction these are going.
Kind of west striking kind of roughly.
Man, kind of hard to say here, but it's almost, it's roughly perpendicular or like 45 degrees in perpendicular from that wrinkle ridge that I was, that wrinkle I was talking about.
And that looks like it's crossing like the entirety of Ingenii.
So, and I, other than that though, there's not like a ton of pattern that I'm seeing in the mare, but super cool views.
And don't worry, science, I'm going to get you all kinds of pictures.