all righty i heard that we're gonna start to see the moon so buckle up i got my cam ready oh wow oh i'm starting to see this liver this liver of the it looks like a wow what do you got yeah it's earth peeking from behind the moon and it is
Beautiful!
Hey!
Trevor!
Kelsey!
Whatever you're doing, get over here!
This is what we've been waiting for!
And look out the window!
It's, it's everything right... there.
Wow.
A beauty!
That's, that's something special.
That's, that's pretty breathtaking.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna take a moment.
Yeah, wow.
Take a look at that.
Alright, I'm doing it.
I'm blocking it out with my thumb.
It's an honor, guys.
There's really no one I'd rather be here right now in this moment than with you guys.
Back at ya.
Trevor, stop what you're doing over there.
Stop being productive.
Come on over and take a look at this.
All right, all right.
Okay, I'll start to describe.
Yeah, I'm seeing the, oh, it's just, it's hard to do the science, but I'm looking at something so special.
Yeah, I'm seeing the blues.
Dark and light blues.
The white's really standing out.
Hi, Antarctica!
Earth's South Pole looks pretty great from over here.
Oh, I can see you guys, Houston.
See those swirls of clouds.
South America.
Oh, don't worry, Earth.
I'm getting pictures of all your good angles.
You're looking great from here, Houston.
Oh, all right.
And now I take a full Earth.
So mark this time.
That's when the...
I can see it all.
There's no more shadow of the moon on the Earth.
So that's pretty crazy.
Space has never looked so black from over here.
So yes, Earth is coming right above or north of the equator or the equatorial line.
So like if north is 12 o'clock, we're looking at like 930.
Man, the Earth looks so smooth.
It looks peaceful from here, doesn't it?
It really does.
And the far side of the moon looks pretty rough compared to just how smooth and beautiful the Earth is.
I'm feeling like the luckiest person, not on Earth, luckiest person around the moon right now.
Yeah, I can see it all, Houston.
I'm starting to feel a little homesick.
But yeah, I'm looking through my camera lens.
See a little bit more detail for you guys.
I can see the greens and the browns.
See Amazon rainforests.
Maybe those are the Andes.
Absolutely gorgeous.
Angela's got some good pictures here.
Hey, mark this up.
This is definitely the first one that we're going to have to send down back to Earth.
People are going to want to see these pictures as soon as we can.
So prep yourself, Houston.
You've got some beautiful shots coming down.
I can't wait to tell you all about it.
Oh my god.
I could cry.