Hello, perfect.
This is Marie making a recording of Crook's Crater.
And so I am looking at the crater with my eyes just out the window.
I can see that it is partway between Jackson Crater and Apollo Basin.
The Crook's Crater, you can see that it has an injected blanket and a couple of rays that come out.
Um, and so that ejecta blanket is very white compared to the surrounding as it's very bright.
Um, and almost looks, um, see, it is a, it is very similar in size.
It almost looks like the majority of the race system could fit inside, um, Apollo basin.
Um, and so that ejecta blanket is about that size.
It's very bright.
It's very white.
I can't really see any shadows here based on our geometry because I'm essentially looking straight down on it.
I can't really see much structure to it, but you do see that white circle interior of the crater.
It does stand out as brighter from the ejecta blanket.
Um, it does look like it is the, um, it almost looks like a ejecta, an ejecta ray from Jackson actually goes over it.
Um, and it looks very much like a, um, it just passes right through.
So I think that it is underneath one of those rays that is coming down from Jackson crater.
Um,
It's really neat to see all these bright spots with all these rays right now in this lighting and really excited to move on to our next target.