This is Marie making observations with the camera.
I'm trying to find Bozum Ballot.
Bozum Ballot.
Nope.
Bozum Baba.
Crater right now.
Craters.
I know that they're below Apollo Basin, but it's actually, at this lighting, it's really hard to pull them out because of the morphology is making it
more difficult to find exactly where the craters are.
And so what I'm doing instead is I'm just going to take a bunch of pictures of this bottom rim below Apollo Basin at the highest resolution that I can and try hopefully that you'll be able to see.
So I'm sure that I will have captured it.
might not be in the middle of the frame.
Yeah, without that defining morphology, it's actually pretty difficult to see, but I can still see a lot of that rusty brown color down here, and so the rims of the craters aren't as well pronounced, and so it's definitely a more difficult one to find, but hopefully the pictures help.