All right, moving on to target 20, the Poincaré Crater region.
I've been staring at this one for a little bit now before I started this recording, and I'm looking for that stratigraphic relationship that's called out for this basin.
I totally understand that it's within SPA, or at least in a Western region of SPA, but I'm trying to look for this resurface volcanism
And it's just not standing out to me.
Maybe it's the illumination condition on this one.
Maybe it's because of that being near the Terminator, but I'm not picking up on the things, the actions that are outlined in the LTP.
Color's pretty diffuse across this one, not picking up any kind of color differentiation that, at least from my eyes and at this, you know, without a,
optical device to get any closer in on it.
Wrinkle ridges, not seeing any.
The basin rings, I can't see that it's a basin, but I kind of have to squint to see that in that area.
And the mari relationships, just because it's all tonal, about the same down there in this illumination conditions.
Not, not
not anything's really standing out to me.
So sorry, this one might be a dud for you guys, but really not seeing anything standing out in that area that gets me at the stratigraphic relationship or the volcanic activity in this area.
Sorry about that one, but moving on to the next one.