All right, coming up on the Dewar Crater region here.
I think I'll be, well, someone will be getting the opportunity to look at it again later.
But for right now, I see it's fairly close to the terminator edge.
I know I'm looking for a sort of albedo anomaly here and looking for some sort of like darker material that kind of comes out from the bottom of Dewar.
I think I see it.
It's more diffuse.
I don't really see, it's not like constrained or confined to a crater, but rather it appears to be darker material.
I don't see a ton of like vibrant colors, but it's definitely darker material that's kind of coming out like to the, almost like the southeast of Dewar Crater.
Let's see, size, it's probably like,
maybe one Dewar Crater diameter, long away from, again, the southeast edge of Dewar Crater.
And again, it's diffuse, even the sort of like the boundaries of the Albedo Anomaly itself are fairly diffuse.
It also kind of comes up like sort of to the east and the north a bit, again, diffused.
It almost looks like, I don't know, like someone
sprayed flour on the lunar surface or something and it sort of came out in an irregular pattern from the middle of Dewar crater.
Let's see what else I can tell you here.
Texture-wise, it doesn't appear to have an underlying consistent texture that's associated with the albedo anomaly.
I can't quite tell if there's any sort of surface texture associated with it, which makes me think there likely isn't.
It really just does appear to be a darker patch of lunar surface.
I hope that's helpful.
Looking forward to round two.