Okay, back at Dewar Crater.
I'm fortunate to get a chance to look at this twice.
I know these different illumination conditions that I'm experiencing now might bring out some different information about morphology and about
composition, as I recall.
So let me take a look here.
Again, we have Dewar Crater here.
And again, the albedo anomaly that I think I'm looking for here comes out to the south, to the east, and actually maybe in this viewing geometry, maybe more to the north than I had initially thought.
I'm still not seeing, you know, a ton jump out at me in terms of morphology of this albedo anomaly.
Dewar Crater has a pretty sharp and defined rim from what I
As you can see here, it looks like sort of the western edge of Dewar Crater.
let's see, a bit, um, maybe more like slumped than the, than the right side, than the east side of, of Dewar crater.
Um, the mid, but it is a pretty, um, sharp and beautiful crater boundary there.
Um, again, I'm seeing the albedo anomaly over top of it, some smaller craters, um, that are significantly smaller than Dewar all the way down to almost the resolution that I can see with my naked eye here.
seem to be on top of the albedo anomaly, just because they do appear to be sort of like brighter and don't seem to have that darker, that darker colored material on top of the brighter craters.
One of the younger craters at about three o'clock from Dewar sticks out particularly to my eye as being lighter in albedo than what it's sitting on, which is that darker material I described earlier.
Like I said earlier, I don't really see any morphology or texture that underlies the dark albedo material, but I do definitely see what you guys are directing me to look at, which is some really interesting material that, again, kind of looks like somebody threw a powder onto a surface, and it sort of originates from about halfway through Dewar Crater itself.
Thanks, and I'll move on to the next target.