All right, this is Andre, and I'm doing my target six.
This is the Oriental annular ring.
As I'm looking at Oriental, I'm at the, oh, thank you.
Cool.
All right, so for Oriental, I have it identified.
It's got the outer ring and the inner ring.
There is a dark mare in the middle.
It's a dark gray overall.
There's some shades of lighter gray as well.
And then on the 7 and 8 o'clock position of Orientale, I see the annular ring.
I kind of describe it as a kiss mark or a lipstick mark.
is there's a darker mare on the inboard side of the annular ring at that 7-8 o'clock position and a lighter mare on the outboard side of the annular ring on the edge there.
Those are where the lips would be and I'm noticing that the annular ring is on the
edge of the Orientale Basin where it doesn't look like the outer ring is very prominent or high.
It looks kind of flat maybe because it's lower in elevation and on the opposite side at the two or three o'clock you can see Orientale's more prominent features, rugged terrain, but more on the southeast side it looks flat
And as I notice on the most outward piece of this ring for the bottom lip, I'll call it, on the kiss, it actually starts to, as you move outward, narrow into a triangle.
And then it looks like there's a small point that's somewhat separate of this bottom lip, almost like a bottom lip ring, I would say.
So that's an interesting feature.
where I never noticed that until looking at it in detail here, the extra dark patch that's outboard of the kiss itself.
And then in between the kiss and the dark mare of orientale, there's just a very light, very small crater or patch of albedo.
So I'm not sure if that's a crater that would be above the upper lip on the left side.
And then to the left of that, there's a little
white plain field as well.
And I think that's mostly it for this annular ring, but very interesting feature.