Alright, this is Maria.
I'm gonna again talk through the Terminator because I did it once already but completely missed it the last time so I guess I'll just take a new mosaic.
So I'm gonna just take a higher resolution one.
I did just finish a mosaic before but I will do another one because I want to talk through the recording.
So, I am snaking my way up.
Oh, there's Mare Injunai.
I can really see that in the swirls there.
I'm working my way up from there, and then I'm going to snake over closer to the Terminator.
Right now, the Terminator is not in my view, but I'll get over there.
It's really interesting to see the depressions, the difference in the amount of depression that you see in these critters.
as I work my way up here.
I'm up near the North Pole now.
I'm gonna snake over a little bit more to the left.
Sounds like they're working on the toilet behind me, but glad they can get that checked out.
Now I'm up in Muscoviense.
I'm working my way back down.
There's that little tiny mare-filled crater not too far below it.
Now I'm working my way back down.
Making sure that I have- oh, now I'm back at Jules Verne with those scarps.
Back over to the left.
And now I have the Terminator in view.
There I am at that.
make sure that I get and now the moon is the earth is back in that view also absolutely incredible view here