All right, moving on to Mare Inginii in Swirls, target number five.
I've got a good view of it out the window, getting a little bit of glare coming across a portion of the moon, but it got Mare Inginii pretty clear.
One of the things that immediately stands out to me is the in-bang relationships of some of the infill.
I expected it to be a little bit rougher, but man, it really looks smooth.
The boundary relationship between the embayment and the hills, especially to the three o'clock of that feature with the 12 o'clock being the moon as it's currently oriented in the window, are really stark.
So across the three o'clock, that boundary between the embayment of the two little ears that are kind of looking
towards that three o'clock direction and the hills, if I call it that, just adjacent to them is really stark and really prominent from this orientation.
I'm looking pretty close at any color relations or colors that stick out to me.
I'm not seeing anything immediate, but the albedo of those swirls is definitely standing out to me.
I can see light tone grays, but also a medium gray that are pretty stark against the background of that infilling material.
So I was seeing at least three tones of gray
no distinct colors outside that gray spectrum from my eye right now.
The illumination is perfect right now, especially to pick up those hills that I was talking about at the three o'clock position, and not seeing many textures again.
They're just really stark across the flat part of that infilling of Mare Inginii and the textures at the
nine o'clock are starting to be a little diffuse, but that could be an illumination condition.
I talked about those contacts again, it just really stick out to me at that three o'clock between the inbaying and the hills.
And yeah, really just an amazing feature, good illumination for this one.
And those swirls are pretty prominent as I talked about in that mid to light tone gray.