All right, we're back with you in window three.
We just did a successful switch over to have a little chat with the outgoing shift, and they're going to send up a sign set up here in a little bit.
But I'm going to start with the exosphere dust get ahead target, target delta, because I see a little bit of a phenomena that's happening right on the Terminator, just proximal to
Muscovy Ents.
So I'm going to go ahead and try to describe that while I draw a little diagram of that area.
So I'm looking at Muscovy Ents and if I go 10 o'clock towards the limb, the dark limb from there, I'm seeing a little bit of color change along that horizon.
It's like a slight glare, but I could convince myself that it's maybe a little bit of
phenomena of dust lofting or some kind of exospheric phenomena that my eye is picking up only in that area.
I've looked along the entire Terminator from north to south, and that's the only area that I see that popping out at me.
So I'm going to go ahead and end this audio for that delta exosphere get ahead target and try to get some of that annotated in the OneNote.