Hey, Angela, back with you.
I am looking at high priority target 16 South Poleaitken Basin Region, one of two.
I don't have the camera anymore, so I will probably take some annotations now that I have my hand available.
It was very difficult to do annotations with the camera.
It's South Poleaitken Basin Region zoning in.
Yeah, I'm looking at it.
I wish I had the camera so I could see a little bit more detail.
So let's see.
I guess I can see a little bit of topography on the horizon.
It's not quite right dead south,
pole but there's some topography differences if I look to the east.
I see a little bit more ruggedness in the in the perimeter and then a little bit more ruggedness in the boundary just when I'm looking west just because of the Terminator shadow.
Okay, let me try and locate Schrodinger.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I see.
So that area where there's some topography differences in the perimeter on the western, the west of the South Poleaitken Basin is closer to the Schrodinger Basin zone.
Actually,
Now I'm trying to convince myself that I'm not seeing more of Schrodinger than what the picture in my LTP is showing.
Yeah, sorry, I'm just trying to take it in and identify if I can tell Schrodinger.
I'm not sure if I can but and it's a little bit cut off in my video so I can't see the exact tip but I was I was taking pictures of the screen
there they didn't look good but if you wanted Earthset pictures I needed to take picture of the screen yeah it's interesting to think about the like
us landing on the South Poleaitken Basin, but honestly, with my naked eye, I'm not entirely sure if there's much more I can say.