All right, coming up on my next, and I believe last target before the swap, wow, that time flew by, it's Tsiolkovsky Crater here and the Terminator.
So let's go in here and see that I'm looking for Tsiolkovsky, which is right along the Terminator.
I actually can see it fairly decently popping out along the Terminator now.
And I can see that the central peak pops up in the middle.
Let me see if I can take a picture of that.
Let's see.
Same orientation as the last target.
So my head is pointing sort of toward the right here.
I'm going to take one all the way at 180.
And I'm going to zoom in to 400 here.
I will say, a couple times the cameras bumped the microphone, so I don't know how well that's going to impact audio quality.
But man, that central peak of Silkoski is beauty.
I can see why it's Reed's favorite crater.
Let's see.
Mosaic of Hull Terminator.
Okay, let's see here.
Highest focal length for individual features.
Oh boy, that's gonna be a lot of images.
As I'm saying this, I think that that South Polar Region mosaic wasn't necessarily all the way zoomed in, so I apologize for that.
All right, I got that mosaic.
And now I'm looking at, for Tsiolkovsky, color-albedo texture variations, crater interior and exterior.
Let's see here.
So zooming in here, I do see, again, the crater, the inside of the crater is fully dark because it's in shadow, but you can see the central peak popping out, and it's nice and bright and white.
in the middle there, right in the middle of Tsiolkovsky's o'clock.
I can't tell, but it seems like in the sort of 10 to 11 p.m. if Tsiolkovsky was o'clock.
No, sorry, it's about nine o'clock if Tsiolkovsky was o'clock from my current body orientation.
There seems to be a light albedo patch.
I can't tell though if it's just because it's coming into the sun or not.
I'm gonna take a picture of it, see what you guys make of it.
All right.