Alright, it is Marie.
I just got back into the seat.
I'm going to try to look along the exosphere.
Just sort of look and see if I can see any light coming up.
So I have the camera in window 3 and window 2.
The one without the cab cam.
The one where I should be with my camera.
So I'm going to start looking along the limbs here.
I think Earth is going to be coming from.
Looking to see if I can... oh my camera isn't on.
My camera is on.
We're still doing a little picture wise.
We got our new card inside.
That is card 1029 is in my slot 1.
so i can actually now getting organized here so i'm going to be looking along the the rim and the exosphere trying to look and see if i can see any evidence i don't really see too much right now this looks a little bit fuzzy but it's it is hard because we know the Earth will be coming up from behind
an area that is in darkness so it's still really hard but if I look at the disappearing limb taking some images as I look at that as well just going up and down oh I could see a little spot of something off in the distance there and that's very interesting a little white spot off of the limb
I'm not really sure what that is but it's sort of like coming over from Jackson, halfway between Jackson, like following that about the 430 ray down.
It goes towards where that little light area is.
So that's the end of my...