All right, starting number target two, the limb out at Ocea procularis.
So gonna try to cover this in a series of photos at the highest focal length right along that limb.
So that's about where I left off on target one.
The highest focal length, trying to make sure the target's sharp.
As I work down, trying to get almost 75% overlap.
I'm also gonna give that more of a context by zooming out, targeting the center of target two.
And do that again with another series of images at about 75% overlap.
Definitely can see the darker parts of that target.
All right, on the limb, don't noticeably see a lot of topography picking up just based on the illumination right now.
Through the highest zoom of the lens,
Definitely see a lot of albedo change across the transition.
Take a few just centered in right on the limb, kind of pressing the extremes of the camera focus.
And again, gonna take a fully zoomed out but centered image
on that target and just work inwards.
He's in the same center spot, but just changing the zoom.
Okay, quick look at the observation actions.
I covered a lot of the focus changes that I was making.
The color is pretty stark in that area, goes from the dark
black of the part of the target that is centered on the target image seen in the LTP, and then has a pretty stark transition from that dark area into the lighter albedo areas, kind of towards Ohm Crater Crater as you make your way out that way.
I could pick it up, the resolution of Marius Hills, but not as much topography as I thought I would see along the
that complex rim.
I'm going to end voice recording here and move on to target three.