All right, starting target three, Orientale Basin.
Looking for a mosaic of the entire feature, west to east snake pattern with 50% overlap with the highest focal length.
So I'm at the 400 focal length.
First off, I'm gonna take more of a context photo of Orientale Basin with the red square dead center, and then start that mosaic.
So that should provide context for a mosaic.
I'm almost gonna go for 75% overlap and really blast across the top of Oriental, west to east.
Second pass.
Across the center of Oriental.
third pass across the bottom of Oriental.
Had a couple camera fires there that only caught one or two images out of the three stack.
And again, finishing off that target with a context photo at about mid-zoom level, about 200.
So I see that's a high-priority target.
It captured everything at least at 50% overlap.
Saw a lot of the annular ring and ejecta structure as I was taking those photos.
I'm also gonna make an annotation since that's a high-priority target with a wavefowl.
Standby for that, but incredible target overall.
The annular ring does start to pick up in that illumination condition.
In fact, I'm going to take a few more photos just zoomed in right on the part dead center that I see the annular ring sticking up the most.
That's kind of at the three o'clock position.
Hip north is up the window north.
Also some spectacular topography seen at the smaller craters that are in Oriental.
And a really good contrast between the
the darker regions at the base of Oriental, the darker rim of Oriental, kind of from the 12 o'clock to the three o'clock.
And that topography really stands out, as I said, in this illumination condition.
Took a few more zoomed in pictures that just capture the entirety of Oriental.
I'm gonna try one using the camera in a vertical position.
And I'm going to end the recording here and put an audio recording to mark that in the D5.