All right, I'm still in window two.
I'm using the camera to look for Impact Flashes, but while I do that, I'm gonna capture a full frame of the moon when this dramatic, like, half-Terminator thing creeping across the moon.
I'm gonna use the camera to keep an eye out for Impact Flashes.
Whoop, I just saw something in a wiggly line through the camera.
I wasn't holding down the,
the shutter at the time, but I saw a squiggly green line fly across the Terminator of the moon.
It definitely wasn't a point function, but it was a, maybe I saw kind of a streak, possible impact flash.
If it was, it was bright green.
It was in the northern third of the dark Terminator area.
Trying to take some pictures there, but I'll try to go ahead and annotate what I saw.
after taking a few more photos and then I'll get back to making observations.
So look out for a one note annotation from my observations of a green impact possible flash in the early parts of observing the target 27.